A long time ago, in a remote part
of Europe, in a place called "Vigrid"...
lived those who were known
as the observers of history.
The Umbra Witches, the
followers of darkness.
And the Lumen Sages, the
followers of the light.
The witches were in league with demons
and the sages were allied with angels...
they were responsible
for protecting the world...
by keeping the right
balance between them.
However, the balance was lost suddenly.
It started because a sage and a witch
violated the decrees that bound them...
and produced a child.
The woman was imprisoned
and the man was banished...
but that was only the beginning.
"The intersection of light and
dark will bring calamity to this earth."
That legend had become reality.
Right Eye and Left Eye
govern the power of creation.
The forbidden child,
who the witches took
charge of, possessed the
powers of Left Eye.
When the two eyes are brought together...
the Creator Jubileus will be made
incarnate and a New World will be created.
This is heaven's will and heaven's order.
The sages were on heaven's side,
the witches were against them...
resulting in a conflict over Left Eye.
The conflict grew and
grew until it became a
full-blown war between
angels and demons...
and the world was sent
hurtling towards destruction.
The sages and the witches died out
in droves, and the war came to an end.
The truth of their existences
slipped into obscurity.
The forbidden child grew
up to be a witch...
but she was hidden away
and sealed in a secret place...
500 years later...
The witch, who hunts
angels, has returned...
"Mass suicide in Ragna church."
Fleur de Cirey...
I am the way into the city of woe.
I am the way to a forsaken people.
I am the way into eternal sorrow.
Abandon all hope ye who enter here.
I am the way into the city of woe.
I am the way to a forsaken people.
I am the way into eternal sorrow.
Abandon all hope ye who enter here.
What's going on?
This time, I'll reveal her
for who she really is.
Look what you've done to
my outfit. You're so impatient.
You presume too much.
I'm not the partner you seek.
It was a wonderful performance, Rodin.
But of course, Bayonetta.
By the way... is my Knight ready?
Whether you'll like him
or not is another thing.
The Elfin Knight.
It is a good name for a knight's weapon.
The fun's only just started.
What's going on?
Beautiful!
MY Car!
I'm still paying the loan.
This is bad!
I must become the cornerstone of Left Eye.
Unleash all your powers of darkness.
What are you talking about?
The Creator will soon return.
You're wasting your time.
What's going on here?
My infernal partner is
telling me he's hungry!
He'd be quite satisfied
with a catch like you.
It's dinnertime, my sweet.
Oh, I forgot. There's another
reason why I'm hunting you.
I take pleasure from watching
your face distort with pain.
Transform the world into
what it should be...
That's the face I was talking about.
It gets me so excited!!
Glory be to the Creator Jubileus!
You put on quite a show.
Did you like the Knight?
Not bad.
It'll do as a sidekick for a while.
Time to open the bar.
I'll be waiting.
If I can be bothered.
I'll prepare Mysterious
Destiny with an olive.
I thought it was a mouse.
But it was you, Cheshire.
The name's Luka. It's about
time you remembered.
What is it?
Guys who stalk the ladies
never get the girl.
I wouldn't worry. I've got the looks.
Claire, Trish, Sylvia, and
Ammy are all crazy about me.
I'm impressed you have so many friends.
But it's not nice to be a peeping Tom.
Such a bad boy.
Stop it! That's professional equipment.
Not to mention, you made
a huge dent in my car!
Did I?
Did it conveniently slip your mind again?
I'll never forget what
happened 20 years ago.
Fleur de Cirey.
I'll always remember the smell.
The same smell from the day
my father died... the day I first saw you.
Father!
Father”.
As a journalist...
I'll expose you for who you are.
That's a turn on.
Remember this.
You can disappear,
but I'll know you by your scent.
The famous perfume, Fleur de Cirey.
The sweet essence of rosemary.
It doesn't suit you.
You don't know that much
about perfume do you, Cheshire?
My name's Luka!
Rosemary isn't used in Fleur de Cirey.
I wear it to ward off evil spirits.
A witch with a perfume to
ward off evil? That's a laugh.
They heard the commotion.
See you, Cheshire.
Bayonetta, wait!
This isn't good.
The reawakening is close.
Good girl.
There are demons in places like this.
You should go somewhere safer.
I am here in front of the
lthavoll Tower, in Vigrid...
a sacred site of the Ragna.
This year, the 500-year
wait for the return of
the Creator Jubileus is
meant to come to an end.
Believers all around the world
are joyously celebrating his coming.
Meanwhile, however, we
continue to hear of believers
committing suicide "to
aid the resurrection."
Only yesterday a head
priest of the Ragna...
committed suicide
with over 20 believers.
Unknown parties later partially destroyed
the cathedral housing their bodies.
This has prompted many countries
to pronounce states of emergency...
and believers of Ragna
have been asked to remain calm.
The supreme leader of the lthavoll Group,
who effectively governs this sacred city...
is preparing to appear
in public for the first time.
The humans are panicking.
It's pathetic!
Sacrificing themselves for
the resurrection of some god?
But it's thanks to these
idiots that I'm in business.
You're overcharging for
the funerals you're taking on.
You're not such a good guy, either.
I'm a good guy. As long
as I'm making money!
Anyone with a conscience wouldn't
want to handle these crazy believers.
When you look at it,
I'm quite the philanthropist.
If that's the case,
you should be donating to the Church.
And you owe me my reward.
Don't make me laugh. You
enjoy killing angels.
You take pleasure in it, right?
Isn't that enough?
Hey, wait. Slow down.
I'm sorry?
Shit!! You're the one
that trashed the cathedral.
So I say goodbye to any profit.
Consider my position!
I offer my condolences.
But the deal was information in
exchange for a troublesome funeral.
Yeah, yeah.
You're damn bossy for someone
who can't even remember her own name.
Her name is Bayonetta.
That's the name you gave her.
It's been 20 years since she awoke
from her coffin at the bottom of that lake.
But she's still one big mystery... the only
thing she remembers is that she's a witch.
Killing angels and offering
them up to demons is great and all,
but she might as well do work
more likely to make some money...
Men who blabber lead short lives.
And here he is. Mr. Balder,
the leader of the lthavoll Group.
It's fair to say that the Group's vast
fortune supports the economy of Vigrid.
If Mr. Balder, revered by
his followers, tackles this well...
Oh, that's him!
I'll give you the lowdown
on him as your reward.
He's the head of the Ragna.
Apparently, it's the first time
he's shown his face in public.
This coincides with the
first resurrection in 500 years.
Some say he has been alive
since the last resurrection.
If that's the truth, he's not human.
The lthavoll Group has cutting-edge
technology that ain't exactly in keeping
with the "good old religious hub" image.
The believers see technology
as a holy miracle.
According to informants, Balder is
a descendent of the long lost sages...
the votaries of light and enemy
of the witches spoken of in folklore.
A modern day sage...
A tasty snippet of info, right?
I'm waiting, my dear child.
She seems happy with the reward.
I am going home.
My sons are going to throw
me a birthday party.
Not paying for your drinks again?
That's your birthday present, right?
Thank you.
I'll contact you when I get a job.
Freaky undertaker.
Ciao!
You were holding that when you awoke.
Yes.
It doesn't help you to remember?
Well...
At the moment, that man,
Balder, interests me more.
He holds the key to my lost memory.
Is that what Enzo's info told you?
Call it woman's intuition.
So you're going to Vigrid?
Yes.
Take whatever you want.
I've waited 500 years
for this time to come.
The girl will find her way here in the end.
And will history repeat itself? Or...
Her path is predestined.
And I'll tell you why.
I understand the rules of
the three worlds. I see it all.
Our actions will help in the
reconstruction of the supreme world.
It's ironic that Right Eye
should choose chaos over order.
You're wrong. The world
is already in chaos.
My daughter and I must
become the Eyes of the World.
Until the three worlds
form a perfect whole,
there will be no true
order, no true salvation.
The logic of a madman.
You don't have the capacity to understand.
How unfortunate that you
cannot part with me.
The angels are working hard for me.
You too, Jeanne.
We've waited 500 years.
You must be looking forward
to seeing her again.
Everything we do is to prepare for
the coming of the Creator, Jubileus.
The Creation of a New World draws close.
The data's intact...
Yet I still couldn't capture her true form.
Where will I find you next, Bayonetta?
Ragna... the descendent of the sages...
When my father tried to uncover
the truth about the sages and witches...
Bayonetta killed him.
Awaken, dear daughter!
Daddy?
Yes... come here.
Excuse me, but who are you?
You possess the same magic powers as me.
I'm going to ask you again. Who are you?
Your extended sleep seems
to have dulled your senses.
Have I met you before?
You seem to know who I am.
I may know that better than you do.
I'm even more curious.
If you can defeat me, I'll explain.
The fun's just begun.
I remember this. What about you?
Thanks for your concern.
I get the feeling I'll remember
once I've knocked you down.
You're so slow.
Is that all you have?
I don't know. I think I have a
few other tricks up my sleeve.
What else can you do with that toy?
I'll show you. You still
want to play, right?
You must be kidding...
We're not getting anywhere.
Hey, Daddy. Is Mummy here?
If you're a good girl,
Mummy will come for you very soon.
Cereza's a good girl!
You can wait on your own?
Of course!
Cheshire. It's okay, right?
Please come quickly, Mummy.
I don't recall this bar being here.
It's a temporary outpost.
Isn't there something you want to tell me?
They sure didn't live up to
the "Knight" name, did they?
What did you do to them?
All I did was have a
shootout with some bitch.
You were shooting at yourself?
I'll repair them.
Make them a little tougher next time.
Fancy a drink?
I'm in a hurry. I look forward
to a more satisfactory Knight.
Mummy, where are you?
Mummy...
Rodin's not the only one
who wants me to take a detour.
Where am I exactly?
It's no party spot.
Mummy! Mummy!
Mummy?
Mummy!
Mummy! Mummy!
A ghost!
Can you see angels?
Mummy! Mummy!
This is troublesome!
You want to play, huh? Let me oblige.
Cheshire! Cheshire!
Cheshire?
Mummy!
Stop crying-
I hate crybabies as much
as I hate cockroaches.
And I'm not your mother!
Okay.
Mummy...
You take cover, little one.
An angel seeks my attention.
But it doesn't seem to
want to harm this little girl.
Tell me why you went to
the trouble of bringing me here.
We're going to be safe, right?
I must become the cornerstone
of resurrection.
Come on. Let's dance!
I'm going to enjoy this.
Mummy!
You find me that engaging?
You want to take me by force?
Bad boy!
It seems I'll have to teach you a lesson!
Come on, then. Let's dance, baby!!
Glory be to the Creator Jubileus!
Mummy! Mummy!
What's your name, little one?
Cereza.
Have you forgotten, Mummy?
I probably won't remember
you later, either.
What are you doing in
such a dreadful place?
Daddy told me to wait here for Mummy.
He left you alone?
I'm not alone. Cheshire's here.
You were crying like a baby.
Mummy, let's go home.
How many times do I have
to tell you? I'm not your mother.
Your father will be back soon.
But I want to stay with you, Mummy.
This is awkward.
Come here.
Okay. Mummy!
Ouch!
You're very clumsy.
What is it, Mummy?
Little one, what's this?
You gave it to me for my birthday, Mummy.
No more falling over.
Okay!
Hold on tight!
Okay. Mummy!
And no more "Mummy."
It's been forever since we
took a bath together! This is fun!
Honestly!
You nagged me into it.
You don't live with your mother?
You know I don't. I've
lived on my own for ages.
Your mother hates crybabies, too.
But I'm not a crybaby!
Mummy! Why didn't you come to see me?
Why did you leave me alone?
I don't know.
Because I'm not your mother.
I hate you!
You were all alone?
Any friends?
Cheshire.
It's so pretty! Just like snow!
What a pushover...
I don't recall asking for room service.
You should think about your methods.
Someone could sue.
Not so many methods to
choose from with a witch.
Oh!
Who is he?
Cheshire... No.
He's a perverted old guy
who photographs ladies.
Pervert?
Mummy?
You have a daughter?
Of course not.
But the process of making
a baby interests me.
Well, I'm not interested...
Not interested... at all...
Not... interested... at all!
Oh! He fell!
Is the old guy dead?
No ghost is coming to
fetch him, so he must be alive.
Unfortunately.
I'm not an old guy.
Asleep already?
You're very persistent.
How much longer do you intend to hang
around with that toy of yours, Cheshire?
The name's Luka.
Bayonetta, what's happening in this city?
I don't care.
Why are you here, then?
It's none of your business.
It's everything to do with me...
you killed my father.
I've heard enough of that assumption.
Don't play innocent with me.
My father was a journalist...
who devoted his life to solving
the mystery of the sages and the witches.
Though he probably never
dreamed he'd be killed by a witch...
By revealing your identity,
perhaps I can uncover the truth he sought.
According to his notes,
about 500 years ago...
the sages and the witches
suddenly disappeared...
and their legend was lost.
However, the witch, Bayonetta,
reappeared 20 years ago.
And now a descendent of the sages,
Balder, has come forward.
It must have something
to do with the resurrection.
You're going to see Balder, right?
Possibly...
You'll understand why you killed
my father when you regain your memory.
And what happened that day...
Mummy!
Mummy! Where did you go?
Little one.
I'm busy babysitting.
I wish you could take over.
Well, that's a good idea.
Mummy!
Mummy. Where did you go? I was lonely.
If you cry for one more second,
I won't sleep with you.
You'll never leave me again, right?
What's up, little girl?
I'm a... I'm a crybaby.
So my mummy left me.
Bayonetta's gone?
She didn't!
She was serious about me babysitting you?!
Let's go look for your Mummy together.
Yes, old guy.
Listen, I'm not old, okay?
Let's get 90309-
The two eyes that govern the
world are about to be reunited.
With the resurrection of the Creator
Jubileus at hand, the angels are restless.
You will be sacrificed in
order to awaken Left Eye.
We are in consensus...
All of this is to fulfill our goal.
For the Creation of a New World!
That's a nice car.
It is a pity it'll end up in the scrapyard.
What is it?
What? Something's coming this way?
Can you see something?
No.
They piss me off.
She put on quite a show.
Your mummy is easy to follow.
Yes!
You've had enough fun. It's my turn now.
Mmmm.
Ask me out with a nicer car next time.
Not again... this is taking its toll on me.
May my soul reside with
the Creator, Jubileus.
Old guy. We haven't caught up
with Mummy yet, right?
Nearly there. Be patient.
Okay.
Once we see the airport, we'll be close
to the island with the lthavoll Tower.
We'll find your mother.
Reafly?
Yeah.
As long as the airport itself is intact.
Here's the exit.
Wow!
What's going on?
This is overdoing it,
even by Bayonetta's standards!
That ghost is big!
Mummy!
Retreat! Retreat!
The more I hunt angels,
the more powerful I feel.
What a turn on!
It suits you!
Damn Bayonetta! If I can't find
transport we're going to be in trouble.
We're going to escape in that, little girl.
Wait!
What is it?
Put me down.
You'll get burned.
Did you see Mummy?
Ghosts.
Ghosts?
Ghosts are coming!!
Don't be silly. I can't see a thing.
I smell rosemary.
Old guy?
Little girl, your older
brother's eyesight is good.
It's time to go.
Put these on!
Very well.
What are they? Could they be angels?
Little girl, is this really happening?
Whoa!
Hey, are they really angels?
They look like monsters.
You actually chased me here?
You must be mad.
Mummy!
Is that an angel, too?
She'll be fine!
Little girl, is your
mother fighting the monsters?
Mummy's a witch.
She's strong and protects others.
A witch... who protects others?
Yeah, of course!
I'm going to become a
strong witch to protect Mummy.
Now, how pretty will the explosion be?
Great! Mummy beat the ghosts!
Take these back.
What?
Are they magic glasses?
No.
You can see ghosts
without glasses, you know.
Angels? But I can still smell her.
Mummy!
Little one... are you crying?
No, I'm not!
Good.
I wanted you to babysit her at home.
Luka.
How many times have I told you?
I'm not Luka. I'm Cheshire!
Will you stop taking the piss?
This is Cheshire.
What?
Will you take us to the
lthavoll Tower? Cheshire...
You're in luck. That's just
where this helicopter is headed.
I'm seeing this through to the end.
The Umbra witch...
possesses the outstanding
power the sage spoke of.
The two eyes of darkness and light...
that observed this world for many years.
The Creation of a New World is here.
Umbra witch, receive the
blessings of Jubileus.
Here we are!!
It's good to see you, my dear.
The hardship is nearly over.
The signpost to your
lost memory is waiting.
Give me everything you've got.
Everything...
Damn!
It's on our tail!
Oh! We're safe?
Where's Bayonetta?
You're late. I've been waiting.
I hope you're going to
entertain me this time.
You'll find out soon.
This time, I'll make you
spill everything you know.
Do your best... if you can.
Isn't it a shame that you have
to fight with such a crappy weapon!
I can still sense your fear.
Fear?
Your memory will make things clear.
You instinctively fear
the fate that you bear.
"The intersection of light and
dark would bring calamity to this earth."
It's an ancient saying.
The calamity resulted in the
downfall of the witches and the sages.
The effects can be felt even now...
centered around you,
the forbidden child.
Put simply, the Creator's power
is known as the Eyes of the World.
You possess half of the power...
the power of Left Eye.
Intruder...
Where am I?
I've been waiting, Left Eye.
Witch Jeanne...
Hindering the coming of the
Creator Jubileus will not be permitted.
You think an angel has the
right to order a witch around?
Beat it.
Foolish one.
Left Eye, I'll be waiting
by the side of my Lord.
Well, this looks like a fun place!
More entertaining than your bar.
How many times do I have to say?
I'm not who you're looking for.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here are your guns.
I hope they'll satisfy me this time.
And more to boot.
Scarborough Fair. Your new Knight.
It's had a radical transformation.
See you in the bar.
If I ever miss the boredom...
We seem to be on an equal footing now.
That's right. I'll try
to be gentle with you.
Let's be clear, if you lose to me,
that girl of yours will disappear.
That's it! That's the idea!
I remember...
Jeanne, in accordance with witch law,
we will now test your worthiness
to be one of our greatest warriors.
Choose an opponent.
I'll take the outcast.
That is not permitted!
It is not allowed to engage with
the one cursed with tainted blood.
I remember... I've been here before.
At last! Let the memories return!
Your memory... do you fear it?
Can you feel your strength
increase as your memory returns?
It is the mission of us
witches to protect Left Eye.
Even if the forbidden child possesses it.
Us witches?
Mama. Mama.
The Left Eye of the witches is ours now.
Left Eye...
Let us seek out the Creator Jubileus.
The greatest treasure of
my clan, "Left Eye"...
I will not hand it over!
Jeanne, you saved me.
When you lost your mother,
you also lost the will to fight.
It was the only thing
I could do to protect Left Eye.
We were lucky to have had
an innocent childhood.
Yes...
You were my only friend...
And that silly doll of yours.
Jeanne...
500 years ago... why did you choose me?
Everyone hated me.
To become one of the most powerful witches,
I had to defeat the strongest opponent.
That's all.
You cannot run from the sage Balder.
Bring an end to it all.
That's your destiny.
Fight, win and create a new path.
You can do it!
Jeanne!
Jeanne.
Mummy!
Got here without any fuss.
Seems like I'm a guest, too.
Mummy...?
Little one, what's your greatest treasure?
Cheshire?
No.
Cheshire's a friend.
This is my greatest treasure.
You should never let a treasure go.
Whatever happens.
I know! I won't cry any more.
I want to be like you.
You never run away from anything!
I'm gonna try hard.
You're not going on your own?
You'll tag along anyway, right?
Right?
It's as if we're being asked inside.
That's very generous.
My darling daughter...
It's time to open the "Eyes of the World."
It's Daddy! Daddy's voice!
Wait!
It's Daddy!
This way!
Little one...
Mummy! Mummy's here too, Daddy!
I've waited a long time
for this family reunion.
Save him...
Did you have a good journey?
Yes. Mummy's very strong!
I see...
I was scared of the ghosts,
but Mummy told me not to cry.
You've grown strong, Cereza.
Yes!
Today you must sleep in your own room.
But I don't want to.
There's so much I want to tell you.
You can tell me tomorrow.
Oh... okay.
Good girl.
Sweet dreams!
Yes... good night.
Mummy...
It's okay... I won't cry
anymore, even if I'm alone.
Clever girl.
Good night, Mummy.
How did you bring me from the past?
The past... what?
I opened the door of space-time distorted
by the influence of Jubileus's coming.
I wanted you to see this foolish
world through innocent, untainted eyes.
So this man is...?
The last surviving Lumen Sage.
The cause of everything. And...
little one's... no, my Daddy.
I've been waiting 500 years...
for a chance to purge
the chaotic worlds...
of heaven, hell and the human world...
With the resurrection
of Jubileus, the three
worlds will become
void and be reborn.
Cereza, you and I will
become gods of this new world!
Leave it to the leader
of the lthavoll Group.
You're the master of blowing your own horn.
But it's not enough to make the headlines.
You're Luka, right?
I've been watching your progress.
Like your father,
you've become a great journalist.
You knew my father?
He did some good
investigative work on my plan...
Everything was fine until
he found Cereza...
but he was a little too ambitious.
Wh... What are you doing?
The scent of rosemary...
That's the scent... I
remember from that day.
I see it now... it was you...
Your angels killed my father...
My condolences on your loss.
Bayonetta, please forgive me.
Never mind that.
Well, even that little crybaby
decided never to cry again.
So it's time for me to man up
and bring everything to an end!
Such crude methods for a journalist.
Luka!
Cereza, the journey ends here.
I don't understand.
Why did you summon the younger me?
Why bother with such
convoluted plans to bring me here?
You lost your memory completely...
In order to open Left Eye, you must
reclaim your power, your experience,
and your love.
Not only did you try to
throw the world into chaos...
but you killed Mama.
What do you know of love?
It wasn't me who killed Rosa.
The distortion of the world tore us apart.
Angels anxious for the
resurrection killed her.
The angels chose to fight you and became
sacrifices to enhance your magic powers.
Jeanne was the final ingredient.
She unleashed your full power
and regained the core of you.
Your memory, in other words.
Jeanne did very well.
You're crazy.
I beg to differ.
It is not me who's crazy,
it's the world itself.
Can you really shoot me?
You don't think I can?
You're going to shoot me? Your father?
My dearest daughter, Cereza.
Let's hail the dawning of
a new order and a new world.
The rebirth of the Creator?
You must be kidding...
Jubileus... walk with us!
We must become one with Jubileus.
The time has come at last.
We will become the Creator of a New World.
Don't tell me that's Jubileus?!
Bayonetta!
It's wonderful!
My daughter, this is the
beginning of the new world.
Cereza...
Mama...?
Please... save him...
His soul is trapped in madness.
Save him...
Yes, Mama...
I must do now what I couldn't then.
Jeanne, you're still alive?
"The intersection of light and
dark will bring calamity to this earth."
So it has another meaning.
No,this is the real meaning!
You're too late...
You are not needed in this new world.
I'm not?
Return our greatest treasure to us!
Jeanne... You must
open your eyes!
Finish what started 500 years ago.
No time to hesitate! Cereza!!
I certainly need to keep my eye on you!
You're not dead yet?
You fools... What
have you done?!
What have you done?!
A regular pet isn't good enough!
It would appear so.
My dear daughter, Cereza.
How dare you turn a sword on me?
I won't have it!
This is celestial power, huh?
Cereza, you must follow through.
Of course... but we must do it together.
What?
I've got a special weapon.
Sounds good to me!
Queen of Inferno, Sheba.
A fitting match for him!
Here we go! Okay .
Transform the world...
There's still time. Open your eyes, Cereza.
Father? You don't learn, do you?
Mama was trying to save you.
Such nonsense.
The Creation of a
New World will bring true salvation.
You're such an egoist.
What's the fun in creating a
world where you get your own way?
I rather like this chaos.
You struggle in vain!
No, you struggle in vain.
Got it.
Let's finish it off.
I'll feed you all the magic powers.
Now, understand Mama's feelings.
Daughter...
this lowly world tore Rosa and I apart.
The world must return to its proper state!
It must be!
A pointless wish.
Mama's waiting.
Bye... Daddy!
I love you, Balder.
Rosa”.
Farewell to the last sage.
Bayonetta...
It's been a year since
Bayonetta disappeared.
I've got all this funeral work
and she's not around to help.
My business is over.
Hey, Rodin. Do you think
she's gone for good?
Who's to know? I just help out
people who are looking for weapons.
That's all.
If you say so.
Father... sorry it took so long.
Although I may have
published it, it's not selling.
Wonder where she went?
But we'll meet again, won't we, Bayonetta?
They're tenacious.
I should go before the
church becomes a pile of corpses.
Isn't it ironic that you're a nun!
It is not as bad as you think.
You should try it yourself.
Teaching in high school suits me just fine.
But before I go home...
We've got to teach those bad boys a lesson.
Let's dance, baby!!