Thank you for waiting.
The train bound for Shin Ikebukuro will arrive at Platform 1.
Please watch your step while boarding.
Thank you for using Tokyo Metro, Shin Marunouchi line.
This train is bound for Shin Ikebukuro.
We have an announcement to make.
Tokyo Metro is cooperating with the city of Tokyo
and will take custody of anyone under 20 years old after 9 PM,
in accordance with the Tokyo Juvenile Protection Curfew Ordinance.
Anyone under 20 years old is prohibited from going out after 9 PM...
without being accompanied by their parents or carrying their consent form.
If you are under 20 years old and do not have a consent form,
please come to a ticket window or seek an attendant for your safety.
Do you wish... to be eaten by me?
The train is coming to Platform 1.
Please wait behind the white line.
They are moving around quite visibly.
Shall we go?
Wait a minute.
Gone? Escaped?
What?
They said it was recaptured by another unit.
Where?
Who... who are you?
Confirming the target is destroyed.
There are two witnesses.
Recovery unit, hurry.
A dead body, dead body.
You, who are you?
Fujimura-kun?
Mana-chan?
What? Hiiragi.
You...!
This is the Old Ones.
The Old Ones.
Why are you here?
Matsuo-kun.
Fuji, let's get out of here.
Y-Yes.
Hiiragi.
Dammit. Hurry up!
Drive.
What do you want?!
You are...
We'll be caught..
Dammit!
Witnesses are escaping by car.
We are now in pursuit.
Ground units, hurry to the scene.
They're chasing us!
Point the way!
Come in, SIRRUT, this is Fujimura.
We are being chased by a Tower helicopter!
H-Help!
Yanagi-san!
Calm down, Fujmura-kun.
Yes.
We will send you the escape route within one minute.
Meanwhile, send us the information you have acquired.
U-Understood.
Tsuki-chan, gain control of the traffic system immediately.
Yes.
Also, hack into the District of Land and Transportation Bureaus' computer system.
Is it all right, Mogari-san?
Yes.
There!  Right, right!
Stupid! That's a one-way street!
I... I'm sorry.
I've got the escape route.
Ah, ahead, right at the traffic signal.
That’s the wrong way!
Shut up!
We went off the route...
Fuck the route!
I'll get us back on track.
Fuji-kun!
Behind us! They are coming!
It's not over!
Yanagi-saaan!
Go on.
Speed it up, now!
Screw it, I don't care anymore!
Now.
Yes.
It's over.
We've got to keep going.
There's blood...
Lay off.
Is that guy dead?
I feel relieved now.
My poor car is covered with scratches...
It's the ultimate sacrifice.
My name is Hiiragi Mana.
What's yours?
Huh?
Don’t you guys know each other?
No.
She just rescued me... from that scary guy.
S-She did?
From Tower's Old Ones?
Why do you know about the Old Ones?
What are you guys doing?
What is Tower?
Who are they?
That's what we want to know...
We are trying to expose the identity of Tower.
Do you have a grudge against them?
What happened back there?
Why was that monster... dead?
Because I killed it.
Who are you?
It's from headquarters?
From Yanagi-san?
Kisaragi Saya, don't you wish to shoot Nanahara Fumito?
Fumito...
I am inviting you back to headquarters.
We'll talk... then.
The winner receives a reward...
The loser receives punishment...
Fumito-sama.
The governor of Tokyo is
requesting a lunch meeting
regarding the punishment of all those who violated the Juvenile Protection Curfew Ordinance,
which has been in effect since last month.
If you become the governor of Tokyo soon,
there won't be a need for such wasteful meetings, Yuka-kun.
I agree with you.
How old are you now?
28 years old.
You were only a high-school student six months ago.
You want to forget your bad memories quickly, don't you?
I appreciate that you know how I feel.
Next is the meeting with the Ambassador of the United States.
He wishes to move up the meeting date.
Recent appointments and reports are all like that...
Considering the financial strength and influence of our company, Seventh Heaven,
and the secret you and your family have been protecting,
even this is not enough.
You are ambitious.
Fumito-sama.
What happened, Kuto?
The one that escaped from the laboratory was destroyed.
We have finished recovery from inside of the subway,
but there are two witnesses.
We were outmaneuvered?
I disposed of the ones that let them escape.
Next time, I will handle it personally.
I don't think you'll be able to get them.
Saya's showed up.
We should be going.
What's wrong?
Come here quickly.
Come in.
Hiiragi, I understand the situation.
Y-Yes.
Welcome, Kisaragi Saya. I am Mogari Kuroto.
Why do you know me?
Ukishima.
An experiment took place there that killed all the residents.
Brutality is the only word sufficient to describe the manner in which they were killed.
However, there was one survivor from that experiment.
It was you. Kisaragi Saya.
Why do you have these?
Itsuki sent these to me.
He called himself Tomofusa Itsuki when he was talking to you, didn't he?
He hacked the Tower's surveillance cameras and kept sending us data,
even if it was only bits and pieces.
Is that person...
He did not work with us, but he was a member of SIRRUT.
Is Itsuki...?
Dead.
Itsuki participated in the Ukishima experiment in order to expose everything about Tower.
Tower?
An organization that Nanahara Fumito is secretly controlling.
Officially, Fumito is a chairman of Seventh Heaven — a giant conglomerate,
not only in Japan, but also in the rest of the world.
He has strong political connections,
and is said to have had a part in the new Juvenile Protection Curfew Ordinance.
But the only thing he's interested in is that other organization.
That is Tower?
Fumito is trying to accomplish something using the power of both Seventh Heaven and Tower.
Something?
Unfortunately, we do not know exactly what that “something” is.
But we know that many people have been killed because of it.
And that things called “Old Ones” are involved.
How do you know all this?
Because I researched, using all my time, money and power.
Why?
Because Nanahara Fumito took away my freedom.
And...
The videos that Itsuki had sent were just fragments,
so I only saw bits and pieces of your life in Ukishima,
but I could tell you were almost a different person now
and that you were deceived by Fumito.
You came to Tokyo to look for Fumito, didn't you?
For the past six months, you've been coming around here and making trouble each time.
However, none of this was reported in the news.
If they were not reported…
They could not hide them.
In Japan, censorship of the internet is currently very strict,
but we still have two good hackers.
She is one of them — Tsukiyama Hiro-san.
And the other is...
The other is another story, but this is Fujimura Shu-kun.
And the big one here is Matsuo Iori-kun.
That's me.
Mana introduced herself in the car, didn't she?
I am Yanagi Haruno, a secretary of Mogari-san.
These are all members of SIRRUT who come to this mansion.
There are many others who support us on the internet.
Everyone wants to abolish all the strange regulations and ordinances,
such as the Juvenile Protection Curfew Ordinance and internet censorship.
Where is Fumito now?
These days, for his protection,
his whereabouts are not being made public.
Do you mean you don't know?
I have ways of finding him.
Members of SIRRUT connected through the network will...
provide you with Fumito’s information.
So, I need you to use your power to assist me, Kisaragi Saya.
Nanahara Fumito is my prey.
Do not forget that.
Is it really okay to bring her into our group?
Thank you.
Here, Tsuki-chan.
What? Are you unsatisfied?
No, it’s not that; I just don't like her attitude.
There's no way we can trust her.
She doesn't talk and she's so full of herself.
But she is so beautiful.
Ah, so you don’t care how she acts as long as she looks good?
Did you forget about how she squeezed your cheeks?
I give up.
It’s Mogari-san’s decision.
I know that. But I still don’t like it.
Tsuki-chan, you agree with me, don’t you?
Tsuki-chan is upset because Mana can’t play with her.
She has to show our new member around.
Fuji-kun, I'm not gonna show you the cute cat video I downloaded yesterday...
Nooooooo!
You'll show it to me, won’t you?!
Don’t bother Fuji.
You are so mean, Matsu-san!
Isn't this a huge mansion?
Mogari-san is also the president of Sysnet, which is the most popular...
company among recent graduates.
Saya is... a beautiful name.
Your last name, Kisaragi, is a very nice name as well.
That is not my name.
But...
Oh, wait.
This is your room.
The bathroom is over there and a change of clothes is…
This is fine.
No, you have to wash them.
I'll ask Yanagi-san for the clothes.
Understood.
Everyone else is commuting here from their homes,
but I asked Mogari-san to let me live here.
And my room is next to yours.
So, if , if...
if you're having any trouble or you need anything, let me know.
I don’t need anything, but there is a place I want to go.
Why are you following me?
Huh?
Why are you coming with me?
It's dangerous to be alone... well maybe not...
but, well, you don’t have a cell phone,
so SIRRUT can't reach you, right?
Do you want to have another encounter like yesterday?
But I want to be with you.
Why?
I don’t know...
I didn't know there was a house like this in such a place.
Can you see?
See what? Is there something else?
It’s not a house.
It’s a shop.
Long time no see, Saya.
It’s only been 6 months.
It’s been a while since I've seen the old Saya.
Please.
Thank you very much!
Saya.
I don’t want it.
It’s delicious!
I’m glad.
Umm, what kind of shop this is?
A shop that fulfills your wishes.
Huh?
It’s a variety shop.
Are you a regular patron of this shop?
I've only been here a few times.
There's something I want here.
It's a little surprising that Saya brought company.
I just followed her.
She allowed it.
At Ukishima, I was able to be near you through him, but I can't say I was of any help.
You brought yourself back on your own.
Even so, your words helped me.
Then, what do you want today?
I want a sword... A strong sword.
Amazing, so many..
I expected you would select that one.
What is the price?
You can pay me when you return.
Understood.
Wait.
Will you stay with Saya?
But... I get the feeling that she doesn't want me there...
You are able to enter the shop.
That’s enough.
Well, what's the relationship between you two?
I'm a shop owner and she's my customer, that’s it.
But the longer people live, the more they start to care about one another.
Their fates are already bonded.
Wait, Saya!
This is an announcement from Tokyo Metro.
It is now past 8 PM.
In accordance with the Tokyo Juvenile Protection Curfew Ordinance,
anyone under 20 years old is prohibited from going out after 9 PM
without being accompanied by their parents or carrying their consent form.
If you are under 20 years old and don't have a consent form, please return home immediately.
This is an announcement from Tokyo Metro.
It is now past 8 PM.
In accordance with the Tokyo Juvenile Protection Curfew Ordinance,
anyone under 20 years old is prohibited from going out after 9 PM
Oh, I'm sorry.
I figured I'd use my phone... to tell
the others about it...
without being accompanied by their parents or carrying their consent form.
If you are under 20 years old and don't have a consent form,
About what?
please return home immediately...
About that.
That area under surveillance.
There was an announcement just now, wasn't there?
After 9 PM, juveniles like us can't go outside without permission.
Sign-armband: Juvenile Protection
Hey, it's time for you to go home.
What?
Okay.
That's why rumors about you started circulating on the internet almost instantly.
Afternoon news: Due to business restructuring of Seventh Heaven conglomerate, Mr. Amino Mitsuharu will replace Nanahara Fumito as the Japanese representative. Mr. Amino Mitsuharu is the stepfather of the present governor of Tokyo, Ms. Amino Yuuka, and is the Head of Economic Research...
A mysterious girl roaming around by herself,
despite looking just like a juvenile.
You can't take rumors like that lightly.
Information not just about Seventh Heaven,
but also Tower can be found hidden among them.
It's suspected that the current regulations are also aimed at suppressing such rumors.
Nowadays, compared to news broadcasts or newspapers, the internet is much faster,
so you can't really hide or fabricate information.
And the people who're most familiar with the internet and have the largest online presence are...
Juveniles, right?
Mogari-san also said that the
censorship is probably intended
to ensure that the children who control the future of Japan
will not question the present government, or Tower.
But why would they go to such lengths to do that?
This person, Nanahara Fumito, is...
S-Sorry!
I've been doing all the talking.
Hey, wait, you two!
Huh?
What's the matter?
It's still only barely past 8 PM...
It's not about the time.
You there,
I'm sorry, but could you show me your identification card?
There's something I want to check—Hey!
Wait!
Stop right there!
Sign-armband: Juvenile Protection
You are—
You little brat!
Number 312, please check in.
She's really amazing.
What are you doing?!
We need to get out of here!
I told you...
I told you it was dangerous, didn't I?!
I'm sorry!
By any chance, were we exposed, or...?
I don't think so.
They only talked to Saya.
Why only Saya-san?
But the inspectors were all defeated in the blink of an eye.
That's why there's not even a scratch on me.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thanks, Tsuki-chan.
Hiiragi, if that happens again, you should just run away.
Just leave that broad behind.
But she's a beauty...
She's not my type.
Matsu-san's type is Yanagi-san, isn't it?
T-That's not true, you moron!
Really, you should've just left her behind.
I figured I'd just be in the way if I stayed...
You couldn't bear to leave her behind?
I... guess so.
Mana-chan, I couldn't really get information about your father...
Sorry.
It's been four months now, right?
I think we should reall—
It'll be fine!
Mana, I'll try hard enough for the both of us!
So, you...
Tsuki-chan...
You're right.
Yeah! We're a team!
We'll expose all the evils in this world!
SIRRUT!
We won't let something like this bring us down!
Thanks, everyone.
I see... a katana.
You're going to use that...
...to kill Fumito?
That's right.
Mogari-san, carrying firearms or swords within SIRRUT... no, within this building, is...
I think it's okay in this building.
Let's just prepare for it, so as not to arouse suspicion.
May I call you "Saya"?
Call me whatever you like.
Well then, Saya, Tower is looking for you.
According to information gathered by Tsukiyama-kun and the others,
Tower is running a circular on you through Seventh Heaven.
They've increased the number of inspectors within Tokyo,
and are quietly searching for you.
It'd be great if you could avoid a recurrence of today's incident if possible.
I have no intention of listening to your instructions.
I know that.
However, if you really want to kill Fumito,
wait for your chance.
I'll definitely create one for you,
no matter what I have to do.
What happened between you and that man?
Fumito and I are...
cousins.
Follow me.
Do you know the "Shujikimen"?
Yes.
An agreement with aberrations known as Old Ones.
A compact that allows them to feed on humans, but only up to a set number.
And that is the "Shujikimen".
Fumito and I were from the clan that
hid and protected the "Shujikimen" for generations.
That's right...
we were the descendants of the clan that made the agreement with the Old Ones.
The Mogari family, in the foreground,
will ensure that the controlling governments of each era
follow what's in the agreement.
And the Nanahara family, in the background,
will use the secret powers of Ugetsu to protect the Mogari family.
As a combination of the two, we were called "Tower".
Until Fumito chose to take a different path.
You are the first person I've ever brought here.
Six years ago, Fumito came here with an armed military unit.
His objective was the "Shujikimen".
He killed my father, who was the head of the Mogari family, and my mother.
He took everything I had away from me,
right in front of my eyes.
Saya... kill Fumito for me.
kill... Fumito for me.
I'm searching for Fumito for my own reasons.
I know that.
However, you hate him too, don't you?
Oh, welcome back!
...Or not.
Um... I meant to say thanks...
What for?
Regarding the inspectors earlier...
I'm the reason you got caught up in that mess, aren't I?
But you still escaped and took me with you.
Thanks—
Oh!
Now what?
G-Good night.
I'll talk to her more tomorrow!
At least a minute more...
Saya!
Saya-chan!
Saya-san!
Saya.
Saya!
Stop it!
Saya,
when you lived in Ukishima, and had forgotten everything, I really liked you...
However, what attracted me to you really was....
Fumito-sama.
Everything's ready.
I see.
We'll meet soon, Saya.
What is this outrageous thing?
When are you gonna start following either Tsuki-chan's or Fuji-kun's example?
I'm not techno-savvy in the slightest.
I even struggle with e-mail.
Even though I'm Mogari-san's secretary, I'll still help you guys out.
I'm not a superwoman like you.
You're not being adorable at all.
I'm fine with not being adorable!
I'm just a driver who's got to deal with every single problem around here!
Geez...
What's wrong, Mana-chan?
I didn't reach my one-minute goal.
Huh?
You're so lucky that you and Matsuo-kun can be so friendly with each other.
W-What are you talking about?
You don't like being friendly?
I-I'm not saying that, am I?
I did it!
Huh?
Nanahara Fumito's plans!
We know about one of them!
What?!
High school?
That's right.
This school has been receiving benefits from Seventh Heaven.
There'll be many such organizations, won't there?
Not just schools,
but also other charitable organizations like hospitals and orphanages.
There are so many—
Oh those!
I divided the work with Tsuki-chan, and we checked every one of them!
And then... Bingo!
You mean Tsuki-chan found it, right?
Um, yeah...
Tsuji Private School.
Tomorrow, Nanahara Fumito will be giving a lecture there.
You're really something, managing to get your hands on this info.
Regarding that... you see,
we searched for loopholes in the network security...
You mean Tsuki-chan did, right?
Is this information reliable?
Besides hacking skills,
I was also taught the importance of determining the reliability of information, so...
What will you do, Saya?
I'll go.
Hey wait,
isn't it obvious that the school will have some unbelievably tight security?
If you just go like that,
you won't even be able to pass through the gate, much less get near Fumito.
Regarding that, I've... I've worked hard on it!
The locations of all the guards are at my fingertips!
Fujimura-kun, you're really something!
What about the uniform?
Even if you infiltrate the school under the guise of a student,
it's impossible to get your hands on one,
and even if you wanted to make one, the lecture's tomorrow...
Um...
Huh?
I may be able to help with the uniform.
Wait.
It doesn't look like it's going to stop raining.
Wait up, Saya!
The sound is great!
The GPS is working perfectly too!
But I didn't expect Mana-chan to be a student at Tsuji Private School...
Hiiragi managed to tell Mogari-san herself that she'd be going.
Please let me go with Saya.
Please!
Saya...
Do as you see fit.
We should give it everything we've got as well.
Yeah!
You're right.
If they encounter any danger, make sure you rush in to the rescue, got it?
Sure!
I know you're worried,
but let's provide as much support as we can, okay?
Yes.
You don't look like you're walking around in an unknown school.
I'll stand out more if I'm on my guard.
Y-You're right.
Did you know?
Huh?
That this school has ties with them?
Yes.
A stone monument thanking them for their donations was erected,
and the teachers told us about it.
Actually, I wanted to leave this school, but...
Hiiragi-san!
Huh?
You've come.
Y-Yes.
I thought you would be relaxing,
since it's still winter break.
It's troublesome for someone alone like you, isn't it?
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
There's the matter regarding your father too, so I guess it's inevitable,
but I'm glad that you look well!
Ah, it's almost time...
Let's go.
I'm glad that we don't have to sit according to our class.
Our school is generally like that.
What were you talking about just now...
Huh?
Regarding your father...
Never mind, it's fine.
Everyone, please be quiet.
We'll start our special lecture now.
The speaker will be Mr. Nanahara Fumito.
Nanahara... isn't that Seventh Heaven's...
Are you serious?
So that's why we weren't allowed to bring in our mobile phones.
What's going on?
Please calm down.
Please leave the lecture hall, following the instructions we have given.
We should hurry up and leave.
Saya!
Mana!
What's happening?
I-I don't know!
After the alarm went off, there were screams!
But the school director's not moving at all!
Saya, it's been a long time, hasn't it?
Saya!
Fumito!!!
Saya, I'm sorry to disappoint you after you came all the way here.
You're strong, so I thought it would be
troublesome if things remained this way.
That's why... I'll play around with you a little.
What... am I doing...
Saya!
S-Saya!
Mana!
Saya...
Saya!
Matsu-san!
What?!
Let's go!
Fuji!
Hold on tight!
B-Blood...
Saya.
Mana, let's go!
Sure.
I'll go.
The rest of you, hurry up with the collection.
Saya, move aside please.
I'll open it.
So you're Saya.
What's the matter?
Does it hurt?
You're a monster, just like that one you killed.
Shut up!
Saya!
Don't worry about me!
This is the end!
You can't kill humans, right?
Saya!
That's why you're unable to protect anyone.
Get in!
Quickly!
She needs treatment quickly!
She escaped.
Yeah.
The blood collection went exactly as planned.
We'll send it to the lab now.
Thanks for the hard work.
In other words, we were tricked.
I'm sorry.
Tsuki-chan...
It's not your fault, Tsuki-chan.
I allowed them to carry out the plan.
It's my responsibility.
Mogari-san.
But I'm glad both of them managed to come back safely.
Even though my car got wrecked again.
It's an honorable battle scar.
Well, someone did get injured.
Compared to that, a little scratch is nothing...
Didn't you have something against Saya-san?
She got injured protecting Hiiragi, didn't she?
Even though she could've ran away on her own if she had wanted to...
I think I'm starting to see her in a new light.
How's Saya-san?
She said she's not going to the hospital,
so Hiiragi got angry and ran after her.
Wasn't Mana the one who hacked the lock on the lecture hall?
I think so.
Mana... cracked the code.
Well, one thing led to another.
And within such a short time...
That's so like her.
Now we have another outstanding hacker in our organization.
I'm not outstanding at all!
Mana's the amazing one!
I'm just trying to keep up with what she taught me.
She's totally out of my league.
Will Mana go back to being a hacker because of this?
No!
You mustn't ignore your wounds!
You can't possibly be fine after suffering such an injury!
It's really not a big deal.
Saya!
I'm really sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
But it's...
it's my fault.
I've had enough.
I'm really fine.
The wounds have closed up.
Why?
Even if you don't know the reason, I'm telling you I'm fine.
Do you understand now?
Yeah.
You said you've had enough?
Did you have similar experiences before?
My mother passed away early,
so it's just been me and my father.
My father is bad at cooking, but he tried very hard to learn how to cook for me.
Even though he was always busy with work, he gave it his all for my sake.
You see, my father was a journalist.
He loved reading the newspapers from back when articles were still printed on paper
and delivered to the reader.
When we met occasionally, he would always say that
journalists needed to be curious and have inquisitive minds.
He said that they have to be knowledgeable about a variety of things,
remain unbiased by the information around them,
and provide thorough coverage of the news.
I was often reminded that
once I made a decision, I should always stick with it to the end.
A year ago, my father targeted Seventh Heaven for his next big scoop.
However, he immediately received pressure from his superiors,
and the coverage was discontinued.
But that didn't stop my father.
He said he would continue even on his own,
and that he would definitely write an article on it.
I thought I would be able to help my father, so I did some research.
I only did it because I was so confident in my technological skills.
I managed to hack into Seventh Heaven's system.
That's when I found out how many people had gone there,
and how most of them had disappeared.
I also found out about the existence of something named "Tower".
After gathering all the evidence, my father went off to meet with Nanahara Fumito.
He... thanked me.
And just like that, he was gone forever.
If only I hadn't done such a thing!
Father... my father didn't come back,
and it's all my fault!
I wanted to search for my father,
so I joined this organization.
But I was afraid to find out the truth,
so I couldn't focus on hacking.
What would I do if I found out that my father was dead?
What about your father?
I don't have one.
However, I did have someone who was like a father to me.
He was a kind person.
Why are you so strong?
I'm like your father.
Huh?
I make my own decisions,
and see them through to the very end.
I had to find my resolve,
so I could remain true to myself.
I finally understand...
why I couldn't leave you alone.
We're pretty similar, aren't we?
We're both lonely.
Just as I thought, there's nothing written anywhere
about that incident yesterday at Tsuji Private School.
Geez... damn it!
Mana-san and Saya-san didn't come, did they?
She suffered so many injuries.
Mana-chan's probably taking care of her.
Actually, she really should go to the hospital.
Good morning.
Morning!
Hey, you're lat—
Sorry.
I stayed up late last night.
Tsuki-chan, good morning.
Mana!
Sorry for giving you bad information.
You didn't lie to us on purpose, right?
I would never do such... a thing!
Then it's fine.
As long as you weren't lying, it's okay.
Does it hurt?
No.
Really?
Yeah.
I hope you recover from your injuries soon.
Um, what am I saying?
It seems that I was somewhat mistaken about you.
Why do you sound so arrogant when you're supposed to be apologizing?
Shut up!
Anyway, thank you for protecting Hiiragi!
Wha— are you ignoring me?!
Now, now.
Everyone, I've got something to tell you.
Hacking?
Yes.
Mana-san, are you sure?
I'm sure.
I've realized that I need to stop running away and face my problems,
no matter what the outcome will be.
Hiiragi... I understand.
After that incident at Tsuji Private School, it's very likely that Tower—
or rather, Fumito will make a serious move to crush us.
We should decide whether we need to fortify our defenses first,
or head straight for the enemy headquarters.
I would like everyone to consider these options.
Yes, sir!
It seems that you have a tendency to capture the hearts of those you encounter.
I've done nothing.
"Ask, and it shall be given;
seek, and ye shall find;
knock, and it shall be opened unto you."
Man will find answers on his own.
Saya, have you found your answer?
Hm?
Oh!
Saya, you made this for me?
I only poured what was already made.
Thanks.
Would you like to join me?
I—
Mogari-san made this for me.
Everyone's been grateful to me
because I've been trying so hard.
They said they wanted you to have some as well.
Shouldn't you be sleeping?
When I think I'm about to make a breakthrough, I just can't get to sleep.
Besides, just like how you have your abilities, I have mine.
I see.
W-What's the matter?!
I've found it!
Tower's headquarters!
Tokyo Bay Coastal Breakwater Landfill?
Huh?
She was really amazing.
It didn't matter what security programs they were running—she was shredding them like paper.
Why didn't you wake me up so I could witness the breakthrough?
But there's nothing there.
You can't find it in a residential search,
but you can see it in an aerial view of the area.
What?
There's nothing.
The satellite view had a fake photo embedded in it.
Now let me remove it.
Ah!
Amazing.
You really did a great job.
Saya, we might find Fumito there.
Damn, it's amazing how they were able to hide such a large facility.
We're also amazing since we found it, right?
Sure.
Won't you let me go with you?
No.
They're armed.
This is not your battle.
But Saya, you'll be…
You saw me. Minor injuries are nothing.
Also, you've got more important things to worry about.
You're right. I have to find my father.
We'll do our best to support you.
Are Tsuki-chan and Yanagi-san ready?
We're ready and standing by.
Tell us if something goes wrong.
We'll try to stay put for as long as possible.
If you think you can’t go on, just come back.
Thank you.
Okay. Let’s move.
Where is the target?
It started.
Fuji-kun, please secure our communication line.
Okay.
Tsuki-chan, are you able to infiltrate their communications network?
I've got their wireless communications.
Can you tell how many people there are?
Yes.
Saya, I've got the number of people and their locations.
The higher up you go, the more resistance you'll encounter.
Nanahara Fumito must be on the top floor.
No.
Eh?
Fumito's got something stronger than any human, and it doesn't need wireless communications.
The Old Ones.
What's the path of least resistance?
The basement.
Where is the entrance?
Wait.
Are you Fumito’s proxy?
Saya?
Continue.
Right.
You will not reach Fumito-sama.
You look miserable, Kisaragi Saya.
Don't say... that name.
I've found the route to get to the basement.
Go to the elevator hall all the way back,
and take the right door.
Saya?
Kuto, it is not necessary any more.
Yes, Fumito-sama.
Look, this is what a person who would control the world can do.
What is that sound?
What the hell is going on?
Saya, run straight.
Hurry, Saya.
Saya, next, turn left.
You can go down all the way to the bottom from there.
Saya.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Good evening, Saya.
This is…
what the hell... is this?
Stop.
Stop!
Saya, Saya! What’s wrong?
Saya!
Fumi...
Saya! Saya!
Fuji.
I can’t do anything, the line's dead.
I disabled the wireless communications because
I didn't want anyone to disturb us,
now that we've finally gotten to meet face to face.
I’m sorry.
I'm really happy that you came to see me,
but you shouldn't be causing so much damage.
It's finally working, Kuroto.
I gave her the amount that I was instructed.
Has it just started working after moving around that much?
What's with her?
That cup of coffee...
Why did I have to give her such a thing?
All the kids at your place are nice kids with a strong sense of justice.
They would never agree to drug her, would they?
It doesn't work on humans, only you, Saya.
Are you worried about the members of SIRRUT?
You've become quite friendly with them,
and that helped lure you here.
You even drank the coffee, even though you were so cautious...
and never ate anything offered to you before.
They were quite useful.
Don’t misunderstand.
I did not deceive them, I used them.
At first, SIRRUT was a very small internet group
that wanted more freedom here in Japan, more specifically, in Tokyo.
Well, I could've left them alone,
but you never know how big things will get on the internet.
That's why I offered to become their sponsor and provided funds.
It made things easier since those brats believed any information I leaked.
What's better, you came along,
and they were able to lure you to the mansion.
I didn't think Hiiragi would actually find this place.
Well, I contacted Fumito right away.
Now then, what are you going to do?
Why are you spending so much time and money on one woman like this?
Saya is special.
Using so much of Seventh Heaven's money, and Tower's strength?
Yes.
You said you would dominate the world with your personal connections and power,
along with controlling Tower by killing off both of our families.
Yes, I did say that.
We can expect even more money, power and fame ahead.
I don’t need any of that.
I said I wanted to have the world.
That’s why bigger thinking…
The world is small.
It really is very small. Isn't it, Saya?
This woman is the one?
You've become careless, Fumito.
Disappear here with this monster.
I'll make it look like you were killed by this monster.
Then I'll take everything.
You underestimate me, cousin.
You were always like that.
Always looking down on me,
that gaze enrages me!
Fumito!
I will keep the promise I made to you.
Is this...
Saya’s blood.
Look, he's joined the covenant.
Kuroto, you should now feel the power that you have been longing for.
Saya, the key to controlling the man-eating Old Ones
has been inherited and carried by the head of the Mogari family.
Your blood is the only thing that can sever the ties between humans and the Old Ones.
Curse you, I'll...
Fumito...
Saya, one cannot become human; one must be born human.
You cannot kill humans.
You are not human.
The only thing that can satisfy your hunger is your own kind,
the Old Ones.
Did you know that...
the human population is growing as rapidly as the Old Ones are disappearing?
Soon, there may be no need for the covenant.
Saya, how old are you now?
How many more years,
rather, how many more hundreds of years will you live?
During that time, the Old Ones may become extinct.
How will you survive if that happens?
Your blood.
I tried to use Tower's magic to create the Old Ones from humans,
but so far, I have not succeeded.
They die quickly.
I am doing my best... to gather people and missing persons.
Was it Mana-chan?
I saw the video from Mogari mansion.
Her father was a reporter, wasn't he?
He lived a little bit longer,
but he escaped and died the other day.
You sliced him to death right after you arrived in Tokyo, right, Saya?
What's going on?
You are truly beautiful, Saya.
The winner receives a reward.
This is the strongest power that I could create.
Previously, I could only run, but now look.
The Old Ones.
Those eyes.
They are the same as when I shot you.
They are so beautiful.
I want you, Saya.
Fumito!
Fumito.
Why are you doing this?
Here, Saya.
Fumito...
I told you, it's hard.
I tried it on myself right away.
If I could be the same thing that you are...
I could finally hold you.
I am sorry, Saya.
If I were a human,
your curse... would be broken.
As a winner, you receive a reward.
As a loser, I receive punishment.
You should have avoided me, Saya,
you turned it into a reward now...
I...
I ended up...
alone...
No way.
It's surrounded by police.
The area is off-limits, except to emergency vehicles.
We can’t get in touch with Mogari-san at all.
E-Excuse me, excuse me.
Yes, it is necessary to give young people freedom
in order to nurture them.
If you threaten them with harsh restrictions, only resistance will come out of it.
And it is imperative that adults do not deceive children...
Tsuki-chan, how were classes?
Mm-hm.
I stayed until the end.
Why don’t you join a club?
Clubs are boring.
It’s more fun playing with you guys.
Mana!
Hey!
Once she became the governor,
the internet restrictions were lifted.
The Juvenile Protection Curfew Ordinance was abolished as well.
It's like heaven compared to how it was back then.
Mogari-san... has disappeared, hasn’t he?
Sysnet was taken over by other companies,
and all of Seventh Heaven's executives have been replaced.
Nanahara Fumito has completely disappeared;
even the info about him on the internet is gone.
I am sorry for bringing up such a depressing topic.
Well, it has been almost a year and a half since that day.
But...
But?
That is Matsuo-kun’s fault.
No, it isn't!
You are not sweet!
Yes, I am!
They're fighting again...
You are not sweet at all!
Aren't they supposed to be getting married next month?
What do you mean?
Because you're clueless about stuff like this.
They haven't changed, Matsu-san and Yanagi-san.
What?
Hey there, don’t fight.
Well, of course you're the sweet one.
What? What are you talking about, don't say such nonsense!
Who's the sweet one...?
What?
But I believe I will see her again.