Kyoto
Touzan
Yajima Residence
Due to the storm wind blast from the slopes of Mount Mimuro,
maple leaves are falling.
Make the Tatsuta River look very beautiful.
The same favorite card with Master huh?
This is all thanks to you, Ooka Momiji.
I will thank you after the filming.
Is not this too soon? It's coming?
You apparently!
What's this? Ti-Not possible!
Now spring has arrived and the flowers begin to bloom.
At the moment it is non-negotiable.
Wow, his caruta card was thrown so far?
Ah, no need to bother.
Eh? Yes.
Forgive me.
Sweetness!
Hey, daddy, do not be noisy!
Beautiful sister!
He's like an idol!
Kimono is also suitable!
By the way why are we here and watching the karuta match?
Mikiko already told you, right?
... to wait in the locker room until consultation time arrives...
... but the uncle is captivated by these beautiful girls, and just goes to the studio.
Mikiko, who is she?
Did not I already introduce it to you?
The opponent of the beautiful cute player, the girl with the glasses!
He is the chairman of the Kaihou Academy Karuta Club, which I am a member of!
Members... Kazuha, can you play karuta?
Iyalah, did you just know?
You went to the bathroom for a long time, Heiji?
Sorry, sorry!
The entrance to the studio is closed, so I'm not sure what it can open.
Excuse me.
We're in the middle of filming, so can you calm down?
Good!
For your precious sake,
Even though my life is full of spirit itself...
I do not care.
Cool!
Hey, Kudo...
... did the uncle forget that he came to Osaka for consultation?
Well, do not be so to him.
He took the kids with him because they kept nagging...
... want to go see Osaka, while Professor Agasa is busy.
By the way what happened to that rich girl?
Oh, Sonoko.
He was lying in bed with a fever.
I'm still surprised. Kazuha, why did you join Club Karuta?
I'm still joining the Aikido Club really.
Club Karuta was almost disbanded for not having enough members, so I signed up.
Sometimes I also accompany Mikiko to practice, I'm at a club like a member of a zombie.
Member of zombies? Funny thing!
Fun, it looks like the two of you are having fun...
... it feels like being in a cafe alone.
Forgive us!
Detective Conan Movie: Love Letter Red
I am a high school detective, Kudo Shinichi!
As I go to the playground with my childhood friend, Mouri Ran...
... I see people dressed in black, doing a suspicious transaction.
Being too focused on seeing their transactions...
... I did not realize there was another member who beat me from behind.
I was forced to take strange medicine by them...
... and when I wake up...
... my body is getting smaller!
If they know Kudo Shinichi is still alive...
... they will look for me and harm the people around me.
At the suggestion of Professor Agasa, I hid my identity. When Ran asks my name...
... spontaneous I answer Edogawa Conan!
To dig deeper information about them, I live with Ran whose father is a private detective.
This is Hattori Heiji.
Detective SMA from the west.
With the great deduction capabilities passed on from the father, the Osaka Police Department Leader...
... he has solved countless difficult cases.
He is one of the few people who know my true identity.
Toyama Kazuha.
Hattori's childhood classmate and childhood friend.
He is always restless with words spoken by Hattori.
And finally that is still shrouded in mystery, the Queen of the future.
Who is she really?
Even though my body is smaller, my intelligence remains the same.
A famous detective.
Truth there is only one!
Nichiuri TV
Well. We can finally visit the TV studio, but instead were told to wait in the locker room ?!
I want to watch their shoot!
Not possible. They scolded Uncle Kogoro as well.
World Karuta Satsuki-Kai
Tuan Mouri Kogoro
Sorry. It's because I was talking too loud.
Ah, I know!
Let's go to the souvenir shop when the others are back?
Heh ?!
The right one ?!
Yes. If you want to be nice until the shooting is over, okay?
Of course!
Hooray!
Let's go shopping together!
Oh, yeah... Conan went where?
Ah, Conan...
... he is watching my father to replace me.
Hey, boy!
Did not I already tell you to wait in the locker room?
But Kak Ran asks me to keep an eye on my uncle during filming.
God.
Please step aside!
Please give way! Karuta wants to pass!
Gosh! Karuta Satsuki-Kai!
Wow! Is that not too much for a caruta?
What are you saying, Kazuha?
It is a legendary karuta that is only used in the final round of national tournaments organized by Satsuki-Kai!
Ah, is not your dream to play using it, Mikiko?
It's not me!
No one in Satsuki-Kai's 20-year history is not captivated by the card.
Aah... I really want to touch that legendary caruta during the final.
Hey, hey, why are those cards used only when the final?
Since it is often used in fierce matches, so it has gone through a lot of damage.
That's why, in addition to the final, the cards remain in the box...
... and also often exhibited in the museum.
But is not that much keeper still excessive?
Not really!
After last year's Satsuki Cup, there was an unbelievable furor over the loss of his karuta.
Although it can eventually be found quickly, but...
... I heard that Yajima, the defending champion, convinced President Achiwa to tighten his guard.
So yes.
But who are they?
This uncle is stupid or what ?!
These are the people who will consult you!
Oh, really?
That is the uncle we know and we love.
The person in this photo is President Achiwa Kensuke.
He is a great man who founded Achiwa Real Estate.
Also known as the Naniwa Real Estate King.
Why would such a person want to play karuta?
I think it's just his hobby.
But I heard he is also great.
But here it is written that Pak Achiwa wants to be a reader, not a player.
Oh! Who is this beautiful woman?
His wife Mr. Achiwa, Mrs. Satsuki.
Oh! So he's married.
Satsuki-Kai was founded by Mrs. Satsuki, former Queen, and Mr. Achiwa took over and became president.
Queen = Female Karuta Champion
Is there anything else...
Ah! Is not this interesting?
Here it is written that Pak Achiwa believes in superstition...
... and always wash his car the day before his wife will play an important game.
He says if a clean car is his secret to success and win!
And I have to talk to this superstitious couple?
No. Mrs. Satsuki has died of a serious illness 3 years ago.
So only Pak Achiwa will be consulting today.
Be-I see.
Emm, who is the burly person who is always beside Mr. Achiwa in all these photos ?.
Ah, he's a former secretary of Pak Achiwa, his name is Kaieda Togo.
He is the cunning guy who is responsible for the illegal business of Achiwa Real Estate.
He resigned from his position as secretary, and is where he is now...
Wait for Hattori! Stop spreading such unfounded accusations!
There is no illegal business from President Satsuki-Kai!
That's right, Heiji!
Well, yeah. It's just a hoax, hoax.
Welcome the President!
President Achiwa!
I have to welcome him.
Mr. President! Thank you for coming today.
Well, it's great to be here.
Thank you.
If I'm not mistaken today there is a demonstration of a Yajima match against Momiji, right?
Then there's the consultation.
Right! And after that we will show special coverage about Karuta Satsuki-Kai which was recorded last week with the help of Yajima.
So the whole country can see the attraction of this caruta!
Oh, so Karuta Satsuki-Kai has been prepared huh?
All right, I'm counting on you.
Good!
What an impressive man.
Well, that's the King of Real Estate Naniwa.
Excuse me! Can you call Master Yajima?
We will start soon, but...
... we can not reach him.
That's weird...
... he says he'll be here an hour before the filming starts.
Yajima's arrogant man comes too late ?!
Ask Sekine to come here too, just in case.
So we can ask him to replace if something goes wrong.
But that's just a maple leaf, helpless to fly away.
Ti-Not possible.
We have a little time before filming starts.
Right!
Hey, Heiji. We have to buy okonomiyaki.
Heh? Before buying okonomiyaki, there is one place we should go first!
Well, but after that okonomiyaki...
Sorry! Are you okay?
You're the carunt player that was ?!
Fate.
Finally I can meet you.
Eh ?!
My husband's candidate!
Candidate ?!
Husband ?!
Eh ?!
I have no plans after filming, so...
... will you talk to me while you have tea?
Wow... this big sister's chest too!
H-Hey what do you mean ?!
Miss Momiji!
Sorry, but can you come back to the room now!
Ah, why in a fun time like this.
Looks like Mr. Yajima is late, you know?
Yajima?
Well, when he himself planned this event...
... is that what keeps him busy?
Then see you again, Heiji!
Well, see you soon!
Who is that woman ?!
That's the pretty sister who was!
He is very beautiful!
The man called her Miss Momiji.
I told you I do not know who he is!
But he knows your name is Heiji!
Kak Ran.
I will not be angry, let's confess!
We wait for them outside !?
You're already angry!
Instead of seeing them quarrel.
I'm not angry!
Come on, come on!
He's too familiar to someone you do not know!
Why is he so angry?
I-That... maybe I used to meet him somewhere.
Look at my eyes when talking...
... you know him, right ?!
I told you so, I do not know!
Anyway, how could I ever forget such a beautiful woman!
As beautiful as that...?
Iyalah, and here there are people who are unforgettable in a completely different way.
Huh ?!
What do you mean ?!
Hey, hey. Kak Heiji, you really do not know him?
Ooka Momiji?
Satsuki Cup Winner High school level twice in a row.
Class two in Kyoto Senshin High is a strong candidate for the next Queen.
Ooka Momiji?
Queen's Candidate?
Osaka Prefectural Police Station
So that's the only threat?
Yes. Just inscribed "Nichiuri TV will explode".
Then what about this caruta image?
It is attached in the letter.
We still do not know what it means.
So, what does Nichiuri TV know about this?
We already warned them.
How did you respond, Heizo?
This is just a prankster or a real bomb threat?
It is very difficult to specify only by e-mail.
If not a prankster, this is not a matter of carelessness.
We have just received an order from the Osaka Police For an emergency evacuation.
Stop all your work and filming process, then exit through the nearest emergency door.
What announcement is this?
Hm? Are they in an evacuation drill?
I repeat: We just received an order from the Osaka Police For an emergency evacuation.
What happened something?
He said from the police.
Maybe this is part of filming ?!
Stop all your work and filming process...
Hey, quickly find out!
... then exit through the nearest emergency door.
Good!
What's happening?
Kazuha, you just come out through the emergency exit! Understand?!
Eh? What about you, Heiji?
I'll find out what's really going on.
You hurry out!
Wait... Heiji!
Be careful!
Hey, boy!
You think you want to go where?
Something's missing in the studio.
Bego!
Did not you hear the announcement ?!
Forgive me. I have no experience in anything like this.
This is my first time doing an evacuation with a kimono.
This is bad! We must evacuate as soon as possible!
Be calm, what's going on?
We... received a bomb threat!
What ?!
President of Achiwa, this may be a false threat...
... but please do evacuation until we are sure it is completely safe.
All right!
Everything! Follow my instructions and get out!
Come on! Hurry up!
Good!
What are you doing, Mikiko?
Harmful if it's still here!
Hurry away!
Mr. Achiwa, you too.
What are you doing ?! Let's go!
Everything! Please keep calm!
Not to worry. Everything is safe.
You guys wait here and do not go anywhere, understand?
What... waiting again?
Can not connect...
... I hope father and the others are fine.
Ran!
Dad! Conan!
Woi, what really happened ?!
Could this be an evacuation drill without prior warning?
No, I asked his TV employee, and he said...
... this building got a bomb threat!
Really ?!
Eh, then Kazuha and Hattori are there ?!
What?
Are not they with you guys?
No... I'm so worried, let me look for a while.
Do not! I'm the one looking.
You stay here!
You guys too!
God.
Emergency during peak hours like this.
Heiji!
Mikiko!
I told you to go out first!
Yeah, but I'm worried about you.
Sorry ya Kazuha. I can not leave that caruta here.
I will track the GPS signal from the phone.
What? Hattori is still inside ?!
You're there...
... what are you doing ?!
Leave it here and hurry out!
God.
Mikiko!
Kazuha! Hattori!
Do you know we are in danger ?!
I'm sorry!
Geez.
Permission to report, there are still three people in Studio 3.
Mikiko!
You are so clumsy.
I'm sorry.
I'm worried about this when I imagine if the bomb threat is really going to happen.
We can not confirm when the bomb will explode.
We will wait for the next command.
I'm counting on you.
We've evacuated three people still in the studio.
Make sure everything is safe!
Good.
Great. Now it's time we look for something that looks suspicious.
All troops, start combing all the inside of the building!
Ready to execute!
They entered.
Is there really a bomb?
I'm sure this is a prankster.
Quickly! Through this way!
What ?!
Everything is moving!
Tell everyone to back off!
Get away from the building!
Mr. President, please be faster.
Beware!
Kazuha!
Cool!
Do not come near! Too dangerous!
Shit! Where the hell are they both ?!
You're not stuck in there right, Hattori ?!
Kazuha!
We do not keep quiet. It's dangerous here. Let's go!
Are you okay? Can you still walk?
M-Still.
Good, let's get out of here!
With this kind of situation it's too hard to get inside.
Yes.
Everything away from the building!
Someone just came out of there ?!
Is there anything else?
There are still two more people inside!
What ?!
Kazuha, over here!
Shit!
Heiji!
Nearly.
Quick, fast! Get away from here!
We can not go down ya ?!
Kazuha, here!
We go up to the roof!
What?
Is not we supposed to get out?
If we can not get out, at least we should find a place to be able to breathe.
Could it be, Hattori?
He's up ?!
Shit! Can not be connected.
Come on, Kazuha!
Kazuha!
Be careful!
Is not this roof made of concrete ?!
Closer! We need to get closer!
Impossible! Dangerous if too close!
Excuse me! Please give way!
Shit!
I can not see anything because of this smoke.
I can not do it myself... can not if it's on my own.
Kudo!
Sink or swim?
I'll try!
Ayoo !!
What's that...?
Finally he comes!
Hattori.
Hey, Heiji, where are we going?
Come on! There is only one path down.
Go down ?! What do you mean?
Stay here Kazuha! Understand?
Heiji ?!
Get off from here?
Are you kidding right ?!
Hey! We're ready!
Me too.
There is no time, I will drop you both at once.
All right!
Kazuha!
Do we really want to get off the top of the...
Wait! At this point I can not see!
Not possible. You're not serious right, Heiji ?!
Close your eyes and tight grip!
Eh ?! T-Tu-Wait!
Wait a minute!
Thanks! I wait for you downstairs!
Well.
Kudo!
Shit!
Not possible. Somebody's over there, let's get over there quick!
Let me get there!
There really are people! Stretcher! Bring a stretcher!
Kazuha!
He-Heiji!
Shit!
Only from this place can I go down.
Thinking... there must be another way out!
Rescue helicopter?
No, impossible.
With fire and smoke this thick as helicopters can not get close.
Wait!
Is not there a river next to the TV studio ?!
If I jump over there.
All right!
Ah no!
There is not enough ground to accelerate my skateboard rate.
Emergency!
I just took a short breath but my lungs burned.
I have to... do... something.
Ran!
I can not... give up.
There must be something to use for a skateboarding... somewhere.
There!
What are you doing, Kudo? Hurry up!
That's right ?!
No doubt, it's Kudo. But what is he...
So yes!
So that's it!
More...
... even faster!
I can not breathe.
A little more, just a little more!
It will fall!
This is it!
Shit!
Is it still not fast enough ?!
Emergency! Will not be up!
You made me wait!
I caught you!
You're okay, Kudo?
Well...
... I guess so.
You dropped this.
Thank you.
Anyway, you bring that thing huh?
Did you know that Nichiuri TV will explode?
Stupid.
Of course not!
I'm just in case something happens.
Something like this huh?
Hmm. That's it.
Kazuha!
Ran!
Are you okay?
Yeah, but I can not remember how to survive...
... because it is so hard to breathe, too much smoke.
It's okay, it's important you survived.
Thank goodness! I'm glad you survived.
Ran.
It looks like my car keys are missing, I'm going to go find it.
Okay.
Oh yes, where is Conan?
I think he went to the point of gathering as well.
Ah, Conan!
That's right Conan!
Conan! Where have you been?
We are very worried.
K-Kazuha!
Wait, Heiji!
Where have you been?
E-Eh... anu.
You are also Conan!
I'm very very worried about you.
I'm sorry.
What about Mikiko?
It looks like his hand was injured, so he was immediately rushed to the hospital.
His hand?
I hope it is not bad.
I know the address of the hospital, what if we go together?
Yes! Let's go!
Heiji!
Uncle Otaki!
Thank goodness you survived.
Kazuha, do you seem to go first?
Eeh ?!
Later I'll catch up soon.
Aduuh. Let's go, Ran!
Y-Well. Ah yes, Conan come on!
Y-Well.
You can not go anywhere without me!
Good.
See you later, Conan.
Is it true that the Police Department received a bomb threat?
This is the letter that the police received.
Ah! There's a karuta card too?
Maybe this is related to the filming of their caruta program.
But with Nichiuri TV conditions like this.
It will take a lot of time to do the crime scene.
Right.
In the corners of the mountains, stepping on the red leaves, came the sound of the stag dance that ran. When I heard the cry of loneliness, sad, how sad this autumn.
What do the perpetrators want?
Naniwa Police Hospital
Thanks for the help.
Equally. Get well soon!
Mr. President, how are you doing?
Ah, not too bad. Just scratch a little.
Thank goodness.
With this incident the competition will...
Well... this is very unexpected.
Looks like I have to stop the Satsuki Cup that has been going on for years.
Do not stop!
I think now is the right time to show how exciting Satsuki-Kai is!
But Satsuki-Kai's karuta to be used for the final is on fire.
If that's you do not have to worry.
His caruta survived.
A-What ?!
A-What...
... m-you mean?
Miss Hiramoto stuck it out during the evacuation process.
Mi-Mikiko ?!
If his karuta is burned I can understand, but his karuta is safe, so...
Really ?!
Is it true that Satsuki-Kai karuta was saved ?!
Pe-The museum officer who took it and is being examined.
Mr. President.
The caruta is fine.
So you do not have to worry.
Well.
I think it will burn, thank goodness if survived.
Then, how is the circumstance of Mikiko who has saved Satsuki-Kai karuta?
It looks like the injury was not so bad, but...
He's still under investigation.
So yes.
Mikiko long time huh?
Doctors say Mikiko just need first aid...
Thank you very much.
Mikiko, your hand why? Is it possible...?
Yes. My hand is broken.
This may be my law...
Not possible.
... for putting Kazuha and Hattori in danger to take back his cards.
What are you saying?
I am indebted to you, Mikiko!
You saved the karuta that has become a symbol of Satsuki-Kai.
Representing the association, I thank you very much for what you have done.
But Mr. President...
... I can not participate in Satsuki Cup with conditions like this.
Well. This is a big loss for Satsuki-Kai because talented players like you can not participate.
But for now you better focus on your healing.
Right.
There is still competition again next year.
Still this is not a good thing!
If we can not get a good result in this year's Satsuki Cup...
... our club will be dissolved.
I do not want his club to break up because I'm injured.
Mr. President.
The police are waiting for you.
We have to go.
Well.
Do not be sad Mikiko.
But.
Well. Only the two of us here are members of our club.
There it is, Kazuha!
Please participate.
To represent the Kaihou Academy, play in my place!
You suddenly said that to me.
Kazuha, did you ever participate in the tournament?
No, no.
But you often help me practice, right?
Well.
Kazuha, you have great strength, quick reflexes and competing spirit.
You're also never afraid to compete.
Your courage is amazing!
This seems too much.
When will the tournament begin?
Will start day after tomorrow.
Not to worry.
If we start training now...
... you can do it, I'm sure of it!
A beginner wants to participate in the tournament and hopes to win?
Are you sure you will replace Hyakunin Isshu with Iroha-garuta?
Hyakunin Isshu is an anthology of classical Japanese poetry, used in Uta-garuta. Iroha-garuta is a variation of Uta-garuta that is more easily understood.
Do not taunt him!
I know his talent is more than anyone because I'm the one who's been practicing with him.
He may not have experience in the tournament...
... but its ability is equivalent to player class A.
Heh?
This girl?
Are not you the one with Heiji?
I wonder what relationship you two have?
We've always been together since childhood! Heiji is...
Is...
Your beloved right ?!
No need to cover up!
That's clear!
Silence you guys!
"Shinoburedo" huh?
The first line in Hyakunin Isshu's fortieth poem, "Though I hid it."
Playing a role as a childhood lover.
Adorable once.
How about this ?!
Who can win the tournament tomorrow will be his future wife Heiji...
... and express love to him!
What do you think?
Wait, what do you mean ?!
If you're serious with Heiji, at least you have the courage to do it, right?
Kazuha, do not be hooked by him!
But as long as you know ya...
... I am very serious.
Wait a minute!
I will accept...
... your challenge!
Ka-Kazuha!
Really!
Your spirit is...
... save it for the game later.
Yes, you too. Do not lose before meeting me!
Then, let's get here.
I will go to the nail salon in preparation to proclaim my love for Heiji.
The sister looks horrible.
There must be something.
You're so cool...
... can say that to Momiji!
What have I done?
Eh ?!
I've promised something bad.
I'm sorry.
No, it's my fault.
Dad! What's the key?
Well, how about it?
The key is not met...
... when I've been looking for it everywhere.
Maybe I should take the spare key.
What is it, Conan?
Looks like the sister had dropped it.
Eh? Try to show me ?!
Right, this is Momiji's.
Dad, I'll give it back for a bit.
Hey, do you know him?
I'm so confused.
What should I do ?!
How is it?
Even though she looks horrible...
But she is beautiful!
If such beautiful woman declares her love for Kak Heiji, she surely will not refuse...
... ta-but of course Kak Kazuha that he will choose.
Really ?!
Right, right!
No time to think about it.
Starting tonight I will practice all night!
This is my first time to the hospital.
This place is huge... I can get lost here.
Kak Ran, he's there!
That.
Momiji!
Wait a minute!
Momiji! Wait!
He's gone.
How should this be?
We already know the full name and the school...
... but is not it easier if we find the address there?
You're right.
Kak Ran, I also want to see.
Oh, okay.
Emm... this...
... a photo.
Who is this guy ?!
Oh, there are others.
Looks like this is a childhood picture.
This is Momiji and...
... Hattori, right ?!
They make the promise of the little finger.
I'm curious about what promises.
Maybe their promise will be married?
They are still kids ?!
That's not possible.
No. This situation is very Heiji.
That's very possible.
Ah! That's Kak Heiji's bike!
Keep it a secret, okay?
Especially from Kazuha.
You two are waiting for me huh?
No, no.
What's up with him?
Ran! What have you returned?
I-yes.
You're so old?
So what information you got?
Nothing. Osaka prefectural police also still experience chaos.
Uncle Otaki will call me if there is more information.
Mr. President.
Sorry to bother you...
... can you answer the phone?
Yes, no problem.
God.
... what's wrong with Ran?
From the Kyoto Prefectural Police ?!
Yes.
So what happened to Yajima?
What ?!
Killed ?!
Hattori!
Yes.
Woi! You two, wait!
Thanks for the help.
Wait, you two!
This is a restricted area!
We came with Mr. Mouri Kogoro.
What are you talking about...
You can let them in.
Long time no see ya, you two ?!
Inspector Ayanokoji!
The victim is Yajima Toshiya.
He is the son of a highly respected sake businessman family, he lives alone in this house.
The time of his death is estimated at 06:00. The body of the victim was found at 14:00.
Ah, watch your step.
This place is very messy.
B-Okay.
Robbery ?!
Viewed from the scene at the scene is very clear this is a robbery case.
Right, we also assume that way.
Somebody broke into this house, looking for money and other valuable objects...
... but Yajima caught him.
When the perpetrator immediately killed him with a Japanese sword that he tried to steal.
Next the perpetrator takes the money and runs off.
But why? Why?
It seems that the victim was playing karuta.
It looks so.
What are you two doing here ?!
Mr. Inspector...
... do you allow us both to do crime scene for a while?
The forensics team has done its job, so go ahead.
Really gapapa ?!
But...
... we will seize this katana as evidence of murder.
Ah, that's okay.
Let these people do the crime scene as they see fit.
Good.
Then I will wait outside.
Tell us if you find anything.
Well.
What do you think?
I'm not so sure...
but look at his right hand.
Well.
You're aware of it too, Kudo ?!
Well, it looks like he was holding something with his blood.
By the way something is blood, in this room...
... only caruta cards.
The perpetrator must be aware of the death message of the victim...
... then mix it with another blood card of the other caruta.
Finding scattered cards is like looking for a needle in a haystack.
Just leave it to me.
I know someone who is great at analyzing things like this.
What?
Viewed from the former blood stain, this remot was located near the side of the victim's body.
Excuse me.
Can I turn on the TV?
Yes, okay.
Thank you.
If he uses the remot just before being killed, there must be something here.
Ooka Momiji.
So before being killed...
... Yajima watching this?
What's up?
Looks like this is a competition the previous year.
Well.
Satsuki Cup tournament between 15th to 20th SMA.
Why is Yajima watching this?
The final capability level is likely to be very high.
So all kinds of tactics and strategy of arranging the cards there...
... can be used as a reference.
I doubt it has anything to do with this murder case.
T-But.
No buts!
Let's go! You too!
Play the detectives until here.
Sorry to have made a scene.
I-yes.
Let go of me!
Latest news.
The explosion occurred at Nichiuri TV.
The news again?
Today around 1 pm...
I'm so worried.
Ai, why did you turn off the TV?
If you feel worried every time you see the news...
... your health will be disturbed.
But.
You contacted the children right?
But Shinichi has not called back.
This...
Edogawa Conan
... long life apparently.
Oh! Let me talk to him after you're done.
Okay.
You are...
... what do you think by not contacting us?
Professor is very worried about you.
My fault, my fault.
A lot happens.
Then why are you calling?
I just sent a photo to your laptop.
I want you to check the karuta that is in the photo.
I thought you were involved in a bombing case, but you sent me a photo of bloody carcass cards ?!
I want you to find a card that was held by the victim.
You're very reliable in this sort of thing right?
This kind of huh?
Ah! There's a picture of someone also here.
Ah, can you also find information about the man in the photo?
This man also has something to do with karuta?
Yeah, I'm suspicious of that.
I will try, but it will take a while.
Thanks! I'm counting on you!
See you later!
W-Wait! Professor wants...
Evil.
If this is the case, the likelihood of the target is the members of Satsuki-Kai.
Well.
We'd better pay more attention to those two guys.
I will keep an eye on Mr. Achiwa.
If she's not mistaken she's staying at the same hotel as us.
Then I will handle Ooka Momiji.
Wait, wait! Who are you?!
I'm from Satsuki-Kai, let me by!
Wait a minute, I'll ask for confirmation.
Sekine!
Where have you been ?!
We called you many times, you know ?!
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
I drank too much last night.
To the point of falling asleep and not realizing that my phone runs out of battery.
Geez.
When I woke up I was told that there was an explosion in the TV studio.
Then I called the association and they told me that Mr. President was in Yajima place and was looking for me...
... so I hurried here. But it looks like there's been a mess here.
A lot of cops here, what happened to Yajima?
Yajima has...
... killed.
Eh ?!
Looks like the robber who has killed him...
... with the katana in the corridor.
With katana?
Not possible.
Pak Achiwa, who is this man?
Ah, I'm sorry. I am a cameraman and also a member of Satsuki-Kai.
My name is Sekine Koji.
Sekine is his rival Yajima.
The Satsuki Cup final of the last two years is theirs.
Well, but both I lost.
I think that this year I... will win.
But now I can not compete against it anymore.
Are you going to keep performing the tournament as planned?
Ah, about that...
... I just thought about it.
You have to do it, President!
If the Satsuki Cup that has become this tradition fails only because of the death of Yajima...
... maybe his soul will not even calm down.
It is hopeless he was beaten to death.
Sekine! Be careful when talking!
Well.
Forgive me.
I'm from Kyoto Prefectural Police.
There is something I want to ask you, can you ask for a moment?
Ah, of course. Please ask any questions.
Please follow me.
Good, good.
Mr. Mouri, we should both go back to Osaka.
Hey, Kudo...
... I seem to know who did it.
Yes, no problem.
Me too.
Please yes!
It seems that the one who killed Yajima is that person.
But it's too soon to accuse him of being a TV studio bomber targeting Satsuki-Kai members.
Right.
I think keeping an eye on Mr. Achiwa and Momiji is the right move right now, as we have set out.
Yes.
Hotel New Otani
Pertamax.
Bothx.
That's not fair! Wait!
Wow, the room is very spacious!
Sonoko who hired him for us.
He really hopes to come here you know.
That's why he rented a hotel close to Nichiuri TV.
As expected from the owner of Suzuki Group.
Well, right.
They will practice all night, so please provide evening snacks as well for them.
Well, thanks.
Geez, why am I doing this?
When I see you, support your friend with passion...
All right!
Okay! Time to practice!
We will help.
If there is anything we can do please just say it!
We will support you!
You guys.
Really ?! Thanks.
There is a phone.
Who is it?
Professor!
Ayumi also wants to talk!
Let's all talk to the professor!
Yes, let's do it.
We ask to practice earnestly.
We will call over there, so it will not interfere.
"Will the spirit support" he said.
That's it.
Well, I can see you guys!
No more events after that right?
Yes!
We're fine!
We are at the hotel now!
So yes, the time is right!
Eh ?! Is it possible?!
Ta-daa! The long-awaited...
... Professor Quiz Corner!
So that's why Professor called us...?
Let's get started!
They say that the unique style of competitive karuta game has similarities to the ancient Japanese tradition...
... which is it?
Number one: Picking tea.
Number two: Fly a kite.
Number three: Mashing the mochi.
Number four: Harvest rice.
The verb "taking cards" is "tsumu".
"Picking tea" is "chatsumi".
When playing karuta you take the card right? Maybe the answer is picking tea?
Maybe fly a kite? I want to eat takoyaki.
"Fly a kite" in Japanese "Takoage".
There is a phrase when you touch the wrong card right, maybe the answer is pounding mochi.
"Touching the wrong card" is "otetsuki".
"Mashing mochi" is "mochitsuki".
That's your final answer?
The answer is number four, harvesting rice.
Ai!
"Ine" means "Rice".
Rice can become rice field...
"Tanbo" means "Rice Field".
... so it means you are harvesting rice in the fields.
"Harvesting" means "Karu".
That's "karuta"!
How can you live without such mercy?
All of you are...
... do not stay up late, despite being on vacation!
Okee!
Yes, the phone is closed.
Good!
Is not it late?
Many things happen today.
Dad and the others have not come home yet.
Ah, Heiji too. Are they still together?
If you're worried about why you did not call him?
B-Right.
What's wrong Kazuha?
Do not ask what's wrong! What are you doing this late ?!
Eh ?! Kyoto?
What's happening?
Sorry, I have a little business here. Maybe it'll be till night, you do not have to wait for me.
What ?! I thought you would help me practice karuta for the tournament.
Exercise?
I'm participating in a karuta tournament instead of Mikiko.
You've never had experience in tournaments?
That's why I practice!
You're a kid when you play karuta and you're so great Heiji!
Ah, right.
When I was in elementary school I joined in the tournament.
I'm very surprised how can you win Heiji ?!
It's been a long time ago, I do not really remember.
I still remember it clearly.
When Mikiko asked me to join the club...
... the memory suddenly flashed through my mind.
So we're just going to talk about the memories of the past?
I shut down the phone?
How much do you say that to me?
You want to end our conversation while I'm on story?
I did not mean that.
Yes, yes. Whatever you say, Heiji!
Huh? What is my fault?
Enough! Heiji, you stupid!
God, what's up with Heiji ?!
God, what's up with him.
Well... whatever.
Ah, it's me. I want you to do something for me.
Ooka
Yes, fine. thanks.
Oh, I'm tired.
Welcome Uncle.
Well. Who would have thought I was all the way to Osaka instead involved an incident.
Eh? Dad, Conan where?
We gave him a ride because he wants to come back with us.
But when he got to the hotel he said he wanted to talk to Mr. Achiwa.
Eh ?!
Gosh, basic Conan.
If that person is the true culprit...
... it looks like he did not make Mr. Achiwa his target tonight.
What is Kak Ran?
Are you done with your business?
I-yes.
Then hurry back to the room!
After the incident I became easily worried.
All right. I will be right back.
Good...
... I can track her where she goes whenever she goes.
Oh! Is not he...
What is he doing here?
Gosh! Brother is so cool!
Looks like I'm not the right person to train a match with you.
Hey! Is not this excessive ?! I almost...
I'm back.
Ah, Conan!
I am with someone who can help your practice.
Eh ?!
Who is he?
Eh ?! His mother Heiji!
I've heard everything from Heiji.
So I hurried here.
Eh? Why?
Of course to help you Kazuha.
Are not we going to practice karuta?
Yeah, but.
Let me be your opponent.
Maybe as a former Queen my ability is not so great.
Former Queen ?!
I'm here because Heiji is asking me.
I will teach you everything I know.
But we do not have enough time...
... so the exercise will be a little difficult.
Are you ready?
Good.
Please help.
I did not think you would come here...
... Inspector Ayanokoji.
It seems we are thinking the same thing?
Well.
Are the detective boys not here?
He is watching Mr. Achiwa.
So yes.
Good cooperation.
But I kind of regret choosing here.
I did not think he lived in a house of this size.
Thank you for your hard work.
Well.
I'm the maid of Miss Young Momiji.
My name is Iori.
Do you guys want to rest for a while over tea?
He's worried about me.
My potential husband.
Although continuously exposed to water, the color will not fade.
Emergency!
Looks like he has not left the hotel yet.
Waves collected on the beach at Sumi Bay. And in the night collected...
You've tried very hard.
I honestly did not think you could get this far.
Let's take a break?
No! I can still continue.
Rest is also part of the exercise.
I will buy porridge for us.
Ah, Kazuha!
Are you okay ?!
Let him sleep.
He has fought hard without sleeping at all.
How is Kazuha doing?
He is more than I think.
But to get to the last four round it will be difficult.
To be honest all the games will be hard for him.
But.
I have not finished up there yet.
I'm saying it's hard...
... not impossible.
In karuta tournaments, mental steadiness and the ability to maintain focus are the key.
This girl has both.
If he can stay calm and not let his feelings mislead him...
... he has hope of winning.
If I show this to him...
... Kazuha must have lost his concentration.
It will not be long.
Sit quietly.
God, I have to hurry away, you know ?!
So what do you want?
This is about the Yajima murder case.
Is not the robber doing it?
Really?
But I can conclude that this is a premeditated murder by a cold-blooded killer.
Are you kidding right? Well, Yajima is not my best friend...
... but I doubt there are people who really hate him and bear to kill his life.
What about you?
Nonsense!
Why me ?!
Sekine!
You lost the Satsuki Cup final two years in a row right?
And all that defeat you got from Yajima.
If only Yajima does not exist... you must be...
What's all this about!
Of course I want to win the tournament.
But not by killing my rival anyway!
Is not the police have made sure that the perpetrators are robbers? Why do not you?
The reason is a lot.
First, the place was like a deliberately made messed-up so it looks like there has been a robbery.
You know? The culprit did not touch anything related to karuta.
Yes, the culprit has just killed a man, so he must just run away right ?!
So yes.
But I feel if the culprit has a strong emotional bond with the carp...
... therefore he can not treat karuta harshly.
Detectives always make a strange conclusion.
Well, it's all up to your deduction.
Just so you know...
... it has nothing to do with me.
Oh-Oh yeah!
What's up ?!
The pavilion floor creaks...
... when something is running. You remember?
What's up with that?
The voice of the cries can tell someone in the room if anyone wants to enter.
The body of the victim does not show any traces of fights...
So yes.
What you want to say is Yajima must know the culprit?
But that's not true!
Even when practicing alone, karuta requires a high level of concentration...
... once you focus on playing, you will not realize the trivial thing like the sounds around you.
So Yajima can get killed because he is not aware of anyone entering.
That's not possible.
The severe injury Yajima received was on his forehead.
Even though he does not realize there are people who enter because of the focus of playing karuta...
... the injury should be on the back or side of his head.
In other words, the only reason he can get such injuries is because Yajima and the culprit know each other.
The culprit loves karuta, knowing Yajima...
... and did not have an alibi when the incident occurred.
The culprit will also benefit from his death.
This is very strange.
Everything you say shows me that it is me. Just so you know...
... your babbling so far is only conjecture.
If you want to accuse me as the culprit, you must have strong evidence.
Mr. Sekine, it's time.
Come with me.
Well, it's time! Too bad, but I have to go now.
See you again.
Before you leave, I want to ask you one more thing.
You're stubborn. What else?
Something you said earlier drew my attention.
I'm not sure if you remember it.
If the Satsuki Cup that has become this tradition fails only because of the death of Yajima, maybe his soul will not even calm down.
It is hopeless he was beaten to death.
That's what you said.
After hearing that the cause of his death is katana, you should assume that it must be to stab or to slashing.
But you explicitly say "hit".
Only the perpetrator will know that his katana forgot not to be removed from its scabbard.
How can you say "beaten" to death?
I-That's because I saw his corpse at the scene.
Enough!
His body was put in the body bag when you got there.
So you will not have a chance to see it.
Be-I see... I'm just nonsense.
I think if you die beaten after seeing the splash of blood!
However I have nothing to do with this murder!
It's very disrespectful.
I wonder if he will be shocked and affect his behavior?
Now all we have to do is...
Check out the venue.
Well. I've actually been looking for information, it seems to be a bit difficult.
Really! This place is huge!
What building is on the cliff?
Hall of Satsuki.
Satsuki? Is not that...
Right. The place was built in honor of his wife Pak Achiwa, Mrs. Satsuki.
hence the name is given.
So yes. Only two final participants and a reader, Mr. Achiwa, are allowed to go up there once a year.
The game is recorded using the camera and microphone already installed there...
... then it will be broadcast in the audience hall on the other side of the river.
Excessive.
It is said that the humidity and temperature inside the hall remain constant due to the air circulation system.
And the soundproofed walls will completely muffle the sound from the outside. The system installed there is an art of its own.
They build the ideal state of the environment just to play karuta ?!
I'm hungry!
Let's go to where to eat!
I want a cake!
Then, I stay first huh?
Have fun.
Kak Ran!
Let's get going!
Dah, until later.
See you later.
Be careful.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The souvenir runs out later if not quickly.
Auntie!
Let's start the exercise again!
Hold on for a while!
If you lack sleep, your energy will not be enough to get to the finals.
I'm fine!
Kazuha, a-is it Mrs. Shizuka? Could it be the former Queen who trained you?
Well.
That's great.
If this is possible you can win.
Let's go back to the room and start training ?!
If you really want to practice like that...
... how about trying to fight me?
I'm not sure this girl will get to the final.
What are you saying!
Calm down Kazuha!
Auntie!
I will be your opponent, are you willing?
Former Queen! Bu Ikenami Shizuka!
Why are you doing all this for the girl?
So you want to compete with me?
If you insist...
... with pleasure.
Pak Achiwa and Sekine?
Looks like they will go to the Achiwa Compound Building and train for tomorrow's game.
They were escorted by police on the way there, so no worries.
But the problem will start when they get there.
What about Momiji?
Do not worry!
He lives in Kyoto, he will leave with the others.
Ah, briefly. There's a phone.
The person in the photo you sent me, I've managed to identify it.
What? Is it true?
Yes. You might be shocked to find out.
I sent the details by e-mail, do not forget to read!
Thank you. Then, what about his karuta cards?
I'm running the current penganalisanya program, Professor who made.
I think I'll be able to find the card in the next hour.
Great. Immediately contact me when I've met.
Okay.
Geez.
From: Haibara
Subject: Do not forget the souvenir!
I sent you the profile of Nagoro.
Nagoro Shikao.
I have not felt this happy for a long time.
Thank you very much.
Come back, Iori ?!
Good.
Even though you're brave enough, but...
... my level that is still this far has surprised you. Do you still want to join the tournament?
Remember this is fine! My name is Momiji.
Momiji: The leaves are red.
I'm different from ordinary leaves like you.
The words "Kazuha" can be read "Happa": Literally meaning leaf.
D-Leaf?
Enough!
I will not hold back, even if my enemy is a beginner like you.
I've made a mistake by underestimating my previous opponent, the result I lost a landslide.
I do not want to feel ashamed like that anymore.
That is why I will play earnestly with all my capabilities.
I-That's what I want!
Well, let's just talk about his karuta.
Are you okay still here? Would not this make the president worried?
I thank you for your attention to me, but I'm fine.
That's because the famous western detective, Hattori Heiji, is always watching me.
What do you mean ?!
Ah, do not you know ?! Heiji is now my bodyguard.
Huh ?!
He has been keeping an eye on my house since yesterday.
All right, then I'll excuse you first.
I'm looking forward to our match tomorrow.
Ah, Heiji, that insolent child.
Hey, Kazuha ?!
You're okay right?
Heiji !!
I do not know what you've done with that woman, but I'm gonna destroy it at the karuta tournament tomorrow!
See it later, Heiji !!
Well, all right then.
What's up Hattori ?!
I do not know why, all of a sudden the hairs on my neck stood up and felt very cold!
Did you catch a cold?
Catch the wind? No, it's not like that...
... this is a sign of something creepy.
Ah, they are passing!
President of Achiwa.
Ooka Momiji.
And also Sekine.
Everything is together.
M-Could it be.
The car is Sekine.
So how is Sekine current?
The hospital has given news...
... it looks like he's still unconscious.
The probability of life expectancy is 50:50.
Ooka also hit by explosion, is she okay?
He is not hurt, but just in case...
... he and his driver, Iori, are undergoing an examination at the hospital.
Since this case is becoming more and more, you have to say everything you know.
Pak Achiwa.
Bomb blast at Nichiuri TV...
... we suspect that the target is the members of Satsuki-Kai.
Hey, uncle.
Do you know Pak Nagoro Shikao?
Bo-Boy, that photo... where do you come from?
You look very surprised, then you must know who this person is?
If you know something...
... please share the information with us without any cover-ups, Mr. Achiwa.
There is a karuta association in Kyoto called Nagoro-Kai.
They teach certain streams that are very elite.
Its members, who are not even more than 20 people, undergo a rigorous daily training routine each month.
Nagoro Shikao is the leader.
He is so talented.
People say if only a matter of time he can compete with Meijin.
But he is very insistent when playing.
Honestly, judging from wherever, the style of play is very far from the word beautiful.
Hey, I'm faster! The card is mine!
No! I did not touch the wrong card! Can not you see ya ?!
About five years ago, let's say Nagoro challenged the then president, Satsuki.
Provided that the loser must dissolve his association.
What ?! Does not that sound like a yaburi dojo?
Dojo Yaburi: Challenging a dojo with the aim of destroying or dispersing it.
But Mrs. Satsuki does not accept the challenge right?
Nagoro leaked all information about the challenge to the media, Satsuki inevitably have to accept it.
He says if Satsuki-Kai is afraid of fighting Nagoro-Kai and will definitely refuse to compete.
So yes.
So he is in a difficult position to be able to resist his challenge.
Then, the game itself?
It never happened.
Nagoro does not appear in the scheduled time.
Thus his match is considered a failure and Satsuki is declared the winner.
Nagoro who escaped from the match when the game will be covered by a very large media...
... because of his own actions, is the biggest disgrace in the world of karuta.
Then he disappears from the public spotlight.
So...
... what happened to Pak Nagoro and Nagoro-Kai now?
Nagoro-Kai is disbanded over his president's defeat.
Nagoro himself until now has not known its existence.
What is possible if Nagoro, driven by his hatred of Satsuki-Kai, is the mastermind behind all this.
I do not know. But the person who really wants Nagoro-Kai to be dissolved is...
... The late Yajima.
What ?!
We, Satsuki-Kai, are eager to settle the matter peacefully so things do not get worse.
Even so...
What about the other Nagoro-Kai members?
Anyone who wants to join Satsuki-Kai will be gladly accepted.
But, only they both decide to join.
Could they both be...?
Right. They are Ooka and Sekine.
The two men were involved in the explosion.
Yes. Especially Ooka, who studies Nagoro's special techniques to perfect his abilities.
Which of his favorite cards is almost the same as his teacher first.
The six cards containing the momiji poems inside have never escaped their decks.
He is Nagoro's first student and also the best.
Why Pak Nagoro's favorite cards should contain the momiji poems?
Since Nagoro's first name is Shikao.
Shikao: The stag.
Venison ?!
Venison: Shika niku.
Yes. The venison is often called the momiji right?
Venison can be called autumn foliage.
It may be very unpleasant for Nagoro because his beloved pupil joins Satsuki-Kai and is active there.
But why is his revenge now? Besides, what is the reason for sending threats to us?
We still do not know the reason for not doing anything for the last five years.
But maybe the bomb threat indicates that he has returned.
Means...
... we are deliberately told to see the serial action of revenge Nagoro Shikao against Satsuki-Kai.
Excuse me for a moment.
What is this? Good.
I think we should cooperate in an investigation with the Kyoto Prefectural Police.
Right.
What ?!
Inspector! We have checked Sekine's cell phone, it seems like she received a weird message just before the explosion happened.
The strange message?
We have not been able to confirm who the sender is, but the message is just a cargo card drawing.
What kind of cargo card?
At the moment it is non-negotiable.
Look at Mount Tamuke, it becomes beautiful because of the red foliage.
That's Nagoro's favorite card!
What ?!
What's wrong, Heiji ?!
I have to make sure now!
Momiji is in danger!
Is this Iori?
This voice, Mr. Hattori ?!
Right. Please check my Momiji inbox immediately if there is a message from an unknown sender!
Inbox message?
Is something wrong, Iori?
This is a phone call from Mr. Hattori.
Heiji ?!
Let me talk to him Iori!
Momiji!
Immediately check your message inbox!
Inbox? What's wrong all of a sudden ?!
Besides, I'm really glad you called Heiji.
Ah, what exactly do you mean?
Here there is only a picture submission.
What is a caruta card image ?!
Not possible! How do you know?
What card is that? Quickly read it!
Due to the storm wind blast from the slopes of Mount Mimuro, maple leaves are falling.
Momiji, listen carefully! Do not go anywhere tonight!
And do not go home!
Go to the Osaka Police Station right now!
Understand ?!
Even if you ask for it yourself, but I still can not do that.
I have to prepare for Satsuki Cup tomorrow, so...
You have no right to say that now! Chances are you've been the next target, you know ?!
I'll be fine.
Anyway, I have you Heiji.
You will protect me right?
Huh ?!
Because I never forget the promise.
Promise ?!
Already yes!
The stupid guy, he hung up the phone.
It seems that he also received a picture message in the form of a karuta card.
Right.
Otaki! Tightening up on Ooka Momiji, now!
Ready!
This means only Yajima does not receive the card message karuta.
But actually there is a message coming from the karuta card at the Yajima murder scene.
Meaning, after killing Yajima, Mr. Nagoro, the real culprit...
... leave his favorite card there and escape from the scene.
Then Sekine comes afterwards and hides that fact.
So yes. Sekine must have realized that Nagoro who had committed the murder was seeing the message at the crime scene...
... so he ruffled the victim's house to disguise his ex-teacher's actions as if it were a robber.
That means Sekine arrived at the scene before the police?
Yeah, chances are like that.
Actually we have someone to analyze the pictures from the scene for us.
By judging by the angle and shape of the splash of blood present in the card...
Here it is!
... we can know the true state of the scene.
Please pay attention to the TV!
On the right you can see the cards scattered on the floor and blood-stained from Yajima.
Then, on the left there are cards that are still clean and that have blood stains that are then randomized.
So from the faint distortion caused by how the blood is splashed...
... the card held by Yajima is...
Card number 32!
Harumichi no Tsuraki!
In the mountain stream, there is a barrier wall formed by a storm.
But that's just a maple leaf, helpless to fly away.
So far one of Mr. Nagoro's favorite cards is in Yajima's place!
Please pay attention here. These are the cards used in the incident so far.
Top left corner, Nichiuri TV.
Yajima.
Sekine.
This is the card Momiji received, which we are investigating.
These cards have an equation.
Everything contains the words "autumn foliage" or "momiji".
As we all know, all the cards are his favorite Nagoro.
It seems no doubt that the real offender is Nagoro Shikao.
I do not think that's possible, but if it is Nagoro the culprit...
I'm worried about the fact that there are six cards featuring "momiji" that Mr. Nagoro always uses.
What do you mean?
That means there are still two remaining cards that have not been used.
Eh ?!
If Pak Nagoro had used those karuta cards to indicate that he was the mastermind behind all this...
... then he will not leave two unused cards.
Could there be anyone other than the ooka...
The question is, who is the target matching the two remaining cards?
If we do not solve it soon, it will be difficult to protect them from Mr. Nagoro.
Good work, both of you! I have a feeling that you can stop Nagoro before the police.
But we still need more information.
Say, what happened between you and Pak Nagoro five years ago?
B-Okay.
So there is still something huh ?!
Something you did not say before!
Right. I did not say it, but since there's only two of you here, it should not matter.
Let's go back to my hotel!
I'll tell you what really happened that day.
You guys wait till i come back huh?
I'm giving this back to Momiji first.
Good!
We are waiting for you!
Young lady, the police just got in touch.
Looks like they are improving the guard around the house.
It's okay, it does not matter.
Excuse me!
You're Momiji right? My name is Mouri. I was the one who called.
Ah, so that was you ?!
Thank you very much for bothering to come here to return it to me.
T-No problem.
This, this thing is yours right, Momiji, right?
Thank you very much! It's like a lucky charm for me!
Without this, I'm really very worried about the tournament tomorrow.
But now I'm relieved.
It's like you've reached out to help your enemy.
No, no.
I hope the girl does not hurt her finger from practicing too hard.
Wow, those nails are so beautiful!
Ah, this I use to protect my fingertips.
Because it is an asset for the player karuta, besides when practicing, I always wear it.
Ah, so so.
By the way I've opened the wallet to find your address.
There is a photo.
What is this photo you mean?
The person in the photo...?
It's Heiji.
I thought so.
This is a picture of my childhood when I lost to Heiji in the karuta tournament.
As I cry for losing, Heiji tells me...
Do not cry! I'll make you my wife when we meet again, so just wait.
Be-Really?
Yes.
I promise.
Heh ?!
So that's the real statement of love.
Because of that promise Heiji is my future husband.
T-But that's just a promise of children!
Children or adults alike!
The real man will not break his promise easily right ?!
In order to accurately summarize the heart of the girl I love.
Right.
Although the water flow is fast,
branched off because of a large rock,
will definitely be united again at the mouth of the river.
It means that in any case you will be separated, your heart will remain connected.
I always believe that.
Please tell this to Happa-chan!
H-Happa-chan?
Once I point my gaze at a card, I will not let anyone take it from me!
My teacher taught me!
Momiji.
Ran!
Why are you daydreaming? Your behavior is so strange after returning from the streets keliliing Osaka, Ran!
Sorry! What about your practice?
Well, his mother Heiji gave me the task of choosing the favorite card I would use in the competition.
But I still have not found which card suits me.
Is it that difficult?
Hyakunin Isshu has a lot of love poems right?
Do not think about the tournament.
Just pick a poem that you can easily understand.
Love ya...
If it were me, I would choose this one!
"Meguri aite", Murasaki Shikibu right?
We met at the intersection, but I do not know if it was him. Because the moon at night disappears behind the clouds.
It was a poem about a friend who suddenly disappeared in a meeting that had been eagerly awaited.
Wherever I think if I'm going to meet him, he just disappears somewhere.
Yet there are still many who want to talk to him you know.
Right. If so...
I am...
Even though I hide it, it will still be visible on my face, the person I love, my secret love.
And people ask me, is there anything bothering you?
Poems about love that can not possibly be hidden.
That's perfect for you Kazuha! Even Momiji can also find out.
Talk about him, I wonder why he can be so confident.
He speaks as if he already is a fiancée of Heiji.
Hey, Ran! You also think so right ?!
Ah, right.
I can not tell her that when I was a kid...
... Hattori once proposed to Momiji.
What ?! Pak Nagoro came to play with Mrs. Satsuki the day before the day of the match?
Is it true ?!
Yes. I was away.
The article mentions that Nagoro escaped from the game for fear of fighting Satsuki, but...
... he actually came the day before.
But why the day before?
Who knows. We would not know if we did not ask Nagoro ourselves, but maybe...
... Satsuki says that Nagoro wants to defeat him using Satsuki-Kai karuta card.
He uses that karuta ?!
But karats Satsuki-Kai right...
... stored in a museum ?!
No one wants it then, so we keep it at home.
But the match can not be held without the reader right?
We keep a lot of tapes on our shelves.
We use it to practice karuta.
So, how's the match?
Satsuki won it brilliantly.
Nagoro is no match.
I still remember his pale face as I rushed out the front door after I got home.
That's the last time I saw it.
Why do not you tell the police ?!
I'm afraid the information will leak to the media and other Satsuki-Kai members if I tell you.
If they find out the legendary caruta used in such unofficial rivalry, there will be commotion among the members.
Well, that does not mean I can not understand your reasoning.
I mean, it's not that I do not trust the police...
Is this... something wrong with this photo.
Maybe because Mr. Achiwa's car is different from the present one.
Please stop Nagoro's crime as soon as possible.
Of course! You can count on us.
Ran, just two will not be enough.
Can you add two more?
My brain needs a lot of sugar intake.
O-Okay.
He knows just from his voice?
This girl...
Kakoi-te (close hands): close the card by hand.
Watari-te (crossed arms): snapping away two different cards spread far apart.
This is bad, I still can not use kakoi-te or watari-te well.
I also still can not predict the course of the game, if not immediately I fix...
... Heiji. The woman will take Heiji.
What's wrong Kazuha?
You look moody?
Heiji ?!
Do you fight with someone?
Be quiet you're stupid!
You're the bodyguard of that woman right?
Go there, just go back to him!
What the hell is this. And I want to replace my tired Mama to play against you.
I do not ever lose playing karuta against you know.
That was when we were in elementary school!
You are not my match now!
Hey, hey, Hattori. Do not you remember something about a karuta tournament when you were in elementary school?
Maybe something about a girl crying after losing to you?
Oh, right! Kazuha, I met him in a karuta tournament!
The only tournament that you follow and you even win it is not it?
Well. There is a girl crying because she lost to me!
The boy is Ooka Momiji!
So the girl...
So, Hattori. Do you remember it?
Remember what?
Like you ever promised something to Momiji maybe...?
As I recall I said this to him "try harder when we meet again".
In addition, you hurry back to him!
You have to protect that woman right?
But the police are already...
Whatever, it's important to go!
If he gets injured before the tournament starts...
... he will not be able to join right ?!
Are you serious?
All right then.
Mama, I leave it to you.
Okay.
Even though I hide it, it will still be visible on my face, the person I love, my secret love.
And people ask me, is there anything bothering you?
Pak Guru Nagoro.
Please lend me your strength again this year.
Please guard me...
... Satsuki.
Kyoto
Achiwa Compound Building
In the Bay of Naniwa, the flowers are now blooming, having been dormant throughout the winter.
Now spring has arrived and the flowers begin to bloom.
From Mount Yoshino, blowing cool breeze, autumn wind.
Kak Kazuha got it!
He wears clothes that are different from other players, so we can easily see them.
Right.
Is not he wearing aikidogi?
Why is Conan not watching with us?
Well that's it.
He said he would go somewhere with Kak Heiji.
Ah, right! Let's send to Conan Genta's photo at the souvenir shop!
Photo when he got angry?
The eight-fold cherry blossom in Nara, our ancient capital, has been blooming.
It looks like the show has started.
Yes.
There is no way for Nagoro to break in with this tight security.
Right. Not just Nagoro...
... employees who had been fired were also not allowed to enter.
We have also checked all employees seriously.
We will not allow any gap for Nagoro to enter.
What's up Hattori ?!
Ah, it's nothing.
Who is this?
Oh, it's from Mitsuhiko.
Geez, what are you doing Genta? Gripping senmaizuke is like a hawk.
Senmaizuke: Pickles made from sliced radish.
So yes!
As the dew promised, a hope for a thirsty plant.
Aochwa Compound Guard Post
The first momiji finishes it, according to our shadow.
Kak Kazuha?
Looks like he's still not done yet.
Ah, is not that him!
There it is! Kak Kazuha!
You're great Kazuha!
He won the first half, a good start.
Pak Sekine? Mr. Sekine?
Ooka Momiji
Toyama Kazuha
Final
Thank you very much.
Oh, so that girl can get to the final.
This is shocking! We do not know of any very talented participants among us.
Great!
Maybe he'll be a champion ?!
Of course!
Great Kazuha! If you keep playing like this, your victory is confirmed!
I wonder what Kazuha understands...
... if he should declare his love for Hattori if he can defeat Momiji.
Kazuha. He tried very hard.
He will play Momiji shortly.
Well.
What ?!
Sekine already aware?
Well! So our guess is right ?!
Understandable! I'll leave this to the Kyoto Police and I'll be right there.
Sekine already aware?
Right, it seems so.
More or less everything is like Heiji's suspicions.
But there is a need what Sekine visit Yajima's house?
It seems that lately Yajima is looking for Nagoro.
Sekine knows it, it seems that he's keeping an eye on Yajima and wants to know if Yajima knows something about his former teacher.
Then, when he realizes that something is wrong...
... he even found a corpse.
It's possible. I hope we can hear the whole story directly from Sekine upon our return to Osaka.
Yes.
Now just trust to the Kyoto Prefectural Police.
Good.
Ah, wait a minute! I'm coming with you.
This is the last one.
But, what's the importance of putting dynamite in a place like this?
What's with the smoke?
Fire?
No, the alarm does not sound so it's not a fire!
Could it be a bomb blast ?!
Hey, hey! No kidding!
Is not it outside that is very noisy ?!
What place is in the western forest?
Ah, there is only an old warehouse.
Does the camera show anything?
The area is out of range, so there is no camera.
What ?!
Hey, that smoke, is it possible?
Well. Come on!
We are going to the Satsuki Hall there.
What smell is this?
Ah, the elevator has improved recently.
This smell may come from the oil they use.
Are you bothered?
No, not so...
... maybe I'm just too excited.
This does make me excited.
What do you feel now?
Well, I did not expect to get this far...
... so I'm very excited. I guess you're not like me?
You're wrong, I feel my heart seems to be dislodged.
I can not stop thinking about Heiji's face when I express my feelings for her.
I... I can not lose to him. Will not!
Do not come near!
What's going on ?!
Inspector!
Is there an explosion?
Right. The victim was one person.
His body severely injured...
... we can not identify the body with that condition.
So yes.
The question is, when and how...
... the bomb could be planted here?
From the scene of the crime scene we have a possibility that the survivors themselves planted the explosives.
What ?!
Pak Nagoro accidentally blew himself up ?!
Please start autopsinya as soon as possible!
Good!
Hello? Here is Ayanokoji.
What's wrong with Kudo?
Hattori, look at that!
What is it ?! A ring?
Well, possibly belong to the victim.
You found something?
There! Look at that ring! The possibility of the victim.
The ring is big enough.
Well, that big ring is not something you see everyday.
The ring is big enough... wait a minute!
Kaieda Togo!
Kaieda ?! You mean his former secretary Pak Achiwa?
Yes! No more mistake.
Kaieda wears a ring like this on his thumb.
What does that mean Kaieda is the real culprit ?!
No! If we do not find the ring...
... we must assume that it was Mr. Nagoro's body!
That means the explosion was meant to make it look like Mr. Nagoro is dead.
Wait...
... if it should be today Mr. Nagoro died here...
... surely two remaining cargo cards have been sent to someone right ?!
Not two. Otaki just called me...
... his secretary Pak Achiwa checks his message inbox again...
... and Pak Achiwa apparently also received a picture message card karuta this morning.
That means only one card left ?!
There is only one card... and the final match.
I understand!
Because Mr. Achiwa has received his picture of his karuta card, it means there's only one left!
So who will receive his final card (final)...
... not yet certain!
That means... Inspector! Please check out his phone Toyama Kazuha!
Eh? OK.
But what does all this mean?
The reason why the last card has not been sent is...
... the perpetrators do not know who will go to the final round!
Means that the next target is...
... three people who are in Satsuki Hall ?!
Previously I'm sorry.
You two, take all your skills and show us a great game!
Please help!
In the Bay of Naniwa, the flowers are now blooming, having been dormant throughout the winter.
One, two... fight!
Kazuha, show them your true abilities!
How, did he receive a picture card message karuta?
Yes. 15 minutes ago, Nagoro's favorite card.
I thought he would send it!
You should immediately stop the final game, understand ?!
This way Kudo!
Hey, where are you going ?!
Faster if you use a motorcycle!
Eh ?! Stop the final game?
Good! Understandable!
I will try to contact the person in the Hall right now...
What's this?
Probably just a small earthquake. You do not have to worry.
What ?! What happened?
Maybe it's broken.
What the hell. Why break the final fitting...
What's the power outage?
No, the lights here are still on.
Shit! They've started it!
Right! A tight grip!
Hattori! How do we get to the Satsuki Hall ?!
Trust me! I have an idea.
Oi, is it possible?
Bahwan the goddess who controls all in the past, I never heard it.
As expected.
Happa-chan has not moved.
He ignored my favorite card.
In this extreme difficulty...
What ?! Why is the fire already this big ?!
We suspect that there is something flammable in there.
Have the firefighters not arrived yet ?!
The road is too narrow for a fire truck.
And the disaster prevention system is also offline ?!
Yes.
So this is over yes?
Hattori, do you still think the real culprit is Mr. Nagoro ?!
No. There is only one person who can re-register Kaieda, who has left Satsuki-Kai, as an employee and gave him a bomb!
President Achiwa Kensuke.
And he plans to commit suicide by involving the two men!
I will not let him do it!
The card is in a hard place to reach, and Momiji definitely knows it well if it's my favorite card!
You want this card is not it?
But I will not let you get it! If I can secure it, my victory can be ascertained!
I'll get it, for whatever's sake. I have to get it!
Be still, be quiet!
These insignificant voices, immediately get out of my mind!
What's wrong Kazuha? You look gloomy?
Do you fight with someone?
Please permit a moment!
Right, I can not fight it.
The sound of air conditioning, the sound of kimono friction, the sound when we touch the card, the breath sound is weak...
... and the sound of my heartbeat, they are all friends!
They allow me to enter my mind.
Thanks time.
I'll catch the right sound!
With the pine growing there I will come back to you again.
We all assume that all this incident is Pak Nagoro's revenge action to Satsuki-Kai!
But all that is just a story by Pak Achiwa for us.
For a reason, five years ago, Mr. Nagoro appeared on the night before his game with Mrs. Satsuki.
Pak Achiwa claimed that the winning moment was Mrs. Satsuki, but something was wrong with it.
You mean the photo we saw in the article in the hotel first?
Well. Mr. Achiwa showed the article that contained Mrs. Satsuki's victory at that time.
Is not she going to wash her car until the day before the game? But in that picture the car looks dirty!
He did not wash his car the day before the game because he already knows Pak Nagoro will not come!
My love is like the month before dawn, cold and unsympathetic.
Looks like I'm faster.
No, I'm faster!
Are you the right person to judge who is faster among us ?!
I did not think they would do such an action in the final game.
If in the preliminary match five years ago Mrs. Satsuki lost, could not that be her motive?
Well, and Pak Nagoro is purposely silenced for the purpose of protecting Satsuki-Kai's honor.
Yajima realizes that his karuta card can be a proof that Mr. Achiwa has committed a crime.
But what kind of evidence is that ?!
What if Mr. Achiwa accidentally holds the stack of cards with his hands that are exposed to Mr. Nagoro's blood?
You're right, fingerprints!
I did not realize it until recently I saw a picture, but...
... chances are that the caruta card still has his fingerprint Pak Achiwa.
That's why Yajima suggests the idea of broadcast coverage of Satsuki-Kai...
... so he can get a videotape of Satsuki-Kai's karuta as evidence.
Well, that's why the Yajima was killed to coincide with a bomb blast in a TV studio.
Right! But why...
... why did he bring his crime in the final tournament in this Achiwa Compound Building?
What if Mr. Nagoro's body was hidden in the Satsuki Hall, where the final match was held?
That's right, it's the perfect place to hide it.
So... he has planned all his crimes from scratch ?!
He must have made this perfect plan to describe Mr. Nagoro as the culprit.
But, if his corpse can be found, he will lose everything.
That's the aula!
Well!
I do not know where the ends are.
The deep heart.
The ghost card!
The situation is getting worse, the fire has reached that level!
We have to get there soon!
How? In addition we have to extinguish the fire first!
No time to hesitate! You just think how to extinguish the fire!
And you? Impossible! You're kidding, right ?!
We're starting, Kudo!
Let's hurry!
What's that ?!
Good! Now grew up!
Quickly! We must succeed on time!
What's... a fire ?!
Stop! Do not get out!
Heiji? What are you doing here?!
Oh! The direction of the waterfall changed!
This is a miracle!
The fire is gone!
What? What happened?!
It seems we have done it in time somehow.
Very good, Kudo.
Heiji, what happened?
I told you to stay inside, it's dangerous outside!
Uh, is there Conan too? What is this? What are you two doing here?
It may be easier if we ask Mr. Achiwa.
What do you mean?
The two of you, stay behind me.
Why should we...?
Hey, Mr. Achiwa.
Would not a bad thing happen to you if someone checks these karuta cards?
Hey, Heij, what have you done with all this ?!
Let's start by hearing the explanation of what happened to this uncle.
It started exactly a year ago when Momiji recorded his victory in this special hall.
At that time, a set of cards belonging to Momiji was very similar to that of his teacher, Pak Nagoro, whom he used in certain matches.
Our favorite cards are almost the same because Master Nagoro was the one who taught me to play karuta with seme-garuta style.
Seme-garuta: The attacking style in karuta.
But, it is an incredible coincidence to...
Say coincidence is true.
The black mark on this side of Satsuki-Kai karuta is...
... surely the late Yajima noticed that it appeared from nowhere five years ago.
What is the real black mark?
It is the fingerprint of the man who holds his karuta with hands already exposed to Mr. Nagoro's blood.
The blood of Guru Nagoro?
Pak Nagoro who is thought to have disappeared since five years ago...
... was killed at the time.
Not possible.
And the owner of that fingerprint is...
... the real culprit behind Pak Nagoro's murder.
I have been defeated.
I will admit it all.
Instead, do not hand over Satsuki-Kai's karuta as evidence.
For Satsuki-Kai, that...
Oh, so that's it?
There's something I can not understand, but you end up saying it.
The fingerprints on this caruta are not yours, Mr. Achiwa!
No, it's mine! Of course it's my fingerprint!
Never mind...
... it is true that you and Kaieda are behind the recent sequence of events.
But you are not the murderer of Pak Nagoro five years ago!
The culprit is Mrs. Satsuki.
When I saw the incident, I realized everything...
... Nagoro has challenged him then Satsuki has been defeated.
They use cassettes that we always use instead of readers.
Do you know what that means?
Satsuki has often listened to it many times.
Of course that's just one of our tapes...
... but, he knows the composition of the card with the heart to some extent.
He greatly benefited with it...
... but he still lost.
Nagoro's ability exceeded what we imagined.
I can only guess what kind of fear Satsuki feels...
... because there is no doubt that he will definitely be embarrassed in the next game.
Fear is what drives him to commit the crime.
After that, Satsuki get rid of all his human feelings...
... to resign from the Satsuki-Kai management ranks.
Then, two years ago, he died of a serious illness from the misery.
That is the truth.
Please understand me.
Stop!
Do not do it!
This is all wrong Nagoro.
If that person does not embarrass Satsuki, this will not be...
He does not mean to embarrass him!
Before Master Nagoro came to her the day before the game...
... I asked him then...
... the reason is to treat Satsuki-Kai as an enemy.
Enemy? I thought it might seem that from the outside.
But if it is not so, I will not be able to compete with him.
I just want to hear it say "you're great" when I win...
... as my enemy as well as my first love.
C-Love first ?!
Right. Master Nagoro admired Bu Satsuki and started playing karuta because of it.
However, doctors say that he only has one year to play karuta because of his eye condition.
I think that is the reason his karuta style of play became very aggressive.
Because Master has no time.
So he wants to show him his true abilities the day before the game, then let Mrs Satsuki win the real match.
So that his students, including me, can not see him anymore...
... has a reason to join Satsuki-Kai.
Mrs. Satsuki did not know that and killed Mr Nagoro.
Ti-Not.
What have I done?
A-what is that ?!
Kazuha!
Are you okay ?!
Yes!
But I can not stand.
All of you get into the elevators! Sakarang!
Momiji! Come on, quickly!
O-Okay.
Get up! Come on, quickly!
Do not care about me. Leave me alone.
Stop the nonsense. You can not die now!
Momiji! come on, fast!
Okay.
Kazuha!
Go crawling up to my place!
Yes.
Faster!
Emergency! Just a little more.
Can be!
What's...?!
Please...
... do not fall down!
Shit!
What ?!
I will not let you!
Are you all right ?! We're right there!
It was almost there.
Hattori!
This is bad... the building will collapse! Get out of here!
Eh ?! Wait! Do not go!
Heiji!
Kazuha, get on!
Hattori... Kazuha.
Please, get out of there somehow!
Heiji, look at that!
Yes.
What's up, Heiji?
A tight grip!
Not possible! Are you going to jump far across the river ?!
Yes that's it! Great if you understand!
Are you kidding right? What do you think?! It is too far!
Hey, Heiji!
How about jumping into the lake instead?
Impossible! if we jump from this distance, the surface of the water will feel hard like concrete!
Pegangang yangatat, Kazuha! If you let it go...
... I will kill you!
All right.
There is no other way...
... we'll die if we stay here!
That...
... Hattori ?!
There's still something I want to tell you!
The motor.
Coming there!
Heiji!
Kazuha!
Are you all right, Kazuha ?!
Yes.
I'm getting bored with this dramatic escape.
Gosh... they both base.
For a moment I thought we would not make it.
By the way, Heiji.
What do you want to tell me ?!
A-What? What do you mean?
Are not you the one telling yourself... if you can not die before saying something to me?
Maybe you heard wrong?
No! Since the weight of my listening karuta so sharp!
No need to dodge, confess it!
Ti-No, wait...
What's up ?!
I've told you to wait, right ?!
What do you want to tell me ?!
The only thing I want to say to you is...
Thank you for bringing us on our way.
We are the ones who should be grateful.
Anyway... what happened to your Karuta Club?
Well, the school has appreciated my efforts to get to the final so the club does not get dissolved!
Even though I ended up losing.
Kazuha.
Come with me!
Ah ?!
What's happening?
What's this? Is that a secret?
Really?
Yeah right, because I'm going to take "shinoburedo".
So you really chose that poem as your favorite card?
No, not because of the poem, but the name of the poet!
Taira no Kanemori, the only poet among all poets of Hyakunin Isshu...
平 兼 盛 - Taira no Kanemori 平 次
- Heiji
... who owns Kanji "Hey" as in Heiji in his name.
So that's where I can see it as a Heiji card.
After that, I send it to Heiji picture "shinoburedo"!
"That's what I feel".
You sent a "shinoburedo" card to express your feelings?
Is not that against the rules?
Momiji!
Did you hear what we were talking about ?!
You're not the only one who has a sharp hearing.
Oh, Momiji!
What are you doing here?
I came to express my love as promised.
Because Heiji did not say it first.
Huh? What are you talking about?
This photo is the proof!
The promise of the little finger.
Which means that they promise something to each other.
If you break the agreement, you must stab the eye with a needle!
Wait a minute! What did I promise?
condo attara, yome ni
toru sakai Yome: Wife
"Do not cry! I'll make you my wife when we meet again, so just wait."
This person has the ability to be captured while in the most embarrassing situations.
Or will you pretend that it never happened?
Ah, I remember now!
What I said then is...
"Do not cry, let's fight back someday!"
condo attara, motto Tsuyome ni
toru sakai Tsuyume: Stronger
"But at the next meeting, I will also get stronger, so grasp your skills and wait for me!"
Tsu...
Yome ni...
Toru sakai!
Because my opponent is a girl, I realize I can not hurt her.
Iori, we're leaving now!
Good, young lady!
Anyhow, I'm leaving now!
Once I point my gaze at a card, I will not let anyone take it from me!
You remember that's fine!
Kazuha!
What? Does he want a re-match, Kazuha?
Sorry, are you sleeping?
Sonoko, you know Hyakunin Isshu well, right?
Well, I play it with my family every new year.
I sent a meguri aite card to Shinichi.
And reply by sending me a card se wo hayami, but...
... I forgot what it means.
"Even though I'm separated from a very valuable person...
... someday we must meet again!"
It is a love poem written by Sutoku In! Basic is in love.
Ah! Wait, Sonoko!
You should not forget such a thing, right ?!
Translator:
darkestseven
Yogyakarta, October 25, 2017.
Thanks to Barikios for the Arabic version subtitle.