Ten thousand years ago, Antarctica
This is...
Doctor!
Great.
This is the bones of the green giant right?
Over there.
Be carefully!
The last shadow is...
Carla, hurry!
Come right here Get out!
Bleed!
Love squid ink!
Let me use the soundproof gun to deal with it, go away!
Dr., hurry up!
Dead!
Right!
Golden ring!
Ten thousand years later, ToKyo
Now the heat has not shown signs of retracement. Ten thousand years later, ToKyo
Now the heat has not shown signs of retracement.
Today many areas remain above 35 degrees Celsius.
And according to the forecast hot sun is still prolonged...
In the central area, we note, there are places up to 45 degrees.
The hot sun is shining all over the country.
Tokyo has been continuously 2 weeks...
You need an ice-shingling supply.
Predicting the day the heat will be extremely hot.
This way I will be baked cooked.
It's not like you can do this kind of exercise.
You say that again.
Doraemi called to this.
Doraemon, are you okay?
That's good, it looks good to me.
Not good at all, it's hot here.
Hot? Strange too we.
As predicted by the robot,
This week he will meet the most unlucky in life,
He will die of freezing.
Frozen?
The result of the fortune teller is that.
Frozen.
Guess he will meet "ice accident". Frozen.
Guess he will meet "ice accident".
East hard because of ice,
You will have an ice-related accident.
In short, you have to be careful about what's involved with that tape.
Do not come near them.
He also has to watch out for penguins.
Your lucky thing is the star.
Do not know what to do.
Doraemi, you are easily affected by the movement too.
What are you talking about?
There is no proper eating ice that is hot dead.
Want to eat ice? Ice flowing... Yes.
I know there is a place to eat ice shakes delight.
Make sure to leave this place.
This is the place, come here want to take as much ice as well
The secret of nature, reveal the iceberg mystery. The iceberg, 27 kilometers long, travels from Antarctica to the Arctic.
Huge iceberg The secret of nature, reveal the iceberg mystery. The iceberg, 27 kilometers long, travels from Antarctica to the Arctic.
We go to eat ice cream delight. The secret of nature, reveal the iceberg mystery. The iceberg, 27 kilometers long, travels from Antarctica to the Arctic.
We go to eat ice cream delight.
That's how is it!
But Doraemi's fortune?
You are about to crash, need to avoid ice.
No need to worry, no need to worry.
Is this a giant iceberg?
Over there!
Nothing at all.
That was a newsletter more than a month ago.
Has iceberg melted yet?
Here, over there!
Hey, I just hit a wall of ice.
You look at this side!
Huge iceberg!
Great, here is the ice!
Come here you can eat ice shakes delight it!
The ice here is not eaten up too much!
Let me borrow a miracle door for a moment.
No need, I have a good security.
Ice sculpture stick
What is this?
Oil!
This is the furniture?
I was wrong.
Let's see, adjust the incremental mode.
Next we will add some more details.
Like this.
Here.
Great, into a sofa!
Advantage is complete, followed by soft sponge spray.
After spraying this up,
The tape will become soft and spongy, but will not melt.
Can I make another table?
Of course, it can be made into any shape.
Cool pleasant too heaven!
The recent summer is getting hotter and hotter.
If there is ice cover
The entire surface of the earth is good.
There it goes again.
But long ago,
It's just like you said.
The surface of the earth is covered by a thick layer of ice.
I know, is the time of the mammoth right?
It's far more than that mammoth time.
At that time,
The surface of the earth is covered by a very thick layer of ice.
Really?
At that time, both the mountains and the sea were covered by ice.
So no matter where you go,
Also see the scene as before us now.
What I'm saying is that the phenomenon of the earth is called snowball.
Extend those tens of millions of years.
In short, these are very distant things,
Since before there are humans.
Well, cool enough,
We go home for homework.
I have found a good place like this.
We play here a little longer.
That's right, we created a playground on ice!
Let's do it!
Use ice to make a ferris wheel and roller coaster.
What about exercise?
No problem, summer vacation is full of time.
Home! Home!
Then, just for a moment!
Great, no Doraemon!
Doraemon: Nobita And The Adventures To Antarctic kachikochi Sync: a lé - NetHD.org
Why stop it?
Nobita, what's wrong?
That's strange.
Doraemon, fast, fast!
Nobita!
Dangerous it!
Make sure!
Sorry.
Hey, let us play ice-skating with.
It is OK...
Let me build a more solid play area.
Okay, what do you plan to do?
I just heard something.
Hey, wait!
Extreme!
Doraemon dig the tunnel too deep too.
What is it?
What is this round?
The tunnel is about to collapse!
Dead, it looks like the iceberg is flowing.
Where did Nobita go?
Nobita Oh!
Nobita!
That's dangerous!
Doraemon!
Nobita!
Look!
What is this ice sheet for?
I found it at the head of the iceberg.
What is this?
Is Doraemon's security?
Not my stuff.
Sorry.
I find it like a bracelet,
Did someone drop it?
Then to the police station.
At that time outside of us there was no one.
It is frozen in ice,
It must have been there for a long time.
Yeah, that iceberg drifted from Antarctica right?
That's right.
So this is the Antarctic's drop?
Antarctica how can someone live?
Probably there is, there is an Antarctic base somewhere...
The back of this ring may have a bigger detector.
Is this
So how?
The device determines the tape life
Use this inscription to determine when the ice has frozen.
Super too!
Ten thousand years ago, of course.
Ten thousand years ago?
Is it so old?
Iceberg
It is precisely because of the snowfall of ten thousand years ago gradually accumulated,
Snow accumulation gradually formed into perennial ice.
Was it ten thousand years ago that was down there?
Not only that.
Since the Antarctic continent was discovered about 200 years ago.
So before that
Surely mankind has never stepped on Antarctica.
More than ten thousand years ago, the Stone Age.
Man of the moment
Still, it is not possible to make this exquisitely crafted metal ring.
Ten thousand years ago? In Antarctica?
If you can find the owner of that ring...
Discover new...
Bring the century!
Nobita, did you find anything frozen in the ice?
Let's go back and find it!
OK, let's...
It is too late today, tomorrow.
Tomorrow we will go back to the iceberg where to find it.
Too good, so tomorrow we will focus here.
Do not sleep!
Of course!
Good night, Mom!
Good night!
Nobita!
Who?
Wait.
Cold too, wait a minute.
Doraemon.
You will meet the cold limit, your luck is the star.
So you have to be careful with cold ice.
Has anyone dropped it?
This must be submitted to the police department.
Doraemon.
We're out here.
Where did you rush in the early morning?
Coming to Antarctica a little.
Have to go back to dinner.
Yes.
Atlantis.
I also heard him say.
Under the Antarctic ice sheet
Is an ancient civilization.
There are many legends about it.
Actually also possible.
This is the Atlantis civilization.
If there is a mysterious Atlantis civilization
So the metal ring was created 100 thousand years ago
Nor is it not possible.
It turned out to be so, this Atlantis
Where is Antarctica located?
That's Atlantis. If I know
It was not called a mysterious civilization.
Really?
Although I do not know much about Atlantis.
But I feel under the Antarctic ice sheet
It is true that something is buried.
Let me use this map
This is the location of the iceberg yesterday.
Now show the sea currents around.
Iceberg may have been pushed by currents.
If backward in the ocean current,
Take a large circle around the West Antarctic continent,
Will eventually come to this position.
The first iceberg was formed here.
So come on.
Atlantis?
No, that golden ring is not frozen here.
What do you mean?
Are not icebergs from here?
Next.
Time to form ice sheets in Antarctica
Was about 40 million years ago.
Snow turns into ice, ice slowly builds up into heaps.
Eventually formed a giant glacier also known as ice bed.
It moves,
Ice increasingly heavy,
It will be like water running from high to low.
After the ice floes with sea water,
Hit by sea waves,
Should be cut off,
Then form the glaciers.
It turned out that way.
So where is the gold ring frozen?
From here begin to go in the direction of the glacier
So it must have been frozen somewhere on this continent.
So follow this map
Explore the world under the ice only!
But I have not imagined yet.
Does the star go down like sugar?
In short, from now on,
We will come to form icebergs
Show on this map look up.
What do you guys see?
Great.
Let's just leave.
Find Atlantis in Antarctica
Is the discovery of the century.
Look for the owner of the ring.
So next.
Are you ready?
Is this the Antarctic?
You can see also.
The front is half the other hemispheres.
It is winter now.
In winter, the Antarctic sunk into the darkness.
Months did not see the sunrise.
Always night?
Be careful.
The temperature of our place is now about 30 degrees.
The temperature on the other side is minus 40 degrees.
That is not possible.
We are going to die free.
Not afraid.
Wear this on
What is this?
How are you?
Wear this?
This is the extreme adventurous outfit.
Wearing it on tape will not be slippery.
Even to Antarctica is also warm comfort.
How?
Great, very good.
Pawn shop yet?
Now let's start.
Look, it's full of stars.
Look, there is a house there.
That is the research station.
Scientists conduct observations and work there.
This is my area.
Based on what to say?
To tell the truth, I still do not see the glacier flowing.
The glacier is only moving a few millimeters.
So the eyes are usually not visible.
Is that so?
How do we explore under the ice?
This.
Winding the cords.
what is this?
Yes, it is possible to explore the things buried at our feet.
Close your eyes and move.
So what?
What can be buried down?
Lemon candy can not?
Do not open your eyes peek.
Open your eyes, friction watch wire.
So what?
If friction is strong wire
It can find buried objects near us.
This means,
We should look at this deeper here.
We follow its instructions
It is possible to find items buried under ice.
It turned out that way.
Okay, let's go.
But how can this be done?
Present. This is a rope that will listen to music as you would like and a spectrum music dedicated to exploring the terrain.
First blow the song of it.
Now begin to blow the song forward.
Through the orchestra can reach speeds of 200km / h.
You are too slow.
What do you say?
Really, quick for me.
Are you ok?
This can not go on.
Camping here
How, now, lost the tent.
Should we really go this route?
I'm tired of dying.
Does Atlantis really exist?
Today stop here.
Stop the snowstorm and then we'll go back.
No, it's not easy to come here.
Nobita, you obviously did not do anything
That said so.
I still friction it forever.
There are reactions.
Go out.
Look at that.
This reaction is?
Is here.
Yes, the rat explores.
First use this.
How so?
What's up?
It is frozen.
Please save me.
Save me.
Looking at this reaction, below is a city.
OK, if so...
Great.
Can it cause little static?
Sorry.
Please drop me down.
This is an iceberg explorer.
It can crawl down the ice surface several thousand meters deep.
Invite everyone to stabilize the seat, seat belt.
Now.
Start the engine, complete the rotary compass adjustment.
Snow regime.
Are you ready?
What to say?
I'm ready.
Next.
Confirmed coordinates, iceberg explorer expands.
The horizontal axis, no wonder.
The state works well.
Increase 2% of X axis.
3% Y axis reduction.  &nbsp
Look, Nobita.
Ice here...
Just like the sky
Because the bubbles in the ice sheet reflect light
Should create this scene.
This thick Antarctic ice sheet?
It is said that the thickest ice sheet is 4000m.
Beneficial, even higher than Mount Fuji.
It has been so deep and yet to come.
Where is this?
It probably came under the Antarctic ice sheet.
What is that?
What's happen?
Wait for me.
This is...
What is that?
Let's see.
Wait for me, Chai-en.
This is precisely the discovery of the century.
Nobita, you look at the pattern.
Same.
See where this is probably
Where this golden ring is frozen.
Where do we come from?
Around no see the entrance.
Looks like the rope is reacting to this tower.
But that reaction was strong before
Unlike of this tower.
Wait for me!
Are you okay?
This is also fall, it can not bear.
Look, Doraemon!
Both towers are frozen.
Turns out that the ropes look for this thing only.
See that!
Accommodation under the statue.
There is the entrance.
Should we get into the tower from there?
Let me pave the way for everyone.
OK, give this to you.
See me here!
Does this seem to be frozen?
Is there anyone here?
Looks like there is something.
What is the Atlantic repository?
Is a block of ice.
Which have the stars?
Give it to yourself.
What is this pile of hairs?
Anyway, I feel unlike treasures.
It moves.
Mammoth!
Looks are not quite like it!
Is not the Atlantic?
We picked up a gold ring, looking for its owner.
How are you?
Impressive, tickle, tickle
What's wrong?
Looks like he likes Nobita very much.
A bag, take me?
What is this?
Do you know what this is?
Looks like where ever, but where?
It's so cute, so cute! Mau stop!
Now I like to be close to Doraemon.
Nobita! Do you know this one?
Do not know! Was the first time.
Hurry up and see. There are steps leading downwards.
It's dark!
Where are these ladders going?
So use this! Disposable artificial sun.
This artificial sun can glow for 10 minutes.
Looks like there is something.
Come down and see.
Wait!
Wait a minute!
Hurry up Chai-en!
Inside seemed to freeze something.
But the sight here is not the same as the mammoth.
I say this is not...
What's the matter?
How can i...
I, why are you frozen here?
So what is this Doraemon?
The band here is dated 100,000 years ago.
Like the gold ring.
Freeze prediction.
Doremi guess is right.
Wait! I'm not frozen yet.
Melt the ice try to see.
Sometimes this thing is moving.
But this one...
What? Ra is a stone statue?
Why is there a Doraemon statue?
What's the matter? Orino
What are you calling? Orino is a wild boar.
How about the son of the mammoth call?
- Ancient.
- Mammoths that...
Ancient language
Do, Doraemon turn, turn into penguins then.
I'm not a penguin.
Ancient language
What is it ultimately?
Nobita!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Already have! Super speed machine
Ancient language
Doraemon turns into a penguin attacking us.
What did this name just say?
Watch out is very angry.
100 thousand years ago what happened to this place?
Right! We are sitting time machine
Back to the time of 100 thousand years ago the gold ring froze away.
So can know what happened then.
That's right!
Torch! Then lead us to Nobita's room.
I forgot the door of time.
So how here?
No problem, there is another item.
Ring around the time.
Timing is 100,000 years ago.
Hurry up, hold on!
Use this item, although not change the location
But it is possible for us to move to any time.
45 thousand years ago.
50 thousand years ago. 55 thousand years ago.
60 thousand years ago. 65 thousand years ago.
70 thousand years ago .. 75 thousand years ago.
80 thousand years ago .. 85 thousand years ago.
90 thousand years ago. 95 thousand years ago.
100,000 years ago.
Was this 100,000 years ago?
Watch out!
The ice is gone.
The lobster is not seen anymore.
What's happening here next?
Remaining 20%.
Many people move the same
The battery consumes too fast.
It is OK!
In case of trouble, I prepared the battery.
Watch this party!
Opposite the light shining.
Here maybe open.
Why open?
See me here!
What are you doing? Help one go!
It hurts so much!
Where is this?
As a city! Still not frozen.
Great!
We have not reached Antarctica yet.
Strange too!
I miss Antarctica 100,000 years ago
Should have been frozen.
This is not the tower we climb?
The tower hits the clouds always.
So this is an underground city in Antarctica?
Is anyone there?
Atlantic people!
Listen to my voice?
You're careful.
It looks very old here.
Is there anyone here?
Otherwise we go down to see.
Down under see what!
Very dangerous! Can not do that.
Wait for me!
This city does not seem to have anyone.
Where are you going?
Sorry, let's wait a long time.
Mamuski likes to fly too.
Mummy
At him he called Mamu too so I called him Mamuski.
Where is this?
This place seems to be abandoned not so long ago.
What is that black and black thing?
Mom!
What's the matter?
Below there is water flowing.
Which fish there?
Do you hear anything?
Is a bang
Nobita!
Mom!
Where do you want to go?
Friend of Mamuski? Daughter.
Ask..
Ice glaciers
Atlantic, what is he saying?
What's the matter? What happened?
What is that?
Ice glaciers
What does it spray?
Cold water too!
Your legs...
Ice glaciers
Does not seem to be moving.
- Glacial icebergs...
- Wait!
She distracts to save us.
What the hell is that?
Is not squid?
Why Nobita?
Doraemon!
What is this?
Take bread to translate language.
Wait! What happened in the end?
Later and more elaborate.
East, frozen.
Ice glaciers
See? The attack of capital city capital of Chai-en himself.
His multi-attack attack was deadly.
What did you say?
Ice glaciers
Doraemon! Okay?
Of this, eat fast.
Just thank you. Are not you injured?
Why you, why do you know our language?
Chai-en's metropolitan city was destroyed.
That type of attack is not, not effective against the leucocyte
Octopus monster! Does that name have any weaknesses?
That's it... Our sound bullets are gone.
Ammunition sounds? So is it most afraid of sound?
Doraemon!
Okay! Maximum loudspeaker.
Do not! Completely ineffective.
Chai-en! Use this to sing.
Sing! What to do to sing?
That...
Star! You sing fast!
Really! If you guys say that, then...
The whale boy stopped.
It works.
OK!
The leopard who just heard Chai-en I was singing is running.
What does it mean?
I see that it is so touching that we do not want to hit us anymore.
Really! That's it.
Wait a minute!
Who are you guys?
We are...
Bao Bao's welcome dance.
Bao Bao close with the boys, showing that he is not bad people.
What's their name?
This kid seems to be lost. Do you know it?
Astray! It looks like Yutaka's brother.
But ear shape is not very similar.
Really!
Nobita!
Tell you! I'm Nobita!
This is Doraemon and Xu-ka.
I'm Xe-ko.
I'm Chai-en.
My name is Carla! It's called Yutaka.
We came from the planet Hioga Hioga.
I went to this monument to investigate.
Planet Hioga Hioga.
So I thought of the Atlantic.
What about that monster?
It's a monster rock monster! It is the guardian of this place.
Yesterday dropped something into the water.
Today when it came to find it was discovered.
Falling out?
Nobita!
We came here to find the owner of this gold ring.
Gold ring! Where did you find it?
Of course you are, it's good.
Actually, this was discovered in the ice of 100 thousand years later.
100 thousand years later, lies in ice.
We come from the future world of 100,000 years later.
What's wrong?
Do not talk anymore, they are rock bats. We were surrounded.
Rock?
Bat?
That's hurt! It hurts so much!
Do not rob me of my bag! Leave me! Please return me.
Inside my noodles and snacks.
Fine chocolate and my French fries! Return here.
They rob things glow and food.
Everyone hurry inside.
People are not injured?
Where is the yellow circle?
They are robbed.
Okay! Bag for items.
The item may not be at your disposal at any time
From this bag
It is fortunate to have you.
Where?
What's the matter?
Painful pain! That's hurt!
They run.
Okay! If so, this is possible.
Trace badge.
Just have this badge
No matter where they are, we can find them.
They fly into the tower already.
We quickly pursue.
Wait!
It's getting dark! Time to chase too dangerous.
It's dark!
Carla! You okay? What's the situation?
I found the gold ring.
But just recently, the bats were robbed.
Like this! It's getting dark! Come on.
Are you sure you can use your map to find the gold ring?
Of course.
There are guests, come immediately.
Guest?
You guys go back to our base.
Safety overnight.
Waiting for morning and then looking for gold ring.
Can your map lend me a little?
Torch.
This city is only 3 hours a day.
The time it takes to get the light is bright.
Another time is night time.
3 hours.
This place is very cold evening.
Night thunderstorms down to -100 degrees Celsius.
The boys in this way can not stand it.
Volume?
-100 dollar. This is where the devil is?
Our ancient ancestors are the planet Hioga Hioga
This city was built a long time ago.
But now there is no one else.
Things are about to be expelled.
Do not worry!
I accelerate, cling to.
Turns out, is the land vehicle under water?
Watch out!
OK!
We are here Welcome everyone coming.
Here are all friends of Mamuski.
It is our companion.
You come back.
So cute!
Follow me!
Why are you in the tape?
These are all hibernating.
Bao Bao should stay in the ice to rest for some time.
Sleep?
So was the time before Mamuski in the ice is also resting?
Bao Bao in the ice will not grow old
So they lived so long.
Evidence that Bao Bao was discovered
When they freeze in the comet and
Floating in the universe for millions of years.
Up there?
Welcome to our base.
What's wrong?
What are you talking about? Welcome to our base.
Doctor! Uncle Xabaru's clothes
Running to study?
Obviously, he told me to stay still and wait.
This is...
Uncle specify the search in the monument.
Do not you like that?
Really... Who told you that the injury was not hurt?
Doctor!
I watch! Now no pain anymore.
Right! Rarely have visitors come,
Tonight to celebrate.
Really?
Recently eat every day.
Everyone happy yet?
This evening everyone invited to party! There are also pudding bombs.
Bom?
Pudding stars?
Everyone goes to wash.
God
Toothpick!
I told my mother to go home before dinner.
Yes! My mother treats me again.
No problem! Wait after the deal is over
We use the time machine back that night.
What's the smell?
Torch.
To steal this one is all right. Wait a little longer.
Torch!
Wait a long time
We eat only
Delicious!
It's so delicous!
The cheese is just soft as candy.
Reminds me of the 5 star restaurant in Paris.
What?
Children from the next 100,000 years?
Especially to bring the gold ring for us.
Planet Hioga Hioga is where this?
The planet Hioga Hioga is 100 thousand light years away.
Look at the other picture.
A white planet cleared.
Previously this planet was blue but
Now all frozen.
Are all planets frozen?
It's in the ice giant.
Giant ice?
This story is long.
Our ancestors are Planet Hioga Hioga
Have advanced science
Can be considered as the head of the galaxy.
Now these techniques are lost.
We can not inherit these techniques.
This is an insecticide caught in the monument.
But outside it is like insects, but
In fact, it is all due to the techniques of the ancients.
Is the same type as the whitetop monster?
Before
We have studied a lot of ancestors left
Developing that incredibly amazing technique.
But one day,
We do not carefully open the gate should not open.
Is a giant ice.
The strongest rock statue.
They are not something we can handle.
Everyone left the planet
We are not committed to leaving
Seeking to seal the ice giant.
Go through a long journey
Finally to this planet.
Find a gold ring of potential energy.
So is the item so important?
We have to rob it about.
Yes!
Why did the ancients create such terrible things?
How does that happen on Earth?
Because if any planet has life
They can use it to freeze their own way.
Freeze stars?
How do not you lose your life?
Not.
Planet only temporarily frozen.
After the ice melts.
That planet would have a terrible shredding.
Is it the ice age?
Say so
Is that all the time the earth is covered by snow?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Does the past of the earth have the same situation?
In roughly 600 million years,
Earth as well as planet Hioga Hioga
Also freeze white.
This situation lasts hundreds of thousands of years.
But after the ice melts not long
Earth life has great evolution.
As far as I know it is called the Cambrian explosion.
Most of the creatures at that time were primitive
And appear at the same time
So,
Are we present thanks to the ancients?
But the giant ice statue appears
When all are in an unfinished state.
I feel the planet is frozen
Most likely not related to our ancestors.
Meaning things are very wrong right?
That's it.
You do not understand anything.
Do not worry!
There are only monsters
Chai-en here will treat them neatly.
Is this also an ancient man?
That is the robot we bought on the planet Bonumera.
I hit the back button.
Very subtle.
The eye can also glow.
There is also this.
This eye can glow.
Eat some sweets.
This is a nail.
Heroes fight monsters
No matter how many times we brushed
He did not give up
Late game
Want to eat too
Too tight
This car can not hold.
Leave them too pitiful.
From yesterday until now not moving.
Inside is their lair.
The bunk of the bat rock.
Maybe maybe something interesting.
Uncle watch
Your feet are not lost
Stay here for us
But we have to use the machine Capture precious documents.
I told you to drop me down!
We'll be back soon!
The shooting job is for us!
What a way out.
What's going on?
Storehouse of ice giants?
Obviously, during the day,
Why gather so many snowflakes?
Look!
Must it climb so high?
That's it!
We're up!
Wait.
We do not know what will happen next.
To prevent any inconvenience, please use these insights to protect yourself!
Okay, let's go!
Everyone, follow me!
What's wrong?
I feel like there's somebody here.
We are near
Where are the Nobitas?
Where did you go?
How are you
It seems they are already lost.
No way, use this!
The trinket hunts.
It will tell us the location of the target.
Where is the yellow circle?
It does not know exactly anymore.
Is this party.
Accuracy is only 70%.
Looks out can not rely on it to find it.
You said the tru?ng tree look like it will be sad!
In short look to see.
Still have to climb?
Of course, hurry!
Stone, is it stone?
Come on, let's go!
It is all the springs are sprinkled on, delicious!
What are you eating?
Nor is it something to eat.
Your Earthmates,
Not so much to the ice giants eat it too?
Right! What is the giant of the ice?
A giant made of ice.
I only saw one close at close range.
They know how to absorb ice.
Then bigger and bigger.
Giant ice!
I go to inform everyone.
That day, our city was frozen like that!
But just get the gold ring that is okay.
It can make a giant Ice back into ice piles.
Torch! So I'll give you siro.
What is delicious?
That's hurt!
Where is Doraemon?
Where?
Nobita, this party!
I know.
You go before that!
This is the cave of the rock fall.
These are the items they collect.
Is not that Suneo and Chaien's bookbag?
Anyhow...
Found, the gold ring!
Who are you? Dare to be so big liver?
Dare to move on my belongings.
Who are you?
What's going on?
The body of the ice giant is recovering.
Shizuka
Probably in the near future!
You're too slow!
Doraemon
What is this
No good
Where are the Nobitas?
Torch!
Where do we go
Doraemon
Nobita, you know?
This side, this side
Machine locates here!
Really?
What is the end of it?
Must fall down from above.
The golden ring is definitely up there.
Do you hear anything?
No, not hear anything.
Nobita!
In the end, where does it want to take them?
As a trap, it is going to kill them!
Nobita!
Have to think of a way to let them know!
Now you need the security now, give yourself away!
Wait!
Do not let him cheat!
That name is fake.
There are these two Doraemon!
What's going on?
Hateful!
I'm the real Doraemon.
No, I'm real!
Which name is the fake name?
Let me handle him.
Look at the other Doraemon!
His bell and magical bag made of ice.
That's it!
Real doraemon
You will be able to get the money back from the magic bag, get it!
No problem.
You guys go watch!
Correct.
That's the Doraemon insignia.
Say so,
That name is fake.
Not that.
His magic bag is stolen.
That's true!
This is also likely that!
Yes, see who you can say my name right.
There is also my name.
That's too simple!
Bottle...
What's going on?
It does not seem to speak.
As Chaien and Suneo.
I said that.
That name is definitely fake.
That fake name!
I will destroy you!
P! P!
Where did that name come from?
E the truth is hidden in the stone tower.
So what to do?
Use the speedy flashlight to freeze him.
Looks like it is extremely angry.
Let us see your true face, fake.
I see that he is really pitiful!
Still not possible now Surely he is a fake.
What are you saying?
Bells and bags are made of ice,
Can not say our name.
But...
Okay, I know.
Let him decide to go!
Right!
You are the one who understands Doraemon most Nobita!
I'm?
Nobita, be careful little!
I see that both of them are real!
What are you talking about? There is no such thing!
OK! Please freeze that name again!
Do not!
He quickly avoided it.
Carla!
Although the bell and the magic bag are not the same,
But I see that he is real!
Do not say your names well,
Doraemon is Doraemon!
Nobita!
What are you kidding
What are you talking about?
Give it to me!
What are you doing?
Nobita!
Doraemon!
When you were first saved me.
Thank you!
That was so dangerous.
If he saved Nobita, then proved...
The other side is a fake!
Freeze it!
Finally say it!
Stay away!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Stop me!
It wants to harm us being stabbed by the bandit.
May have Doraemon save us.
That's right, this place!
Is not that where our journey begins this time?
The true face of the fake name,
It is the penguin.
So keep it freezing here!
Dare say so
100,000 years later did not you release it yourself?
Is that so?
So now I have to give it a new match.
Doing so will change that history.
Just freeze it like that.
May have you, helped us.
Doraemon!
I really apologized to you!
We are not good.
No problem, no other way.
What about the gold ring?
Side.
It's about Doraemon.
What is...
This is not...
Gold ring!
That guy put the gold ring in his magic pocket.
Carla!
Take it!
Thanks, thank you everyone!
What's going on?
No or it's late!
Doctor, we got the gold ring!
Very good!
But definitely have to return the gold ring for the ice giant.
Return?
This ice giant, completely unfinished.
That was soon completed.
But before the soul was liberated it was sealed.
As we did not carefully release the seal!
What is it?
So on,
The planet will freeze it!
How can?
Look over there!
The ice giant is slowly awakening.
Carla!
Now there is still time,
Definitely have to return the gold ring!
If now returned, the gold ring will be how?
Not clear, but no time to hesitate!
But without this golden ring,
Can not solve snow and ice for all the planets!
What are you talking about?
The Earth is about to turn into a snowball?
Is that right?
But...
This is the gold ring!
No, not in time!
There are many holes in the sky!
That is...
Giant ice!
He's awake!
Obnoxious! I will not let it freeze the earth.
No, it will be lost.
Everyone hurry into the tower, hurry up!
Dare to do that? What's going on?
Its ears...
Give your bag, inside with medicine.
Do not worried. At this level, healing quickly.
Doctor.
I have to go back to base, Paopao is okay.
Now we are back to base.
Do not. Now it's too dangerous.
The whole city is frozen.
Mau withdraw.
What should I do? It's getting dark.
Right. Use lumbar time away. Everyone hurry up.
What are you going to do?
We will now reach ten thousand years later to avoid accidents.
Everyone is firmly attached.
Doraemon!
Nobita!
That's hurt.
Is this place ten thousand years later?
People wait.
I have to bring Yukatan and Doraemon here.
0% left.
Low battery.
Why not?
The screen does not light up anymore.
Are we now under the Antarctic ice sheet?
Are we guys stuck here forever?
After all, Carla and the others should not come here.
Yes. It is all in you
So now it's like this.
I...
You think of a way, Carla.
Do not do that.
Carla and everyone just want to save their planet only.
They also have no way.
Nobita.
Yes. You two do not do that.
Obnoxious!
Why did you hit me?
Mommy!
So cold. It does not seem to work.
Doraemi's prediction is fulfilled.
The waist of time is also out of battery.
Continuing this I will also be frozen.
That's right. I can not easily give up.
Nobita needs care later.
Just bring your spare battery of the waist time
To ten thousand years later...
Looks like to see where.
Arrived. Up top
Paopao you just need to be in the ice to be able to hibernate.
If you can not escape, at least you can live on.
Even though I'm a high-end person, I can not hibernate.
Hibernate? Wait. This battery department...
Your lucky thing is the star.
Right. I got it.
The widgets can Can you use only that much?
Up to the top, you will probably find a car tuner.
But it was broken.
Are these enough for us to save people?
This is the battery of the waist time.
Where is the feeling?
Mosuke, is your bag still here?
Where is that bag?
This bag was frozen with Mosuke.
That is the doctor's bag.
Probably Yukatan wearing that bag.
Speak well to say back,
Why did Mosuke hibernate here?
Do you know what this is about?
Mosuke, Yukatan...
For me
Looks like already seen. But where is it?
When I felt soft hair, I called it Mosuke.
What is that?
Doraemon!
I knew. That's how is it.
My dear, I can go save Doraemon.
What's going on?
It is safe in the ice.
Yukatan, bring this to Nobita.
Why does this bag have batteries?
It was Doraemon who gave it to Mosuke.
Get started.
But where did Mosuke come from?
Mosuke is Yukatan being Doraemon
Frozen for hibernation ten thousand years ago.
You say Mosuke is Yukatan?
Incorrect. It must be said that Yukatan is Mosuke.
But the colors are not the same.
Maybe during hibernation its coat color has turned blue.
We go here Returning to ten thousand years ago.
But how are you going to deal with the monster?
Yes. Must handle that name already.
How to handle it?
We have a gold ring.
Use this ring to seal the other guy.
Would not that be Carla?
I can not save the planet Hyogahyoga
But leave your planet frozen.
Carla.
Torch. Let's go.
How to reach the monster?
Give it to yourself. I have a good way.
I knew. In short, it is okay.
Everyone is ready?
We're off
Save our Earth!
Chong bamboo is also lost.
It's dead
It's Jaian and Suneo!
Jaian, turn left.
Doing so can enclose it, so it slows down.
Brain!
This side
Pin arrived.
Nobita! Shizuka!
You guys are coming.
Brizzaga is controlled by Jainan.
We have to endure time.
Ready? We make war on schedule.
Come here.
This side
Sponge nozzle
Do not let you escape so easily.
Good job.
What's up?
It grows wings.
This has not been mentioned before.
Foam sprays are also useless.
That name...
Pierced through the arched porch straight to the ground.
Hurry up.
Everyone hid behind me.
Suneo!
Even shields also...
I... I can not stand it.
Look across.
Its movement slows down.
That is...
Doraemon.
I use the automatic wallet in the lake to come here
So that is.
Its body is made of ice.
Meeting water will weaken.
Nobita, time is here!
We burst out, Carla!
Carla!
The light fades away.
Great.
This side
Torch.
Found it, Jaian.
Also noodle package I like to eat the most.
His high-profile chocolates.
Jaian, look at that.
These rings are supposed to be...
Sorry, Carla.
No problem.
I can go to other planets looking for.
Carla!
The universe is very large.
I will definitely find out
Right. Jaian and Suneo where?
Looks like they...
Where are you going?
People look at this.
We found in the bat's den.
They are all collected by them.
Gold ring.
This is...
These things are very valuable research.
Not yet able to save the planet Hyoga Hyoga.
That's good, Carla.
Thank you, Nobita.
Thank you guys.
I brought the children to the ground.
People pick up the car.
Letting Yukatan be like that?
It is OK.
Ten thousand years later you will wake it up.
Ten thousand years?
To them it is just a nap.
Good evening to you. [Ten thousand years - one week later]
Promotion activities are about to begin.
Really?
Strong healthy trend is very...
After several hot days,
Tomorrow will begin to welcome fresh air.
Nobita!
What are you doing?
I'm watching the celestial body.
The doctor told me coordinates Of Hyoga Hyoga planet.
I looked at the standard.
This planet is about ten thousand light years away.
So now we can See it of ten thousand years ago.
Is this Hyoga Hyoga?
White is good. It's frozen.
You look closely.
See it.
The tape starts melting.
Probably the doctor's research has been successful.
That's good, Carla.
Finally it was already cool.
Summer is about to end?
Nobita, Doraemon!
Let's eat.
Yes.