To those who loved this world...
...and knew friendly company therein:
This Reunion is for you.
498 Years Earlier
Why did humankind even bothered.
You rack everything you've ever made, and start over.
Like there'll be any different after that.
I supposed we're not good at facing our memories,
We'd rather kill the past .
Find something worthwile among the rubble
and build the future with that.
And that's the reason why you hide Mother?
To kill the past?
We were trying to rid ourselves
of a more immediate problem.
You don't mean the stigma?
But you're the one who brought
that on yourself in the first place.
I see.
I guess you really do have a short memory.
No, not me.
You see, it is my choice to forget.
2 Weeks Ago
Tseng! Look at this.
Hm?
Found it.
Not a pretty sight, is it?
Who cares?
Just get the damn thing.
Reno, I'm counting on you.
You got it.
Whoa!
Senpai, hurry!
Senpai!
Who the hell is that?
Elena!
Go! Get out!
Tseng-san!
You are going to give her back eventually.
The Lifestream.
That's what we call the river of life
that circles our planet...
... giving life to the world
and everything in it.
The Shinra Electric Power Company
discovered a way...
... to use the Lifestream
as an energy source.
Because of Shinra's energy, we were
able to live very comfortable lives.
But wasn't that because we were
taking away from the planet's life?
A lot of people thought so.
Shinra used their power to try and
stop anybody who got in their way.
Shinra had a special group
of warriors called SOLDIER.
And all the SOLDIERs
had Jenova cells put inside them.
Jenova was a calamity that fell
from the sky a long, long time ago...
... and tried to destroy the planet.
Anyway, there was one SOLDIER
named Sephiroth...
... who was better than the rest.
But when he found out about the
terrible experiments that made him...
... he began to hate Shinra.
And then, over time,
he began to hate everything.
Shinra and the people against them.
Sephiroth, who hated
the planet so much...
... he wanted to make it go away.
And the people who tried to stop him.
There were a lot of battles.
For every battle,
there was more sadness.
Someone I love went back
to the Lifestream too.
And then, it came.
The chosen day.
In the end, the planet itself had to
make the battles stop for good.
The planet used the Lifestream
as a weapon...
... and when it burst out
of the earth...
... all the fighting,
all the greed and sadness...
... everything was washed away.
"Sadness was the price
to see it end. "
It's been two years
since they told me that.
Move it, move it.
Whoa.
Sis, let's go.
Yeah.
But it looks like the planet
is a lot angrier than we thought.
They call it geostigma.
Well, Marlene?
How does it look?
Please. Please don't
take Denzel away.
"The commission report release this
morning has reveal"
"That lifestream concentration at the atmosphere"
"Has been drop to a mere
hundred of a levels 2 years ago."
"However, the concentration remains toxic"
"Around the Shinra Company main building
as well as the company's mako reactors."
He's not here anymore.
"To prevent the onset of Geostigma"
"The commission does advice that you
stay away from these facilities"
"And the surrounding areas."
"Next up. Should Shinra be held
financial responsible for the crisis?"
Cloud, where is he now?
Strife Delivery Service.
You name it, we ship...
May I ask who's calling?
Yeah, I remember you.
You got a call from Reno.
He's in Healin.
Says he's got work for you.
Cloud, how have you been?
You have no more messages...
Hey, Kadaj?
Is that where Big Brother lives?
Yeah.
Think he'll be happy to see us?
- Not a chance.
- Don't cry, Yazoo.
But Mother's with him?
Maybe not.
Oh, don't cry, Loz.
Look, here he comes.
Where's Mother?
We know you hid her, Brother.
Don't tell me you're leading me on?
Because I think
you do have Mother there.
No need to shout.
Put the president on.
You're starting to bother me.
Don't run away.
Hey, it's me, Barret!
I did it! A new oil field!
O-IL-FIELD!
A huge one, too!
And we're sticking to plan, so soon
I'll be able to come visit Marlene!
Tell her for me!
See ya!
Reno called again.
He says to hurry,
but he sounded kind of strange...
Be careful, okay?
Okay, so you're good.
Yeah, Rude, looking sharp!
Just as expected
from an ex-SOLDIER.
You haven't rusted a bit.
Is that you, Rufus?
You've got no luck either...
- The day of the explosion...
- What do you want?
...I managed to get out...
- Who were the guys that attacked me?
...before it colla...
- I'm leaving.
We need your assistance.
- Not interest...
- I acknowledge that Shinra...
...owes the planet a lot.
It goes without saying
that my company and I...
...are the ones who put
the world in the sorry state it's in.
So we feel we have a responsibility
to set things right.
I'm still out here!
We've already taken the first step...
...by conducting an investigation
in Sephiroth's wake.
It's been 2 years, now that that the
world is on the speed again, what's the threat now?
Well, that one's easy, Geostigma.
And we have to think Sephiroth is the one responsible.
The people blame Mako energy, Mako reactors,
even the Lifestream for causing the stigma
However, isn't it wrong
to put a blame on it?
The Lifestream existed as long as the Planet and even
Mako evergy has been part of our life for 40 years.
And yet there's no mention about
stigma in recorded history.
So, what happen during our time
to change all that?
I can only think of one thing.
Sephiroth's awaken.
Sephiroth is dead.
Of course, but what about
his mind?
What if somehow he dissolve into the
Lifestream coursing with the Planet undiffuse.
I know, it's merely my speculation.
But, there are possibilities right?
And we can't cure the
stigma until we know the truth.
So we took the first step,
and went to look for traces of Sephiroth.
Do you by any chance,
still remember where is it?
At the Northern Cave!
What do you think we found?
We didn't find anything. You can relax.
However, not all went as planned.
We were interrupted.
It was the three who attacked you.
Tseng-san!
Kadaj's gang.
Kadaj?
Really, what could they be thinking?
What does that have to do with me?
You are going to give her back eventually.
Your ties with Sephiroth run
as deep as our too Cloud.
And if Kadaj’s goal is to prepare
for an imminent occasion
We should be prepared
for the upcoming threat.
Prepare?
Sephiroth...
...resurrection.
Are you done talking?
Let's get things clear.
In order to battle with Kadaj,
we need someone with your expertise.
Will you join us?
SOLDIER member, Cloud.
Former.
What's this stuff about 'Mother'?
Beats me. Didn't Kadaj mention
anything to you?
Rufus.
Are you hiding something from me?
I never keep a secret,
especially from a comrade.
I'm sure you wanted to learn
more about the stigma?
Obviously for the sake of
those orphan you live with.
Don't you want to see the
smile of the children?
Think about it. Don't you want
to put smiles back on their faces?
All we want in the end
is to rebuild our world, Cloud.
- But I...
- Come on, Cloud.
Together, we can rebuild Shinra!
Not interested.
- Reno!
Does Cloud live here?
I guess he does.
What's this?
It's just like Denzel. Is Cloud sick?
Why didn't he just say something?
Did he leave because he's sick?
He wants to fight alone.
- Fight?
- No.
I don't think he will.
Tifa?
Let's go back, Marlene?
No! I wanna see Cloud!
...I guess you're right.
- It'd be nice to see him, huh?
- Yeah.
Hey, what should we do when he gets here?
We'll all go home!
Before that, we'll lecture him!
Agreed!
Now we just have to find Tseng and Elena.
The other employees give you any leads?
Nothing yet.
Who have thought, Shinra's employee return to work.
Now that's dedicate.
I'm telling you this going to be a fresh start.
Well, those who alive have a lot to atone for.
It's been 2 years already, right?
It seems a lot longer than that.
What a nightmare huh?
The world was almost done for.
And we're a part of it.
Seriously though,
how we're supposed to atone for that?
Too bad the directors not around.
Elena too.
I hope they're still alive.
It's alright.
Tseng is just like the President.
They always escape from the death god.
I'm sure of that.
You got that right.
Found you.
Church?
Ah, I know that one.
I'll be waiting.
Your call to Sector 7 cannot be reached at the moment.
Cloud, you rarely call back
aren't you?
Anything happen?
Cloud?
No it's not.
Who's this?
Isn't this Cloud's phone?
I don't know.
Who are you?
I don't know. Please, I don't know
what to do, I can't do this.
Are you crying?
What happen?
Are you okay?
- Cloud! Cloud!
- Where are you?
Oi!
Are you alright?
I hate liars.
I apologize.
This time you'll get the truth.
The object you seek fell from the helicopter
while we were running from you.
What a ridiculous story.
Is that right?
I swear it.
Then swear on these.
- Why are you doing this?
- We need Mother's power.
The Reunion is coming
and we need her.
Reunion?
My brothers and sisters who share
Mother's cells will all assemble.
And together, we'll take revenge
on the planet.
We've already sent out the invitations,
but you know.
Someone's gone and hidden
the guest of honor.
Invitations?
The stigma.
But you know all about that.
Mother's memetic legacy lives on in
the Lifestream and makes it happen.
She does so much for us, and we
don't even know where to find her.
But what can we do, we're just
remnants of Mother's legacy.
Until we find Mother and receive
her cells, we can't be whole again.
Geostigma and a legacy
aren't enough.
Not for a true Reunion.
What do you mean?
Mr. President, surely you've noticed?
Sorry, sorry.
The stigma!
Can't you people just stay indoors?
Here.
I said I'd live out both our lives.
Easier said than done.
You wanna be in SOLDIER?
Hang in there!
Hey, how're you doing?
What're you gonna do
once we get to Midgar?
We're friends, right?
Old man, stop somewhere behind a rock.
Cloud, we’re getting off!
My dreams and pride...
...You can have them all.
You're...
...the proof that I existed.
On that day,
I swore I'll never forget.
But, I...
Don't pretend you're sad.
Why tremble with anger that's not even there.
Do you know why, Cloud?
All you are, is an empty puppet.
Wanna play?
I guess that's a no.
Where's Mother?
It stinks.
- Hey, where's Mother?
- There's no one here!
Fine. Play with me.
This'll be fun.
Tifa!
She's not here.
I'm not crying!
Got it. I'll bring it.
Time to finish this.
Cloud!
Run!
About earlier, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
My brother...
Isn't around anymore.
I see.
You've got the stigma too?
Come on, they're gonna fix us.
Tifa?
Tifa!
You're late...
Who did this?
He didn't say.
Marlene?!
No...
You're pretty heavy.
You were living with some kids, right?
They ain't here.
Is that okay with you?
I...
You're a real handful.
Tifa said to take you home, kid.
Hold on tight.
Who are these people
that's going to fix us?
I don't know.
Anyone is fine.
So Big Brother was hiding it.
This is the power of the Lifestream.
This materia will give us
renewed power.
So, those were a gift from Mother?
Yea, it should be.
Then, Brother is hiding Mother too?
No. It's that President guy.
Keeping things hidden is something
Shinra's people are very good at
Then we have to look everywhere
that have to do with Shinra.
Pretty soon, we'll have plenty of helps.
This is fun!
But first.
We need to have a talk with Brother.
He likes to pretend as if he's
not a part of the family.
He makes me sad, really sad.
Right?
Reno and Rude are looking.
You have geostigma, don't you.
So it's okay to just give up and die.
Is that what you think?
It knew it.
There's no cure.
That's not stopping Denzel
from fighting.
Don't run. Let's fight it together.
We can help each other,
I know we can.
Or do we have to be a real family
for that to work?
I...
...am not fit to help anyone.
Not my family, not my friends.
No one.
Dilly-dally, shilly-shally...
I think she wants you
to move on.
Did you find them?
Only a witness.
Saw them being taken away.
- Where are they?
- The Forgotten City.
Their base.
I've received a special power from Mother.
The power to fight...
...against a planet
that torments its people.
She gave this power to all her children.
That's right.
You and I are brethren.
Brothers and sisters chosen...
...when we inherited Mother's memetic
legacy through the Lifestream.
But...
...the planet doesn't like that.
It's trying to hold us back.
That's why it's been racking our bodies
with pain, filling our hearts with doubt!
I will heal you.
Then we will go to Mother.
We will join as a family
and strike back at the planet!
Do as I do.
Denzel.
Denzel!
Mother, look.
All my new siblings.
They will keep me company
until I found you.
You came.
Even though you're about to break.
That's a good sign.
I wanna ask something!
Why exactly did you come here for?
I think I want to be forgiven...
Yes, I want to be forgiven.
By who?
Glad you could make it.
I'm here for the kids.
See this man? He's our big brother.
But you know,
It's a shame...
He's a traitor.
Cloud!
I really can't save anyone, right?
Vincent. What do you know
about this?
I come here often.
I've seen what Kadaj's group
is doing.
The stigma.
Inside our bodies, we all have
a current like the Lifestream.
When alien matter infests the body,
this current is what fights it off.
There's a flow through the body like the Lifestream...
It fights against the invasion of harmful substances.
Harmful substances...
The Sephiroth gene.
Jenova's memetic legacy.
Call it what you want.
You're well-informed.
Tseng and Elena.
They were brought here half-dead.
They must have been
brutally tortured.
I did what I could to save them...
...but it was ugly.
Tortured?
They had it coming.
They got their hands
on Jenova's head.
Then the "Mother"
Kadaj is looking for...
Heaven's dark harbinger.
The calamity, Jenova.
If they wanted to,
they could make another Sephiroth.
Kadaj...
What is he?
I'd rather not know.
Marlene!
Cloud! Denzel and Tifa!
Tifa is all right.
I wanna talk to her!
Do you have it?
I can't believe it!
Vincent, will you take Marlene
back to the bar?
I'm gonna go get some answers
from Shinra.
- You know I can't.
- But...
Cloud, that's enough!
Why won't you listen to what we're trying to say?
Marlene, please give me some time.
There's a battle to be fought...
...but it's not as simple
as just fighting it. You understand, right?
No, I don't!
Cloud, is this really about the fight?
Where are they?
The Forgotten City.
Ajit.
Please take care of it.
- I have to talk to Rufus.
- Stop running!
I know.
Even if you find the kids,
you might not be able to help them.
Maybe something will happen
that can never unhappen.
That scares you, doesn't it?
But you need to think about now.
Take it in.
You think you've got it hard? Tough.
Sharing your life
with other people is hard.
I know you don't want to be alone.
You might not answer the phone,
but you won't throw it away either.
Why don't you just go to Ajit.
Why do we have to lose out
to our memory?
But I let you die.
Really, you're always drifting...
Cloud, why can't you
forgive yourself?
Are sins ever forgiven?
I've never tried.
Tried it?
Tried it...
Marlene, let's go home.
I'm gonna try.
I'll let you know how it goes.
It's me, Reeve.
How's work going?
I saw your flyer. How the hell
do you stay in business?
You never change, Cloud.
I was thinking about helping you out,
but I guess I'll call back another time.
- Later.
- Surprise! It's me, Yuffie.
So, hey, all the kids
are missing from Wutai.
Have you heard anything?
Give me a ring and fill me in, okay?
I never blamed you, not once.
You came for me.
That's all that matters.
- Hey, are you listening?
- Why the hell are you doing this?
Denzel?
Denzel. Denzel!
And what are we up to?
Mother's here, isn't she?
How do you figure?
This, what you call it?
Monument.
I bet Shinra made it.
Wow, you used your head, didn't you?
Am I wrong?
Who knows.
We don't know anything about it either.
I see, as if anyone would trust you.
Rude!
Say something!
Does it hurt?
Yea.
But, not as bad as Denzel's.
Can it be cure?
I don't know.
For Denzel's sake, you've been trying
so hard to find a cure for it.
You knew about that?
Cloud, you should clean-up your desk sometimes.
I guess so.
Say Cloud, because you can't fix Denzel's stigma,
is that the reason why you left?
Or is it because you had the stigma too?
I just thought I could take care for myself.
That's what I think.
How can you look after your family if you can't
even take a good care of yourself.
Or, at least that is what daddy would say.
Cloud, don't give up.
You, and Denzel, and Tifa always
be there to help me.
You're always there whenever I needed you.
For now, it's my turn.
Sure.
Say, Kadaj.
I've got a question for you.
Just one question then.
You said you needed Jenova cells
in order to return to what you were.
What does that mean?
He's coming back.
Sephiroth.
The nightmare.
So they say.
You mean...
I don't know Sephiroth.
But I know he's close.
It gets under my skin.
What if Mother loves him
more than..?
Poor little remnants.
It doesn't matter.
You'll meet the same fate either way!
Mother came to this planet
after a long journey.
To rid the cosmos of fools like you.
But you know about it as well.
Nothing's changed
since Mother came here.
I have to change it.
To make her happy.
There's nothing I wouldn't do,
if she only asked.
Hmph, the nightmare comes again, huh?
As long as you exist, the nightmares
will come again and again.
The Lifestream
courses through our planet...
... back and forth across
the borders of life and death.
If that cycle is the very truth of life...
... then history, too,
will inevitably repeat itself.
So go on, bring your Jenovas
and your Sephiroths.
It won't matter.
We'll do as life dictates...
... and stop you every single time.
Mr. President, is that an excuse
for taking Mother?
Don't tell me
you're feeling remorse?
Remorse?
Why, I've never had this much fun.
Glad to hear that.
Now let's put
an end to all this.
Denzel, we've got to get away!
This is...
Is it coming after us?
Why don't you go ask it?
Having fun yet?
Not at all!
Can't you guys just call it a day?!
We will.
If you give back Mother,
that'll be the end of everything.
Damned punks...
...what do you need
Jenova's head for?
Forget your little Reunion
and get a grip!
All we want is to be with Mother!
Mother will know what's best.
She'll tell us what to do.
Now, where is she?
Mother, mother.
It's Jenova's frigging head!
- Hey!
- Don't talk about Mother like that.
Unforgiven!
We're sorry...
That's right...
Wait, why are we apologizing?
Tifa?
Bastard!
You look after Mom.
Barret!
Marlene's safe, right? Huh?
I can't match this!
Who's using my materia?!
The bad guys, naturally.
Dammit!
Who's that?
The latest model, Sierra!
I'll let you ride it later!
Where's the phone shop?
Who's that person?
These are our friends.
Denzel, can you make it to the bar?
Enough!
Tifa!
Denzel!
Cloud!
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
It's alright.
Are you alright?
Marlene's safe. I took her home.
It feels a little lighter.
Maybe I wore it down by dragging it along so much.
I'm going back to the bar.
I'll be waiting with Marlene.
You're gonna come home,
right, Cloud?
I can do this!
You're late dammit!
Isn't this fun Boss?
What should we summon next?
- Mother?
- A good son would have known.
Go, Cloud!
Haiya!
Fly!
It's not over yet!
Here!
Mother!
- Boss!
Boss!
You mess up with the wrong guy.
Rude!
This is bad! This is bad!
This is bad yo!
Ooh, Rude.
You're alright.
Yea.
I'm just peachy.
Senpai!
Hey, partner.
This thing got any bite?
Shinra technology at its finest.
Oh, so you made this.
I don't know about the power, but it sure is flashy.
Oh-hoh!
You like that, don't you, partner?
No overtime tonight, eh?
Mother!
Mother...
Let's go, Cloud.
I've finally found Mother.
So, what happens now?
Mother will tell me, you'll see.
I guess a remnanets won't know anything.
So what if I'm a puppet.
You used to be no different!
Cloud, I brought you materia!
- Don't shake it!
- Yo, Cid! Land this junk heap.
Shut up! You want off, you jump!
Let them fight by themselves.
Kadaj is an avatar of Sephiroth.
Think of him as
a sort of larval form.
Larva? You mean
he's some kinda insect?
Calm down, Princess!
So that punk's gonna
become Sephiroth?
Wait, Cloud, does he know that?
Probably.
I see.
Let's leave them alone.
I don't get it!
Someone explain it to me!
This is man talk.
Sexist. Sexist!
Will you calm down, Princess!?
Some of the men
ain't following either.
Two years ago...
During our last battle
...do you remember
what it was like to be strong?
It's only been two years...
...but somehow that strength
has slipped away.
I think Cloud's found it
again though.
I'll give him 10 minutes.
Always a pain in the ass, that Cloud.
At least he's honest.
I'll show you my Reunion.
It's been a while, Cloud.
Your stigma is gone?
How unfortunate.
Just what do you really want?
The ghosts of geostigma victims.
They will rejoin the Lifestream
and circle the planet...
Eventually it infringes on the planet...
What I really want, Cloud...
...is to sail the darkness of the cosmos
with this planet as my vessel...
...just as my mother did long ago.
Then one day we'll find
a new planet...
...and on its soil we'll create
a shining future.
What will happen to this planet?
Well, that's up to you to decide.
Sister?
Where did you find this strength?
I don't feel like telling you.
I've thought of
a wonderful present for you.
Shall I give you despair?
Kneel. Beg for forgiveness.
Is this the pain you felt before, Cloud?
Let me remind you again,
And this time, engraved into your memory.
What do you treasure most?
I want the joy of taking it from you.
So, what if they look hopeless?
If it were me, I still
wouldn't give up.
Embrace your dreams.
Also, whatever happen protect your
honor as a SOLDIER.
You never made as a SOLDIER.
But it's the feeling that count, the feeling.
Zacks.
Well, do you need a help there?
You already beat him once didn't you?
This should be an easy one, right?
Yea.
Never forget.
I am...
...the proof that you existed.
How sad.
You who understand nothing.
There is nothing I don't treasure!
Stay in my memories
where you belong.
I will never be a memory.
Brother...
Kadaj?
You can let it go now, if you want.
Mother, is that you?
Everyone's waiting,
if you're ready to go.
He did it!
That's how it goes!
A man!
Cloud-san's a man!
See? Just like I told you.
He can do anything if he puts his mind to it.
Hold on tight, you guys!
You were always with us, weren't you?
Thank you.
Let's all go home together.
And play with everyone...
Cloud!
Cloud said he'd come home.
Let's go.
Mom?
Why does everyone
keep calling me that?
I guess they must be fond of you.
I think this one's outgrown me.
Tough luck, friend.
Looks like your place isn't here.
She said to wait here for Cloud.
Welcome home.
Im home.
There are still children
with the stigma.
Okay, it's time to get fixed up.
It's okay.
Be strong.
- Last one in is a rotten egg!
- It worked, it worked!
You're all right now, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'm not alone.
And all my hopes and dreams
Aren't for anyone
I keep them safe and sound
And hope this picture is
Not yours anymore
But can you hear me now?
Now that’s okay man
I’ll say it across this land,
You should’ve kissed me baby
So try and stop me
Or so forgive this light
Cuz I can’t beg all night
Until my heart stops beating
You’ll never hear me say
I won’t kiss you
If I say,
Its lost its beating
If I can’t find my way
It’s over now
That I won’t
Break away
Until the day
(Whoa, whoa)
I’m never backing down
And hear me say
(Whoa, whoa)
I’ll keep it safe and sound
I’ll keep it safe and…
This hopeless feeling
This fear of falling down
But I’m not crashing now
For all this bleeding
It wasn’t worth the sound
A million screaming out loud
And still
The earth comes reeling
The curtain calls my name
I’m not afraid
And I know
You may not miss me
But I am not ashamed
The choice I made
But I can
Let this go
Until the day
(Whoa, whoa)
I’m never backing down
Just hear me say
(Whoa, whoa)
I’ll keep it safe and sound
I’ll keep it safe and…
No dashing car
Or a dying star
That’s raced into the ground
Like the final words
Of the passengers
Will the angels give it all?
Will the world
Watch us burn?
Until the day
(Whoa, whoa)
I’m never backing down
Just hear me say
(Whoa, whoa)
I’ll keep it safe and sound
Keep it safe and sound
(Whoa, whoa)
Whose grave is this?
No.
This is where the 'hero' began his journey.
Subtitle by k3rry86