Subtitles by explosiveskull
Captain Sakaki, please reply. We can communicate.
My demand is to leave the planet Tau-e immediately,
and abandon the project migration.
Until I hear from Captain, I'm not moving from here.
Migration decision Tau-e made by the Central Committee.
Your intervention will be classified as a first offense.
People will not exist on the planet!
If I was a criminal, then the members of the Committee are killer!
Look this.
This migration list include volunteers.
Why do you interfere?
Shut!
You gather the old men and women, pressed them, and call that volunteer activities?
I'll kill them!
All you want to do is reduce the mouth to eat!
Watch your words, Captain!
We are communicating through an open channel.
Tất cả mọi người trên con tàu này có thể nghe chúng ta, đúng không?
Ngay bây giờ, con tàu này đang cố gắng để từ bỏ những người cao tuổi.
Chúng tôi có thể thiếu tài nguyên.
Nhưng điều này có thể được tha thứ?
Chúng tôi đã không tìm kiếm đất hứa sẽ cứu chúng ta?
Bạn có thể thực sự từ bỏ những yếu kém và tiếp tục giữ đầu của bạn lên cao?
Thuyền trưởng Sakaki.
Tôi sẽ chờ đợi một giờ.
Nếu con tàu này không thay đổi khóa học, tôi sẽ thổi lên đưa đón này.
Tao không đùa!
Làm ơn dừng lại đã, thuyền trưởng Sakaki.
Đó là sự thật mà chúng tôi, các tình nguyện viên, thực sự muốn đi tàu-e.
Chúng tôi không phải bị đuổi ra hoặc bất cứ điều gì.
Đừng dại dột! Điều này là tự sát!
Chúng tôi đã trên con tàu này trong hơn 20 năm trong khi lang thang qua không gian.
Những người trẻ tuổi có thể chịu đựng điều này.
Nhưng đối với chúng tôi, chúng tôi giới hạn của chúng tôi.
Nhưng... nếu bạn từ bỏ, sau đó...
Haruo.
-.. .thì nó là tất cả hơn! -Haruo!
Không sao đâu.
Ít nhất, khi tôi chết, tôi muốn đứng trên mặt đất.
Nó có thể trên bất kỳ hành tinh.
Ông nội.
HÀNH TINH CỦA QUÁI VẬT
Nó bắt đầu vào cuối mùa hè của thế kỷ 20.
Nhìn vào mà! Đó là một con quái vật! Đây là một cảnh không thể tin được.
Lần đầu tiên...
nhân loại nhận ra họ không phải là những người cai trị của hành tinh này nữa.
Con quái vật.
Từ độ sâu của trái đất và biển, hoặc thậm chí từ một huyền thoại thần thánh bị lãng quên,
họ giữ xuất hiện, không ngừng.
Nhằm đem lại một kết thúc với sự thịnh vượng của nhân loại.
HQ Countermeasure của Liên Hiệp Quốc đã đặt tên cho nó "Godzilla."
Và sau đó, cuối cùng, cơn ác mộng tồi tệ nhất của chúng tôi xuất hiện.
Godzilla.
Con người hay quái vật, nó đốt tất cả mọi thứ trong tầm nhìn.
Avatar phá hủy.
Lúc 2:30 EST, một cuộc tấn công hạt nhân quy mô lớn được tung ra chống lại Godzilla, nhưng thất bại.
Lúc nửa đêm, lực lượng đồng minh EC đã thông báo họ đã bắt đầu sơ tán...
Trái đất sụp đổ và bầu trời mưa lửa.
Và sau đó, nó không phải chỉ con người trái đất những người sợ sức mạnh phá hoại của nó.
Ở trên Liên Hiệp Quốc xây dựng, bí ẩn các đối tượng đang bay...
Người dân của trái đất, chúng tôi là Exif.
Chúng tôi đang quan sát và dự đoán.
Chúng tôi đã đến để nói với bạn về số phận của bạn.
Thời gian hủy diệt là hô. Bạn phải khám phá ra một con đường để cống hiến.
Chúng tôi là Bilusaludo.
Hành tinh của chúng tôi, hành tinh thứ ba trong các Bilusaludia nhị phân hệ thống,
nuốt chửng bởi một lỗ đen accursed và bị phá hủy.
Chúng tôi đang yêu cầu nhập cư đến hành tinh thứ ba này hệ thống năng lượng mặt trời.
Nếu bạn chấp nhận, chúng tôi hứa hẹn để diệt trừ mối đe dọa lớn nhất của bạn, Godzilla.
Những người từ một thiên hà xa, những người sau khi hành tinh xanh này cho mình,
không đợi thiên đường này của oxy và nước để trở thành đất scorched.
-Godzilla đã thông qua các đường dây quốc phòng! -Các bức tường sẽ cung cấp cho chúng tôi một thời gian.
A3 và A5 khối AIs là im lặng!
-Mecha-Godzilla sẽ không kích hoạt! -Tại sao nó sẽ không kích hoạt?
Nguyên tử hơi thở phát hiện! Đến!
Thiết giáp tường thứ tư rồi! Mọi chuyện đã xong!
Chúng tôi không có lựa chọn. Di tản!
Tất cả các đơn vị, di tản! Nhanh lên!
Đợi! Nếu chúng ta có thể kích hoạt Mecha-Godzilla, chúng tôi có thể đánh bại nó!
Chúng ta đi, Galu-gu!
Tuy nhiên, ngay cả với hợm thu thập tình báo,
quyền lực của tàu khu trục choáng ngợp với chúng tôi hoàn toàn.
Mẹ và cha ở đâu?
Họ sẽ bắt kịp sớm. Thấy không? Đó là xe buýt.
Hey, đó là cái gì?
Godzilla là nó!
Godzilla của ở đây!
Haruo! Khẩn trương lên!
Tôi nhớ những ngọn lửa đốt cháy trên bầu trời,
và chìm đắm, despaired khuôn mặt của người lớn.
Chúng tôi rời với hy vọng sẽ tìm thấy hành tinh inhabitable.
Tuy nhiên, chúng tôi sẽ sớm phải trả giá cho lạc quan ngu ngốc như vậy.
Trong không gian đông lạnh, màu đen,
đây là một loại địa ngục tồi tệ hơn so với hành tinh chúng ta phá hủy trong lửa.
Có những ngày vô tận của đau khổ từ nạn đói, khát, và cảm lạnh.
Một số ngã bệnh.
Và những người khác dần dần mất đi sự tỉnh táo của họ.
Anh trai chúng tôi con số giảm mạnh trong nháy mắt.
Thậm chí, những người vẫn còn sống không có thời gian để tang người chết.
Nhân ái và niềm tự hào đang xa xưa những câu chuyện của quá khứ.
Một câu chuyện cổ tích từ thời gian chúng tôi từng có quyền truy cập không giới hạn vào nước và ôxy.
Chúng ta đi đâu... và vì lý do gì?
Chúng tôi phải chịu đựng đau khổ của việc có kéo dài cuộc sống của chúng tôi
bằng cách hy sinh những người khác?
Tại sao chúng ta đang sống?
Tại sao?
Bạn đã có một cơn ác mộng?
Vì vậy, bạn đang ở đây, là Metphies.
Nó cũng là công việc của tôi để lắng nghe lời thú nhận của một tù nhân.
Vì vậy, tôi có nên ăn năn với Đức Chúa trời của bạn?
Tôi sẽ giải quyết cho một lời thú nhận giả, quá.
Dưới đây là các dữ liệu mà bạn yêu cầu.
Cảm ơn bạn.
Bạn có khá kiên trì.
Tôi không có bất cứ điều gì khác để làm.
Bạn sẽ không nhận được vào rắc rối nếu họ tìm ra bạn đang giúp đỡ?
Tôi có một quan tâm đến sự nhiệt tình của bạn.
Tại sao các bạn rất tò mò về đào lên dữ liệu bị Cấm
bất cứ ai cũng sẽ không muốn quên tồn tại?
"Tại sao," bạn yêu cầu?
Tôi cũng đang nghĩ "tại sao."
Kể từ khi tôi đã ném ra đây, từ đó sẽ không nhận được ra khỏi đầu của tôi.
Tại sao chúng tôi đã trở thành đau khổ như vậy?
Nó là không thể tránh khỏi? Một hình phạt hợp lý?
Không.
Lý do chúng tôi đang đau khổ là vì chúng ta thua thằng khốn đó.
Chúng tôi đã không chiến đấu để kết thúc, nhưng đã từ bỏ và bỏ trốn.
Tất cả mọi thứ là số phận.
Chúng tôi hợm không có cách để chiến đấu quái vật đó.
Tôi không đồng ý.
Và tôi sẽ cho họ.
Chúng tôi chỉ cần phải chiến lược và lập kế hoạch,
và nhân loại có thể đã đánh bại nó.
Tôi sẽ chứng minh điều đó.
Đó là một điều lạ.
Không giống như những người trẻ tuổi, thế hệ của bạn có kinh nghiệm firsthand tai.
And yet, it's as if you want to see that creature again.
Based on the Gematron calculation, the predictions look disappointing.
The possibility of finding a habitable planet in 20 years is 0.1%.
If we want better results than Tau-e, the outlook is even grimmer.
The lack of resources is severe.
Even doubling the discomfort index, life will be unsustainable in eight years.
The landing ship explosion the other day was a significant psychological blow.
- This is getting... - Indeed.
We need to examine scenario number three in a realistic way.
Returning to Earth. It's already 11.9 light years away.
There's no precedent for traveling so far. It's too risky.
Gematron's guidance isn't bound by time or distance.
As long as the nuclear reactor has sufficient energy, travel is possible.
According to the ship's simulator, it requires 170% of its operation ratio.
I don't know if we can mobilize the manpower.
Would it be a constructive decision to abandon the emigration?
That's the problem.
If we return to Earth, would we be able to survive?
It is currently impossible to calculate how much time has passed on Earth.
At the very least, a few thousand years.
Since we fled Earth, the environment should have calmed down.
It's possible it could've gotten worse.
The problem is that strange thesis published on the shared server.
Why would that research thesis appear at a time like this?
The writer remains anonymous,
but it contains information that requires special log-in credentials to access.
The author aside, there's probably an informant in the Central Committee.
R-Ridiculous!
There's an electromagnetic shield under the body's surface?
It's not a normal organism?
No, its whole body is like a giant coil.
Is that true?
So, what happened in the end?
It's kind of weird.
A new Gematron code is using 80% of the calculation server's power.
Eighty percent?
Isn't it the analysis for predictions?
Still, for a simulation, it's too much.
So, the rumor of returning to Earth is true?
It's 11.9 light years in one go.
Is a subspace jump-warp even possible?
It's not a problem if we use Gematron calculation.
I heard it directly from Navigation.
Gematron, huh?
The ship leaders turn to the gods, as usual.
Maybe even that new anti-Godzilla tactic was a leak from the higher-ups?
Man, are we going to fight it again?
It's a monster that withstood an attack of 150 nuclear warheads at once.
That's 40 megatons of nucleoplasm total.
But the thesis contained new strategies on how to fight it.
Huh?
It's me.
Hey, come in.
So, the Central Committee is leaning towards going to Earth, huh?
Not entirely.
To give up searching for a habitable planet
means someone has to bear that responsibility.
If they're so weak they give up drifting after only 20 years, it can't be helped.
Well, I do sympathize.
They haven't dealt with the loss of their home planet as long as we have.
And then, there's your practical joke.
Obviously, it's a headache for Mori.
I uploaded a new version this morning. Did you read it?
Yeah. When I downloaded it, it already had over 400 views.
Though the file was deleted three seconds later.
Our delinquent captain sure is popular.
When there's rumor of returning to Earth, we get more talk of Godzilla.
It's effective for ridiculing the Central Committee.
Haruo is unaware of the Central Committee's expectations.
He was researching Godzilla purely for personal interest.
But this thesis has content that will support our plan to return to Earth.
Its claim is that Godzilla can be defeated by human hands.
If you can't understand its contents, it just sounds like crazy prattling.
Earthlings harbor that much fear of Godzilla.
So, do you think it's just crazy prattling?
This analysis report?
No, it's actually quite interesting.
So much so, I think better of him.
Godzilla is not invincible.
It's humanity's fault for giving up on the fight.
That's what Haruo thinks.
He analyzed that old data because of you Exifs' Gematron calculation.
It was impossible for Earthlings at the time.
Are you saying that, if the weak-point analysis had been made in time,
that humanity still wouldn't have been victorious?
And if they did defeat Godzilla,
then it was only a matter of time until Exif's cult took over Earth.
Even if Bilusaludo's Mecha-Godzilla had defeated Godzilla,
no one knows who it would have bared its fangs at next.
However, we failed in the construction of Mecha-Godzilla.
And you couldn't brainwash Earthlings with your religion.
That's history now.
The what-ifs are only fairy tales.
Subspace jump-warp procedure, now entering phase two.
Activating shields for all ship sections.
Bypassing electricity for the gravitational coil engine.
Initiating Gematron calculation and gravitational coils controller.
Begin cluster connections with Gematron calculation crystal and central AI.
Gravitational coil engine for all sections functioning normally.
Preparations for spin complete.
Subspace coordinate system render will be displayed on the central hologram.
Attention all personnel.
This ship, Aratrum, will soon initiate subspace jump-warp.
Estimated emergence coordinates are near the solar system's third planet, Earth.
Based on the ship's time, 22 years have passed since our departure.
This subspace jump-warp will be the longest we've traversed.
Finally. The real Earth!
I wonder if we can see the ocean?
That'd be awesome if we can!
The longest? Is this really safe?
...no idea what changes Earth's environment has undergone.
After an investigation,
if we conclude the environment has become unfit for human survival,
we will collect resources...
Hey, is the real Earth prettier than the hologram?
Yes, it is.
Entering Gematron-predicted coordinates. Suspending main propulsion drive.
We now have all the Gematron numbers.
Irrational numbers converted to integers. Computing time-space recon point.
Chances of a wormhole appearing is 440% in a simulated observation.
Releasing gravitational coil output for each section of the ship.
Maximum spin.
Captain, on your order.
Initiate jump-warp.
Jump-warp initiated. Commence shift into phase one space travel.
Gravitational coil at max speed, running stable.
Arriving at launch point required for final trajectory.
Breaking through subspace.
Amazing.
Hey, it's really blue!
- That's the ocean? - It's beautiful.
That's Earth?
Yes, that's right.
It really is blue!
To think that I'd see it again.
Disabling shields in all sections. Normal travel mode stable.
Distance from Earth, 1,800 kilometers.
Recalculating low orbit entrance errors.
Our Earth that was taken from us.
Orbit errors corrected.
Now entering low Earth orbit.
If we can't land on Earth, we'll have a revolt on our hands.
It's too soon to be pessimistic.
Let's just wait for the scouting report.
Unmanned recon drones launching in sequence.
All drone feedback systems are stable.
Begin dispersion to specified areas for surveillance.
Entering the stratosphere. Drone temperature stable.
Altitude 30,000 meters, beginning descent.
Altitude 15,000 meters, entering the troposphere.
Stellar observation parallax calculated.
Elapsed time for the solar system is approximately 10,000 years.
It's been 10,000 years? That long?
It's more than I imagined.
This could be good news.
With that much time, the ecosystem must have changed.
Not even Godzilla...
I wonder.
It's possible it could've multiplied.
That thing is a genetic aberration. It's impossible!
Recon drones are at a scouting altitude of 2,000 meters.
Receiving visuals.
Drone six displaying sound signal monitor.
Just the sound of the wind?
We can't see anything. Can you lower the altitude?
All drones descending.
There are thick particles floating in the atmosphere.
Average visibility less than 300 meters.
This is... Picking up electromagnetic interference.
This isn't just a normal fog.
Switching drones to sensor monitors.
Each drone's altitude at 500 meters.
Atmospheric density is increasing.
Further descent by remote is impossible.
Is this a forest?
Or some kind of complicated terrain.
Can you increase the scan power?
Its reflection is diffused, so this is the limit.
What's that?
It's moving.
Drone six, switching to sound wave reconnaissance.
Temperature around drone six is increasing drastically!
- What? - What's happening?
Drone six, lost!
Estimated energy output around drone six approximately 180 gigawatts.
High probability of high-energy electron particles, or atomic breath!
M-Maybe it was thunder or...
Idiot! No one would ever forget that roar!
Damn it. It's still on this planet.
You're there, aren't you?
You're still there!
If the characteristics match this closely, then that was Godzilla,
or a threat similar to it, and it must be eliminated.
Our one advantage is that it acts independently rather than in a pack.
How can you say that for sure?
The concentration of radiation.
As you're aware, Godzilla is a creature that scatters heavy radiation in its wake.
However, even though the terrain has undergone change,
the toxins present in the atmosphere are maintaining stable numbers.
If we reverse calculate the emission data gathered in the past three days,
multiple Godzillas seem unlikely.
Even now, Godzilla is a unique genetic defect
and cannot be considered a normal living creature, is what I mean.
However, it's been 10,000 years. How can it still be alive?
There are cases where lotus seeds survived for 2,000 years.
It also may be repeating cycles of dormancy every few thousand years.
Or, over 10,000 years, it could have multiplied
and diminished in number, with this being the last surviving one.
Godzilla's biology is beyond every known aspect of life science.
And we can't ignore the possibility that it could be immortal.
Studies and research aren't this meeting's main subject.
We humanoids cannot coexist with Godzilla.
However, if that is indeed Godzilla, and the last one,
then there is only one option.
Complete extermination.
Are you utterly insane?
As you are all aware, we have drafted anti-Godzilla strategies.
You mean that anonymous thesis?
We don't even know who wrote it!
It's from a specialist's investigation.
It's deemed as promising information.
I am also prepared to release the name of the person who wrote it, right here.
However, there are conditions.
And what would those conditions be?
To drop the charges regarding the stolen secret information, and then...
release Captain Haruo Sakaki on bail.
Captain Sakaki? It was him?
You got us, Metphies.
All shall be according to God's will.
It's your turn.
Haruo.
It's here. This waveform is generating the electromagnetic metamaterial.
Since each of Godzilla's cells can function as a powerful electromagnet,
it emits a high-output, high-frequency electromagnetic pulse
and generates an asymmetrically permeable shield.
A physically impervious shield?
It may be enormous, but can a creature even do that?
And if that were true, how can we even begin to fight it?
It's only for about 1/10,000 of a second, but it emits a noise periodically.
If we use an interference wave, we can amplify that noise
to fracture the metamaterial, and we'll target that point.
So by attacking a single point, we can take that colossal thing down?
There should be an organ amplifying the electromagnetic pulse.
If we destroy that, we can neutralize the shield.
And where is it?
Unknown.
There isn't enough data in our visual records.
We need to observe Godzilla and analyze the emission pattern.
As you know from past battles,
we can confirm Godzilla has tremendous regenerative abilities.
The destroyed organs will regenerate, and in the seconds before the shield goes up,
we need to shove an EMP probe into its body and destroy it from within.
The main issue with this operation is the changed atmosphere,
and the electromagnetic wave interference.
To observe and find Godzilla's weak point,
we need detailed coordination with accurate attacks,
so close quarters combat is required.
And for each process,
we need manpower, otherwise we cannot succeed.
Preposterous!
Even if we gather all the races, there are only 4,000 of us.
I cannot approve an operation where lives can be lost.
Captain Sakaki.
I'll be blunt.
In order for your operation to work, how many people do you need?
Combat engineers, infantry, and special forces, so three battalions.
If I form two companies from each,
we're looking at about 600 people.
Out of the question.
Those who do not fight, know not how to fight evil.
Those gathered now, unified as one, shall come to know God's mercy.
Give praise to God. All shall lead down the devoted path.
Garbetrium guidance be with you all.
This is Colonel Elliot Leland, commander of the Earth Landing Brigade.
Everyone, continue your tasks and listen.
All 600 gathered here are the chosen elite forces
who have decided to give their lives to fight against Godzilla.
Everyone correctly understands
that there will be no constructive outlook if you're trapped in an old society.
Instead of a fake promised land,
we will take back our homeland,
and promise prosperity to the next generation.
For the sake of humanity's future, I look forward to everyone's efforts.
All assembled landing ships have exited the gates.
Now closing the first launch gate station.
That speech sounded like you wanted to pick a fight with the Committee.
Hey, Haruo.
Didn't you also want to get the Committee members frustrated?
With the current system, those members will just dry up and die.
There aren't any comfortable chairs for us.
But if we defeat Godzilla, then the story will be different.
A new hero will arrive.
Our era will come.
A hero, huh?
You're just like when you were a kid.
Don't take it the wrong way. You're still on bail status.
We went through a lot just to get you back out.
Commander.
All landing ships have assembled in low orbit.
All ships, enter in sequential order.
Roger.
All ships, begin entry in sequential order.
Ship ten, ignite engine.
Deploy anti-aerodynamic drag and heat shield.
You look unhappy.
Even though your wish is being granted.
I wonder if everything will go according to plan.
It'll be okay. As long as we have the hero who will guide them.
Are you a Leland sympathizer?
Well, the one I put my hope in is you,
Haruo.
The one true path to glory can only be opened through devotion.
This is our, the Exif's, creed.
There are only a few Earthlings who embody that.
You're a rare exception.
You overestimate me.
You are the one who is worthy of fighting Godzilla.
The time will come soon enough when that can be proven.
Ship temperature stable.
Passing the stratosphere.
Altitude 30,000 meters.
Igniting arc jet thrusters for cruising.
Once we go under those clouds, we won't see the sun anymore, huh?
This planet has been completely changed, too.
Now entering the troposphere.
Altitude 2,000. All ships, begin navigating towards landing zone.
The visibility's terrible.
Switching the ship's probes to ultrasonic.
Begin image processing.
Company A, landing zone confirmed.
Obstacles detected.
As the reconnaissance drones reported, this is a thick forest.
Securing landing point now. Prepare the thermobaric bombs.
Roger. Dropping thermo-pressure warheads.
They're being grandiose over there.
Well, the special forces will land on impeded terrain.
What?
An obstacle collided with the ship's exterior.
No issues so far with power and steering.
An obstacle?
Lieutenant Colonel Galu-gu, Company E has also landed.
We will now set the combat engineers' traps.
Okay.
The old Tanzawa Pass, huh?
If it was sunny, it would've been beautiful.
With this heavy fog, a visual battle would be impossible.
Lieutenant Colonel Galu-gu, please look.
This is...
Doesn't it look like something scratched it?
I hope the others are okay out there.
Get the transmission balloons!
You don't need to unload the medical supplies.
Transmission balloon reception favorable.
Companies B and C special force units will reach their destination on schedule.
Companies D and E will deploy artillery as the combat engineers lay down traps.
Okay, the first battle formation is going according to plan.
Whichever company finds Godzilla first, open fire with the special forces.
Provoke it and divert its course.
What's important is to observe Godzilla's electromagnetic waves when it's attacked.
We'll analyze this data to see which organ emits the electromagnetic wave.
Once we destroy that, we can neutralize the asymmetrically permeable shield.
And finally, we'll chase Godzilla into this Tanzawa Pass,
and slow it with traps set by the engineers.
The artillery unit will then open fire from a close range.
We'll amplify the pulse noise, attack all at once, and destroy the organ.
The shield will go down for a few seconds, and then we'll use EMP probes to end it.
If we can't find the amplifying organ, we can't place the infantry.
Exactly.
The special forces analysis of the pattern will influence the plan.
So they'll spread out into a wide area, and advance while analyzing the enemy.
Cooperation is key.
But who knew we'd have to rely on something this pathetic to communicate?
If we can transmit through this convection cloud,
the drones in the stratosphere will relay our communication with no issues.
But in this fog, electronic communication will be limited.
What is going on with this planet's atmosphere?
That's what we're trying to find out.
Colonel, I'd like to form an investigation team.
If I can borrow three teams, as planned.
The scouting team takes priority. I'll give you two teams.
All right, then.
I'd like to go, too. I want to see with my own eyes how this terrain has changed.
You heard him.
- Master Sergeant Yuko Tani, you're up. - Yuko?
You'll be his handler. As you know, he's been released on bail.
So be careful handling him.
Understood.
Unbelievable. Are these really the plants growing on Earth?
Is this what I saw in the ship's records? Trees, was it?
They look different, though.
Don't touch it!
In some places they're sharp as razors.
It'd be deadly if your airtight suit got a hole in it.
Why did you request to join this mission?
Because you're involved, Captain Sakaki, and set up the operation.
Please don't call me that. Just Haruo is fine.
I've always wanted to meet you so we could speak in person.
I wondered if it's because of you, Cap... Haruo, that grandpa died at Tau-e.
I...
The bombs that you brought inside the shuttle,
I heard from security that they were definitely all removed.
But then the emigration group...
Do you think it was an accident?
You don't think it was?
You said the Central Committee wanted to reduce passengers.
They could have used some trick so the emigration group wouldn't...
The Central Committee isn't that corrupt!
That's what I want to think. I don't want to be suspicious of my comrades.
Haruo.
No, that's not it. I couldn't forgive myself for wanting to be suspicious.
I don't want to be so judgmental of humans.
But being on that claustrophobic ship and living on minimal supplies,
it's normal for people to become mistrustful.
Godzilla didn't just steal Earth away from us.
Justice, faith, and the basic pride we have as humans...
we've come to lose them, too.
And that's why we need to fight Godzilla again.
So we can take back the dignity we lost.
This is...
Professor! Please come!
Over there!
Ruins?
But they couldn't have lasted 10,000 years.
Captain Sakaki!
I see.
The lichen used the building's surface as a seedbed and became fossilized.
Afterwards, the building materials weathered away,
but the fossilized fungus must have retained the shape.
This is Earth's civilization. People used to live here?
Haruo?
It remembered.
Although we've forgotten, this planet has always remembered us.
Of course. Even after undergoing change, this is still our Mother Earth.
The planet that belongs to humans.
We'll take it back... no matter what.
With our own hands.
Where's the scouting team? Haven't they responded yet?
It's probably the electromagnetic waves.
The reception area is five kilometers, right?
Yes.
Unexpected atmospheric changes are also possible.
There are reports of geomagnetic storms.
But we're connected with Martin's investigation team. It's strange!
Hey, what's that?
Is it the scouting team?
What?
Damn it! Kill it!
- What? - Something happened at the camp!
- Professor Martin! - Let's go back, now!
This doesn't correspond to any of Earth's primary species records.
It must be a sudden variant,
otherwise, how could something evolve into a form like this?
Would living organisms go through such a change,
even if 10,000 years have passed?
We collected and analyzed the forest's plants,
and by using carbon dating, I know how much time has passed.
And it looks to be within a 50-year range of 19,200 years.
So our time away keeps increasing.
The special cell characteristics of this beast and the plants are interesting.
Okay, it came off.
The flora and fauna have differences, but also similar, wide-ranging traits.
Along with characteristics very similar to metal,
they have bodily functions that exert powerful magnetism.
The same as Godzilla?
Yes. This beast is small, but it may be in the same family as Godzilla.
What's surprising is that the plants also have strikingly similar characteristics.
So this fog causing the electromagnetic disturbance...
The particles in the air are the pollen of this forest's plants.
It could also be their natural chaff.
If the fog's caused by the organisms and not the weather,
we have to burn the entire forest down to disperse this fog?
So, we have no choice but to abandon our first plan of waiting
for the weather to clear up a bit before we attack.
That's not all.
If dangerous beasts are wandering around,
I have to split up our troops for camp defense.
We can reassign groups to join the special forces.
Don't be ridiculous!
You want everyone to wander in this unknown environment without a plan?
Then what's your plan?
Retreat.
Logically, that's our only choice.
What are you saying?
The water and plants are toxic, and the wild animals are hostile.
The only benefits here are air pressure and gravity.
It'd be the height of stupidity to fight Godzilla to reclaim this planet.
This is our home!
You're giving up? Not only once, but twice?
We can settle on the surface of the moon, and collect resources from Earth.
If we're thinking about safety, it's a more realistic plan.
Weren't you going to defeat Godzilla and become a hero?
I underestimated the situation. My eyes are open now and I've learned!
You're going to be a coward now?
From wild beasts alone, we have 12 dead and 35 critically injured!
Without even seeing Godzilla, this is the outcome!
We can't play war with new soldiers who've never fought in actual combat.
Retreat?
I do agree with the commander's decision, but the problem is, how do we retreat?
That attack just now
left us with heavier equipment loss than human casualties.
Is that so?
Frustratingly, those lizard things destroyed four landing ships.
Ship one and two's fuel systems and ship three and four's engines are dead.
We can't return to the mother ship orbiting this planet anymore.
If that's the case, we need to gather Company A,
and join the company with enough transit power to get us all back to space.
Companies B and C are special forces like us, so they can't do it.
So we must join the artillery unit and the trap materials unit,
which are Companies D and E.
In order for us to escape the wild animals' habitat,
we must move through this old Tanzawa Pass.
And our first plan was to go through the projected encounter area for Godzilla.
That's correct.
We need to pass the area where Godzilla appears frequently.
Of course, if we run into Godzilla, that would be extremely awful for us.
In order to secure safe passage...
We would need backup from Companies B and C.
However, if we join up and form a cluster, we'll be open to an atomic breath attack.
What's the safest plan?
While remaining spread out,
repeatedly reciprocate the threat and keep securing each other's safety.
Yes. This is, however, quite close to Captain Sakaki's original plan,
with very few changes.
Listen here. This is a retreat tactic, no matter what.
We will not take any action to lure out Godzilla.
Once all units reach the gathering point, we complete the mission,
and return to the mother ship.
Be careful of that crack.
Okay, that's good. This way!
There's no fuse, but it could still explode, so be careful.
- That's a high explosive. Be careful. - Yeah.
Company B, C, and all landing ships, heading to Company D camp.
- Confirm landing zone. - Landing zone confirmed.
All ships rotate bearing to 202.5 degrees.
- Marker lock. - Roger.
So what's the situation?
Company B, Company C reserves,
and Company A hover squads are to join with Company D and stand by.
What's going on? Is the plan a go, or no?
Based on Commander Leland's orders to the hover squads,
special forces will abandon the base camps.
After all units reach the final gathering point, we'll retreat.
We'll follow our original path, but we won't search for Godzilla.
So, what? Did we come down to Earth just to display our marching orders?
Company A's damage must have been that severe.
I heard there were smaller Godzilla-like creatures.
They were strong enough to destroy a power suit.
Leland, that coward. If he's going to go along with Haruo's madness,
he has to resign himself from the beginning.
They had us design this,
and now we have to abandon it because of overcapacity?
Approaching Godzilla's projected contact area.
Hurry! We need to get through this area quickly!
Can't this thing pump out any more speed?
By shifting parts around, we got ship two moving.
It's all we can do to keep it hovering.
I guess I'm thankful that it's moving.
I wouldn't want to walk through this forest at all.
Are you having foreboding thoughts?
If this ends without us encountering Godzilla, then why did I come here?
Were you hoping to depend on luck?
It's fine if we're actively searching,
but if we pass by in a rush, then we won't even find anything.
That's if we were actively searching for Godzilla, right?
You and Colonel Leland
still don't understand one crucial aspect of that thing.
It will never let humanity escape.
Even more so if we've come to provoke it without a trace of fear.
So, it will be searching for us?
Is that some divine message from god?
It's a legend.
We Exif have been wandering through space as vagrants
far longer than Earthlings have,
and we've witnessed many civilizations destroyed.
Many have been regretfully destroyed by creatures similar to Godzilla.
What's that?
He is the punishing iron hammer for the arrogant.
For the species who pronounce themselves as lords of creation,
a divine avenger will pay them a visit.
And so, he will...
What was that?
An earthquake?
Sound wave analysis! All units, prepare for battle!
Movement detected at two o'clock! It's approaching!
Evade! Evade, now!
We can't evade in time!
Run, Haruo.
Do as your soul cries out to do.
Yeah.
The propellant is leaking! It's going to explode!
Hurry!
I'll get you for this!
That idiot.
Haruo, why?
He's going to record the moment Godzilla activates its shield.
And to do that, you have to attack it.
Damn it, the electromagnetic sensor isn't responding. Why?
What are you doing? Let's go!
But then, Captain Sakaki...
Then, get out.
Again! This time, at a closer distance!
Damn it!
I see.
Such light damage won't cause the shield to activate.
Professor Martin!
Please record this next attack with the sensor.
Captain! What's your plan?
I'm going to nose-dive and slam into it.
What?
You bastard, I will...
This planet can go to hell.
Leland.
Colonel Leland was killed?
Yes. According to rank, the command will now fall to me, though...
Can you do it?
I'll need to reassign a subordinate who has disobeyed military regulations.
This is an emergency, so please understand.
For this occasion, fine. Bring back as many people as you can.
Understood.
Did you analyze the data sent to us?
Finished just now.
The electromagnetic metamaterial's output has been recorded.
Just as you surmised, a shield exists.
The noise in question was confirmed.
It's not unified across its body.
There's clearly a concentrated spot.
The dorsal fin?
This is where the shield is generated. Leland gave his life for this information.
Everyone, during that earlier encounter, Colonel Leland died an honorable death.
And so, as the Central Committee's direct priest,
I have accepted full responsibility for this operation.
However, I cannot say that I am the best man for this job.
All people are born to accomplish the task they were meant to do.
This has been established in our scriptures,
and as I shoulder the burden of a priest, I cannot turn my back to this truth.
With the premise of taking full responsibility,
I will now entrust all decision-making...
to Captain Sakaki, as the commander.
Okay, Haruo.
Your orders.
But that's insane!
The situation is dire, so I'll skip the pleasantries.
I don't have an outlook for humanity's future,
and I don't have enough of a strategy to estimate our chances of winning.
However, I can say this.
Those who didn't yield to Godzilla can proudly welcome another day.
This is not only a battle to kill Godzilla.
What we are about to fight is a humiliating future
with no choice but to accept despair and resignation.
If we can reject and fight that, we can once again dream of hope and pride.
Just as our ancestors did, who thrived here before us.
That's right. If we don't retreat now, if we don't show fear,
and if we put our lives on the line, we've already won.
All we need to do is finish it.
Humanity's 22-year-long nightmare, and Godzilla's 20,000-year era.
I look forward to your brave efforts. That is all.
We'll begin our operation.
Yuko, you know Godzilla's position, right?
Yes. It's about 80 kilometers north-north-east.
Moving southwest at 40 kilometers an hour.
Set up transmission balloons every 3,000 meters on the battlefield.
- We need optimal communicative reception. - Roger.
Major Belu-be, provoke Godzilla from a distance and watch its reaction.
Maintain that distance.
Sure, leave it to me.
Adam, watch for the atomic breath.
If electric potential rises, escape immediately.
Understood.
Galu-gu.
I'll move to the trap point and command the power suit team directly.
What?
I'll determine the EMP probes' target point on-site.
However...
Galu-gu, how are the trap placements?
All according to plan.
Its weak point is the dorsal fin, its back.
Since we need to concentrate our fire at a close distance,
we have to let it pass the line of fire, and lure it deeper into the valley.
So we only have one chance.
To make this plan work, we need to place the traps deeper in the valley.
Artillery units are all in position.
We're ready.
Can we really lure it all the way out here?
We have no choice but to believe in them.
Power suit team, move to the trap point. We'll stand by.
I'm leaving the diversion to you, Belu-be.
Roger.
All squads, ascend to planned altitude. Cross-delta pattern formation.
Godzilla detected at the projected contact area.
All units, commence the diversion plan.
Right wing, squad one, attack!
Godzilla sighting confirmed!
Fire!
All units, turn!
Ascend in battle formation. We'll attack as long as possible!
Target successfully diverted.
We can do this!
Evade!
Damn it! Adam! Take the left wing!
Roger, left wing, squad one.
- The impact area is bigger! - It's hard to evade!
The evading maneuvers are just a second delayed. Let's go!
- Right wing, squad two, follow and attack! - Roger!
These guys aren't part of the plan!
What's wrong?
Major Belu-be! It's what attacked Company A!
What? All squads provide cover fire from a higher altitude.
Shoot them down before more come from the forest!
Left wing, squad two, counterattack!
We have no time for the small fish.
Left wing, squad two, continue the diversion!
Belu-be, are you okay?
It seems like you're in trouble.
Like the simulations predicted, we should be able to lure it to the spot.
But we need more firepower.
It'll be night soon. Can you hasten the process?
Ten have gone down. Ammo and gas are almost depleted.
Adam. Do you copy?
Yes. Captain, I copy.
- I'm reassigning you. - What, right now?
I'm shortening the time allotted to lure Godzilla.
What? How can we do that?
I'll use the landing ships for a bombardment to create a path.
What? Send the landing ships to the frontline?
It's too dangerous.
If they get shot down, how will we return to the mother ship?
But we're already home.
There's nowhere else to return to but here. Isn't that right?
Have you lost your mind?
Let's do it.
It'll be useless to prepare an escape route.
In order to win, we need to play every hand.
This is why belligerent species are difficult to deal with.
Adam, select five elite pilots. Prepare the landing ships for takeoff.
Roger.
Major Belu-be, Second Lieutenant Adam Bindewald, withdrawing!
Hurry and go! We'll handle this somehow!
Right wing, squad one, charge again!
Don't fall behind!
Six elite pilots, standing by!
We can go anytime!
Load all ammunition, even the reserves.
If we mess up, that's it.
Roger!
All landing ships, depart!
Starting from Godzilla's position, create a path until the signal is given.
Fire at will, if you must.
Eliminate any obstacles in its way.
Commencing final diversion.
This is the point of no return. We'll end this, now.
Listen up, the landing ships' mobility can't evade an attack in time.
Once you know you're targeted, abandon ship!
Captain, you're being lavish!
Hover squads, save ammo until the route is open. Minimize losses.
Roger. We're almost out of gas. So there's no second chances!
Turn!
The landing ships are almost here!
Spread out to avoid the bombardment!
All ships, drop the thermobaric bombs! Scatter all that you have!
All landing ships, disperse! Spread out!
So who drew the short straw?
It's me, huh?
Okay! Godzilla is on the diversion path!
Now! All hover squads, fire everything you have! This is it!
Roger! All squads, resume the diversion! Increase attack frequency!
Damn it!
It's no good! I can't speed up!
All squads! Join the left wing! Just a little more!
Diversion is in progress.
Godzilla is accelerating toward the trap point!
Haruo, please hurry and board.
Yuko!
Why are you here?
I've always been on the power suit team.
Do you understand? This is practically a suicide mission!
I want to become stronger!
That's what I thought when Grandpa died.
Godzilla entering Tanzawa Pass. Only 500 meters to the trap point.
Damn it, I'm running out of gas!
Keep provoking it and lure it to the last point.
Stay calm, this is the critical moment.
Trap point arrival, 100 meters!
You will return Earth to humans.
Fifty more meters!
Damn, I can't stand this.
At times like this, I'm jealous of those who have a god to pray to.
All units, disperse!
Ten meters!
Godzilla is at the trap point!
Set off the trap!
Trap detonation complete!
Godzilla's movement stopped.
Did we succeed in capturing it?
Artillery unit, begin concentrated fire!
Asymmetrically permeable shield, generated!
All gun ports, synchronized attack!
Body surface electromagnetic pulse alignment sync at 75%!
At 75%? Is the pattern changing?
Alignment incomplete. Unable to predict shield collapse!
Damn it, we can't attack like this.
Search for the noise. Hurry!
Noise detected. The next shield collapse is in 20 seconds.
Twenty seconds?
Will the restraints hold?
Sync at 100%.
Detecting resonance with noise wave! Shield collapse in ten seconds!
Artillery unit, fire!
If we can destroy the dorsal fin...
The shield is dropping!
Electric potential rising! It's an atomic breath!
It can still attack?
The tissue on Godzilla's back is regenerating!
The shield will be restored.
Shield will be up in about 200 seconds!
The restraints are no longer holding!
Damn it.
I'll finish this!
Haruo!
- What is he... - With a close-range EMP attack,
he'll disrupt the noise pattern.
The pulse is changing. It's syncing again!
The next shield collapse is in ten seconds!
Don't worry about me! Destroy the rest of the dorsal fin!
But then you'll...
Doesn't matter! Fire!
The shield is now collapsing!
Fire! Fire until the gun barrel burns up!
The shield is dropping!
Okay, power suit unit, attack!
The EMP probes are entering its body!
All units, retreat! Retreat!
Electromagnetic concentration in the air, rising!
It didn't work?
It did, the electromagnetic waves are running wild inside it.
You bastard, I have...
killed you!
He really did it.
Haruo!
Look at this.
This body structure...
Yeah. Indeed a monster.
You've accomplished it, Captain.
Because everyone believed in and supported me,
I could be so daring and get this far.
Even though we defeated it... What was it, really?
How was it able to live for 20,000 years?
This is just my opinion,
but I think this is a different Godzilla than the one that drove us from Earth.
But its appearance and abilities were almost identical.
And that's exactly why. Life's true nature is found in change.
No matter how gradual the renewal cycle may be,
it's impossible to maintain the exact same appearance.
So this one may be an offspring that inherited Godzilla's form and nature.
Such a guess would actually be the most natural.
Although the question remains of why there was only this one. Also...
So, there's no guarantee only one of them survived.
I apologize if what I'm saying spoils the victory, but that is correct.
That's fine. Thanks to this battle, we proved that we can defeat Godzilla.
Even if another one shows up, we have nothing to fear.
Since we've established a valid strategy, we can be more effective next time.
Personally, I would never want to cross a tightrope like that ever again, though.
What was that?
Did anyone measure the vibration?
I'm picking it up on this sensor!
Find the origin using Gematoria analysis.
Yes, sir.
No, it can't be. Is the meter damaged?
- What is it? - It's within two kilometers?
It's nearby!
That's ridiculous!
Electric potential, rising. The numbers are unbelievable!
They are far greater than Godzilla's!
Underground heat source...
Wait, a plasma reaction? This can't be!
What's happening?
Is that...
Wh-What is that?
Godzilla?
Height over 300 meters and rising.
Surface vibroscope estimates a mass of about 100,000 tons.
This is impossible!
Can that be a living creature? Unbelievable!
No, according to the rules for living creatures, this is correct.
Professor?
Indeed, the changing form of life isn't just about decay.
If it continued its life activity for 20,000 years, growing earnestly...
When those fleeting lives destined to die,
forget their humbleness and sing praises of their glory,
such will shake the very heavens and split the earth,
and they shall know the wrath of the divine.
The inevitable incarnation of destruction.
So, you show yourself at last.
Since we last saw each other, it has been 20 years for us and 20,000 years for you.
It's been a while...
Oh, King of Destruction.
All landing ships, take off immediately! Emergency retreat!
But we're still withdrawing!
Just take whoever's already onboard before that thing attacks us!
Everyone, do whatever it takes to get far away from here! Hurry!
What's that? A super oscillatory wave?
Estimated electric output is measuring over 900 gigawatts.
Damn it!
What do you intend to do?
I'll divert its attention!
I'll buy time so people can run!
You don't think that'll work, do you?
You bastard... I will...
Subtitles by explosiveskull