Monochrome Inverted
Iron-blooded Chapter
Scarstory
March 25th
Naoetsu
Private
High
School
Entrance
Um...
I didn't see anything.
Naoetsu
Private
High
School
Entrance
I've been thinking, y'know,
that skirts are totally unfit for
hiding things you don't want seen.
A pair of tight shorts could serve as a firewall, don't you think?
Dunno.
If you'd excuse me.
Wait a second!
You walk so fast.
I could hardly catch up to you,
Araragi.
Araragi
How do you know my name?
Are you surprised?
We go to the same school.
Written with an "a" from the Buddhist "antigod,"
Antigod
a "ra" or two for good measure,
ra
rara
and a "gi" from "ginkgo tree" too.
gi
And your name, Koyomi, literally means calendar.
Koyomi
Right? Thus we have Araragi Koyomi.
Araragi Koyomi
You're Hanekawa, right?
Hanekawa Tsubasa.
Hanekawa Tsubasa
Wow.
I'm impressed you remember my name. I don't stand out.
For our second-year finals, in the first semester,
you had a perfect score in all subjects,
even PA and art, save for one single mistake.
Oh please, how do you remember that?
Would you happen to be stalking me?
Nah, that'd be reading a bit too much into it.
It's no big deal.
My alien friend told me.
Wait, you've got friends?!
That's more of a surprise than aliens?!
I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that you seem to prefer being alone,
like a hermit or something.
Well, you're right. I've got no friends.
But you're so famous that even
a loner like me knows about you.
Stop that.
Jokes like that aren't funny to me.
Say, Araragi.
Do you believe in vampires?
What about them?
I've been hearing some rumors lately about a vampire being in town.
They say you shouldn't stay out alone at night.
So vague and unfounded.
They say it's a very beautiful blonde woman
with eyes so cold it chills you to the bone.
And that makes them a vampire?
Couldn't it just be a normal human being who stands out because they're blonde?
Under the streetlights, her blonde hair almost shines,
yet she has no shadow.
Still, this happened at night.
It's not like streetlights make shadows unmistakably clear.
Yeah, I think it's a silly rumor too.
But if there was actually a vampire, I'd love to meet them.
I'm intrigued by such superhuman creatures.
Superhuman? Like gods?
It doesn't have to be a god.
It wouldn't be worth the trouble otherwise.
Ah, my bad.
You're so easy to chat with.
So easy I feel like I said stuff that doesn't make much sense.
It's weird you've got no friends when you're so fun to talk to.
Why don't you make friends?
If I made friends, I'd lose my power level.
What?
I don't think I'm following.
I really don't know how to word it.
If I had friends, I'd have to care about them.
If they got hurt, I'd be hurt too.
If they were sad, I'd be sad too.
Friends are just another weakness.
That's like an affliction for anyone.
But when your friends have fun, you'd have fun too.
When they're happy, you'd be happy too.
It doesn't necessarily have to be a weakness.
No.
Friends having fun would make me jealous.
Their happiness would just make me envious.
You're petty.
Give me a break.
Naoetsu
Private
High
School
Entrance
I'll be heading to the library now.
Wanna come along?
Why?
What would I do in a library?
Study, of course.
Of course?
Alas, I'm not so diligent as to study during spring break when I don't even have any homework.
But next semester you'll have to
prepare for university entry exams.
Naoetsu
Private
High
School
Entrance
University?
I'll be happy if I can graduate at all.
I'm not gonna make it, no matter what I do.
Do you have a cell phone?
Uh, yeah?
Gimme.
Thanks. Here.
Naoetsu
Private
High
School
Entrance
I added my number and email.
Hanekawa Tsubasa
Looks like you've just made a friend!
What the hell?
Naoetsu
Private
High
School
Entrance
Flashback
Hanekawa Tsubasa
Naoetsu North
Express
Local
Departures
Platform
Naoetsu Central
Naoetsu South
Shinjuku
Ginza
Oizumi-gakuen
New York
Indeed,
you shall help me.
Can you not hear me?
I said you shall help me.
Are...
Are you okay?
I'll get you an ambulance!
Ambulance?
I need no such thing.
I demand your blood.
Do you believe in vampires?
They say it's a very beautiful blonde woman
with eyes so cold it chills you to the bone.
I am Kiss-shot Acerola-orion Heart-under-blade,
the iron-blooded, hot-blooded, and cold-blooded vampire.
I shall take your blood as my flesh.
Therefore, I demand your blood.
I thought vampires were immortal.
I lost too much blood.
Too much to even regenerate or transform.
I am about to die.
As a lowly human, you should consider
becoming my flesh to be a great honor.
Blood?
Can't you get a transfusion or something?
How much do you need?
Everything you have should keep me alive for now.
I see. All I've got.
What's wrong?
I demand your blood!
Now! Hurry!
Hurry, you fool!
It's fine.
I can get away.
Can you imagine any honor greater than this?
I can get away from this.
Just run.
That will let me
escape this reality.
What?
You must be jesting.
You refuse to help me?!
No!
No! No! I don't wanna die!
I don't wanna die! I don't wanna die!
Help me! Help me, please!
Please, I beg you!
Help me...
No!
I'm sorry!
I would die.
She's a monster!
She's a vampire!
I don't have to help her.
Right?
I know, goddamn it!
Don't give up, you moron!
Are you okay with this?
Of course I'm not.
Damn it.
Why?
How did it come to this?
I swear I'll do better in my next life.
I'll be smart, and everything bad that happens will be everyone else's fault.
I'll be reborn into someone like that.
I'll help you.
Take my blood.
I give it all to you.
Every last drop of it.
Suck me dry.
Thank you.
Was it a dream?
Surprise
Hey!
Wake up.
Just five more minutes.
Five minutes
Wake up already!
Not feeling it right now.
Feeling it
How long are you gonna sleep?!
4.6 billion years
Like 4.6 billion years.
That's enough to create Earth all over again!
March 28th
It's been two days?
Fool!
Good grief.
How stupid do you have to be
to jump right into the sunlight?
Your average vampire would evaporate in an instant.
Never go outside again while the sun is up.
You are immortal, so you would burn and regenerate, and burn and regenerate forever.
That is, if you consider the undead to be alive in the first place.
Undead?
Wait, are...
Flashback
I very much am Kiss-shot Acerola-orion Heart-under-blade.
Call me Heart-under-blade.
It has been 400 years since I made my last kin.
You are my second.
Seeing your regeneration earlier,
I'd call it a great success.
Kin?
Kin
Indeed! Therefore you—
That reminds me. I have yet to get your name.
Not that I need to.
The name you bore once before is meaningless hereafter.
Welcome to the world of the night,
my servant.
Where...
Where are we?
I believe it was called a cram school.
It went bankrupt a few years ago and is abandoned now.
A suitable place to withdraw to.
Next question, Kiss-shot.
Hold on!
I told you to call me Heart-under-blade!
That's way too long.
I prefer Kiss-shot. It's short.
Can't I call you that?
Oh well.
If you prefer it, so shall it be.
I have no reason to forbid it.
So?
What is your next question?
I turned into a vampire, right?
Is it not obvious?
Do I need to spell it out for you?
You became my kin, my servant.
Consider it an honor.
Your servant...
Why do you have a child's body now?
Earlier you were more, uh, mature—
Sorry for not being more "mature"!
That's not what I meant.
Mature
And
Your limbs were severed
I took all your blood,
but it was insufficient.
Therefore I took a form I could sustain.
Still better than perishing.
Then again, I can only sustain a
minimum amount of immortality,
and most of my vampire powers are unavailable now.
Inconvenient indeed.
Flashback
My limbs are restored, as you can see.
I could at least regenerate the form,
if not the power to fill it.
This should suffice for now.
That said, do not forget that you are my servant.
I may look this way now,
but I am a vampire who has lived for five centuries.
You are but a newborn as a vampire.
Know your place when you address me.
Oh.
Make your replies clear.
Do you really understand?
I do...
Then as a sign of your obedience, pat my head.
That should do.
Why did you turn me into a vampire?
I was prepared to die being sucked dry by you.
I did not intend to.
All who have their blood drunk by a vampire will,
without exception, turn into vampires.
That is all.
I see...
It is quite convenient for me.
There is something I need you to do.
Your blood alone only allows me to regenerate so much.
I am far from my full potential.
Which is why you shall act in my stead.
What do you want from me?
Can I...
Can I return to being human?
I thought so.
I was prepared for that question.
So? Can I?!
You can.
I can guarantee that.
I give you my word if needed.
The names of three people who robbed Kiss-shot of parts of her body.
Those three are specialist vampire slayers.
They're the ones that killed you?
Are you out of your mind?
They have yet to finish me off.
However, they took my limbs.
I have very little regenerative power left too.
I have no chance of standing against them now.
You shall face those three and take back my limbs.
Huh?
"You shall" as if it was that simple.
To make you human once again, I must regain my full power.
I must be whole again.
My limbs are absolutely necessary for that.
But I can't fight at all.
Won't I just get slain instead?
Fool.
You still think as if you were human.
You are now my kin.
Now that I am weakened to a bare minimum,
while I am still a top-class vampire, you could still kill me.
So you're a weak vampire?
No!
You're weakened, so I might be stronger than you at this point,
but those three managed to take your limbs when you were whole and at full power.
How could I—
I was at a disadvantage because they came at me at once.
I took them lightly.
What I mean is that as long as you take on them one by one,
they shall stand no chance against you.
Simply put: it is an easy task.
What now?
Dismember
Would you at least hear me out?!
I'm human!
Do you want to murder a fellow human?!
Mur
der
Spin
You seem so worked up.
Did something nice happen to you?
Huh?
Thanks for saving me.
No need for thanks.
You got saved on your own,
Araragi.
Don't be so alarmed.
Your stare's sharp.
You seem so worked up.
Did something nice happen to you?
Let's just go home for now, Araragi.
Home?
To that old abandoned cram school.
Huh?
Hold on a second!
How do you know about that?
Why are you surprised?
I'm the one who told her about it.
Failing to do the right thing is the sign of cowardice.
Heart-under-blade looked like she was in trouble,
dragging your body around,
so I gave her a good spot.
Who are you?
I'm just an old fart who happened to pass by.
Don't worry.
I'm no vampire slayer or specialist.
I practice in a much wider field.
I'll introduce myself properly later.
You're back!
Who is that behind you?
I feel like I've met you before.
That's so mean.
Is that all you remember of me?
So?
How did it go?
This is a problem.
Those three are still working together.
They took you out even at your full power.
I stand no chance against them.
Which is why I told you to take them on one by one!
They're together. It's not happening.
You said we could just lay low,
but who knows when they find us he—
Don't worry about that.
I drew up a boundary around here while you were asleep.
A boundary?
Like a barrier?
Something like that.
What's up with you, exactly?
Why did you help Kiss-shot and me?
I realize you're not an enemy,
but I doubt you'd be on our side either.
Jeez, you're so cruel.
I'm maintaining the balance.
Consider that my job.
I bridge this side and the other.
Introduce yourself.
You said you would.
Spin
Oshino Meme.
Oshino Meme
I'm like a rolling stone.
I'm kind of an authority on monsters and apparitions.
Unlike those three, I'm not great at exorcising though.
Not great?
Let me rephrase that.
I'm not a fan of it.
Doesn't that make you a specialist then?
Maintaining the balance is my specialty.
I negotiate from neutral ground.
Call me a mediator.
Negotiation?
Bridging this side and the other?
Where is "this side" and what's "the other"?
Speech / Voice
Are the two sides humans and monsters?
In that case, now I
belong to which side?
Monsters?
That's good.
I prefer to call them oddities though.
Oddity
And she's the oddity slayer.
She's a rare kind of vampire who can drain energy from oddities.
That makes her pretty famous actually.
I listened to your little chat earlier.
Quite the pinch you're in.
I didn't expect things to take such a difficult turn.
There is nothing difficult about it.
It is extremely simple.
In the eyes of an undying vampire, maybe.
It's quite the trouble for us humans.
Right, Araragi?
Also, Heart-under-blade,
I liked how you agreed to return
your kin Araragi to being human.
Should I mediate for you?
Between us and those three?
Who else?
So you'll help us?
No. But I'll lend you a hand.
The balance feels off as it is right now.
It's like I'm watching bullies get their way.
Of course, since it's my job, I'm not gonna do it for free.
Hm...
How about 2 million?
2 million?!
Akasegawa
You pay when you can, and I won't bother you about it.
That much is the least I must ask to maintain the balance.
But...
Shall we hear your exact plan?
Negotiations sound nice, but it is not so easy.
Trying to convince those three is futile.
All I can do is ask
earnestly.
If asking doesn't work, more dangerous ideas get involved.
If we can at least communicate, we can play a game.
A game?
Firstly, we need to separate them.
You said dealing with them
one by one shouldn't be an issue.
We should make that happen then.
Boy, how do you plan to negotiate with them in the first place?
The details are a trade secret.
I'll level the playing field,
and Araragi can get back your limbs.
If you regain your limbs, you also regain your full power,
which means you can return Araragi to human.
Servant!
I cannot procure human money.
I have no idea how heavy a debt of 2 million is.
Can you shoulder it?
Do not worry.
His skills are real.
I may be weak now, but even I can see that.
I don't have that much saved,
but if I get to pay when I can
and you don't press me about it,
and I don't need collateral or a guarantor,
then I'll shoulder it.
Deal then.
Thanks for your patronage.
Just kidding.
Voice only
Kiss-shot Acerola-orion Heart-under-blade
Eye for an eye, tooth for a tooth.
Iron-blooded, hot-blooded, and cold-blooded
Vampire for a vampire.
Red
Unnumbered Scene
Vampire
Voice only
Let us begin then.
Dramaturgy
A giant of over 2 meters.
A dual wielder, he held
rippled, huge swords in
both his hands. Such
swords are commonly
referred to as flamberge.
He was a goliath, a man of
massive muscles. He wore
a headband to comb up his
unruly hair. He is the
vampire slayer that took
Kiss-shot's right arm.
(omitted)
It was March 31st,
the last day of March.
A kin-slayer vampire
Voice only
My sides!
Episode
Voice only
He wore a white cloak and had cunning eyes.
He lifted a gargantuan cross three times his size and more
than three times his weight to his shoulder with one hand.
He is a vampire hunter. He hunts vampires for the prize on their heads.
That makes him a bounty hunter. And furthermore—
Half vampire
Voice only
So unpleasant.
Guillotine Cutter
He resembled a priest, with hair that would rival the back of a hedgehog.
He might even seem gentle at first impression.
Human
A human who denies the existence of oddities.
A human who erases the existence of oddities.
Araragi!
Voice only
Don't worry about me!
Hanekawa Tsubasa
He's a nice guy, but that's not all.
He's strong.
Voice only
As if I could do that!
Araragi Koyomi
If I can't see you ever again,
That was the first time
I felt like I finally met Hanekawa for real.
there's no point in being a human again at all!
No mistakes. Straight, eye to eye.
Araragi.
Preview
Give up being human.
Scarstory
Hot-blooded Chapter
In theaters nationwide summer 2016
Scarstory
Hot-blooded Chapter
In theaters nationwide summer 2016