OP
ED
Signs
Tell me, what lies at the end of that river?
The sea.
And beyond that sea?
Foreign lands.
I would very much like to see how they live there.
They're coming from the sea?
How about the visitors closer to
home? Did we take them out?
All mobile units here are responding to IFF signals.
However, some hostiles seem to have escaped from the premises.
Major!
I'm getting reports of similar occurrences outside of Japan as well!
Three squads have been confirmed already!
Any word from UN headquarters?
None.
There's too much conflicting information to tell what's happening.
But combat seems to breaking out all over the world.
Doomsday is upon us, huh?
Yukina! Are you all right?
What were you doing there?
Why didn't you just go home?
How should I know?
Was he kept on life support?
Or maybe it was cryogenic sleep?
Did he mention anything to you?
Only his name.
Wait, he spoke Japanese?
Yeah.
And what was his name?
Uh, Kennosuke Tokisada Ouma?
Never heard of it.
All right. Let's have a chat with him.
This is Director Shirahane.
The man from the cube should wake up soon, right?
What?
Well, yeah, but hang on. I'll be right there.
What's up, Hiromi?
Follow me, Paula.
And you return to your post, Jiro.
Wait, Director!
You stay put right here, Yukina.
Princess!
Sheesh.
Could this day get any worse?
Princess!
I wonder what he means by "Princess."
Is this...
Lab 4, apparently.
The hell is security doing?
Huh? It's open.
Which moron left it unlocked?
The director.
Again?
She forgets and runs off every now and then, doesn't she?
What's the point of quarantining him now?
He's out in the open already.
While it may be pointless,
he is a truly fascinating specimen.
If possible, I'd love to dissect him.
Uh, Dr. Hausen?
Apologies.
I was merely joking.
Er...
Kennosuke Ouma, was it?
Hello?
We'd like to have a chat with you.
He can understand Japanese, right?
Hiromi!
Unhand the director!
Let me out of here at once!
Or else I'll break your neck!
Oh, no!
Crap, he's dangerous!
What remarkable reflexes!
Princess!
He found me!
Pardon me!
Why'd you let him out?
What else was I supposed to do?
More importantly, why was Yukina there?
Hello.
The director?
You left your phone somewhere again, didn't you?
Shirahane speaking.
Huh? Permission to shoot?
No way!
What if you hit Yukina?!
Do not open fire under any circumstances!
I'm glad you're all right.
Who might you be?
Huh? Am I not your princess?
You are not! Who the hell are you, you conniving wench?!
"Conniving wench"?
Jerk! You're the one who mistook me for someone else!
Damn it!
So the princess really did...
And who are you, anyway?
A mere soldier tasked with protecting the princess.
How?!
What in the world is happening?
Why now?
It never responded to my calls before.
Steed!
You're kidding me.
Get in here.
W-Wait! What's going on here?
Yukina!
Below...
My instincts are telling me to travel downward.
This can't be happening!
Yukina?
The giant?
So it was here.
Wh-What is this?
A relic.
Relic?
The Black Relic.
My personal relic.
Ow!
What? What's all this?
Why do I understand it?
What now?
A demon!
A demon?
Sortie!
Crap!
Sorry!
What is this place?
The mountain peaks seem familiar...
But what is this lake?
Could it be the work of demons?
This is Kurobe Dam.
The manifestation of human genius!
Isn't it amazing?
What are you talking about, missy?
Yukina.
What?
I have a name.
Just how long have I been asleep?
Don't ask me.
I think the cube was found around 60 years ago,
so you've probably been asleep for even longer.
Lies! You shan't deceive me with your drivel!
I'm not trying to!
Uh...
Are you really from the past?
I haven't the foggiest what's past or present!
So it was destroyed?
Yes.
A combined assault by the JSDF and ASDF took out the one that landed in Nagano.
And while this is unconfirmed,
one seems to have been suppressed at the UN's Kurobe facility.
How did the security there manage that?
Apparently they used the GAUS.
The GAUS...
The remaining four are on the move!
Where are they headed?
Towards Object 1, which has made landfall in Toyama!
Another large mobile unit detected!
Where did it come from?
The Kurobe research facility.
If it continues down its current course, it'll meet up with Object 1!
I thought they took one out!
Colonel.
It's from Director Shirahane of the Kurobe research facility.
From the facility?
Hello?
This is Director Shirahane.
The large geoframe that just left this facility is the artifact codenamed Giant.
What? Giant?
Please don't attack it.
It's one of humanity's most prized assets.
Artifact?
Disaster alert. Disaster alert.
Further information will be relayed through television and radio broadcasts.
This is crazy!
What is?
Apparently some mysterious giant robot popped out of the sea!
Do you really think you'll catch a glimpse of it from there?
What in seven hells is that?!
Tributary... Distributary...
Crossroad gorge...
River terraces...
Braided streams!
Hey! Don't crush any homes!
No, no! Don't kick the bridge!
Such a pain in the neck.
Why can I tell?
Oh, is this a radar?
You understand it?
Y-Yeah.
I'm not sure why, but I do understand it.
How does that work?
Um, we'll be entering city limits soon, so please be careful.
City limits?
What the...
What is with that mountain of tombstones?
They're buildings, not tombs!
Buildings?
Don't destroy them, no matter what!
U-Uh...
What are you going to do now?
Regardless of how the world may change,
my duty remains the same:
slaying the demons!
What was that just now?
A demon.
A demon?
That's...
...a demon?
They will return to devour humans once more.
They really did return...
And wait, I'm gonna get eaten?!
No way! First I get abducted by a nutcase, and now some demon's gonna munch on my bones?
This is the pits!
Quit your whining!
Human lives don't matter to them in the least.
If we do not slay the demons here,
the entire world will perish!
There's a whole bunch of them now.
How many?
Uh, four!
A-And now we're surrounded!
What are we gonna do?!
It pierced through!
These rotten minions.
Left!
Behind!
What?!
Huh?
Scurrying around like a rodent...
Why do you fight the demons, Kennosuke?
To protect someone?
Because I hate them!
Get back! Above you!
You did well to notice!
This is the end!
Damn, I let it escape.
Say, do I resemble your princess?
Not in the least.
Why'd you mistake me for her, then?
Is that princess still out there somewhere?
The princess...
is dead.
We don't know anything about this black giant.
The samurai seems to be calling it the Black Relic, though.
Immorality creaks in the dark
Blurring the advantages of evolution
Sorrow remains silent
Simply praying for the safety of the soul
I'm always just barely behind the times
Surrounded by thick gray clouds
Acid rain pours down on me
Melting away my morals tonight
Everyone's assigned an alphabet
Everyone's called by their code
Acting with no sense of reason
For whom are these battles fought
The scar that remains in the corner of my memories
shed light to the end
A voice in the distance whispered gently
A new age is coming
Love transcends time
Dreams go the distance
Voices will reach to the ends of the earth
No matter how weak the light
I have the ultimate strength to believe
This is the strength of our bond
Love will transcend time
Everyone's lonely and a stranger to others
The names we are given
Can be easily taken away
The mirror shows our weaknesses
We can't look away from it
It is our feelings that make our hearts scream out in pain
Don't stop
Even if I have to take on the pain of others
I will change the world one step at a time
Acting on emotions won't help us understand each other
But I won't stop believing in my reality
I want to keep on living
Because ever since I met you
Something's taken root deep within my heart
And it is starting to bloom
Mika (Cell): You alive?
Me: Yeah, I am. You?
Mika(Cell): Taking shelter underground
with my old man.
ID Validated
Hiromi Shirahane
History: Hiromi Shirahane
The Black Relic Awakened
Black Relic: 19.5m tall (21.9m including the horns).
Humanoid relic found during dam construction work 60 years ago.
Along with the 3m cube, it is an artifact currently being researched at the Kurobe Research Facility.
The Castle Ruins Cannot Turn Back Time