OP
ED
Signs
They were discovered 60 years ago...
Things that couldn't be deciphered or explained using the science and technology of the time.
A cube and a giant,
two mystical objects of unknown origin that came to be called artifacts.
As they were valuable assets for all of humanity—
assets that nations around the globe didn't want Japan monopolizing—
it was decided that they be placed under the control of the United Nations.
A massive research facility was constructed in the area the artifacts were discovered,
scientists from all across the globe were gathered there to study them,
and the results of those studies were all made public.
Unmanned?
Yes.
The unit we destroyed here
shows no sign of having been piloted by a living being.
Was the big one that fought the artifact also unmanned?
We don't know.
Are we sure that six of those big ones landed all over the world?
Yes.
Based on the various reports,
that seems to be the case.
All of them appear to have descended from satellite orbits.
Some of the smaller Cactus units we let escape are on the run in the mountains.
The JSDF is currently on the hunt for them.
Uh, where are we going?
Is that...
Azumi Castle?
Where have all the residents gone?
Probably ran away.
Impossible.
I am Kennosuke Tokisada Ouma,
retainer to the Washiba Clan.
I am fully aware of my discourtesy, but I still ask of you:
May I speak to someone?
Is anybody there?
Like I said, nobody's home.
Who's the castle lord now?
Jinbo? Uesugi?
Lord? There's no such thing anymore.
Just how much time has passed?!
He really is from the past!
And what is with your appearance?
Huh?
Something wrong with it?
Why are you dressed so outrageously?
Hey, I think it's cute.
I like my school's uniform.
I'm saying a lass should dress more modestly.
Stop it. I don't like that kinda prejudice.
I'm... famished.
Shoot, I need to make dinner for Koharu.
Koharu?
My dear little sister.
I have to make sure that she at least gets to eat proper home cooking.
Going one day without food won't kill her.
You do realize you brought me here against my will, right?
Yes, and I don't regret it.
Though I do feel a tad bad.
So, uh, can we head back now?
You're a hostage, you know.
What? I've been taken hostage?!
You will stay with me awhile.
I-I can't!
What manner of trickery is this?
It's already nighttime, huh...
Kennosuke, what are you going to do now?
I know not!
You insist on standing in my way?
We cannot let you leave here alive.
Draw!
You will come to regret making me draw my sword.
I'd like to watch the news.
But that's boring.
Just a bit, okay?
Please!
Fine, but only for a bit.
This is live footage from the Toyama Castle courtyard.
Can you see those two?
- Yukina?!
Hello?
Are you okay?!
Yeah, I'm okay. Don't worry.
Are you really, really okay?!
Oh, shut up already.
Why are you talking to a box?
Put him on.
You seriously wanna talk to him?
Put. Him. On.
Here.
Like this.
Give Yukina back!
The box talked?!
Who the hell are you?!
Her mother!
How in the world did you get in there?
She's not.
Wait, is this box your mother?!
Don't tell me, you were born from this thing?
Oh, please. Move on.
I'm sorry, Lady of the Box, but I cannot return her at the moment.
You'd better not have done anything to her!
I wouldn't lay a hand on any women or children!
Damn it!
What? Why won't it work?
Can we lug this thing back?
I don't know...
Even back when it was found, nobody could move it due to its weight.
Well, it does weigh 300 tons.
Maybe the GAUS trailers can handle it.
How does this thing even work?
Maybe the pilot is the key?
So it won't turn on without that samurai?
Him, and one other.
Kennosuke has broken out.
Again?
That makes it three times now.
Steed!
Why won't it answer me?
Damn it!
Out of the way, woman!
Or you'll get hurt!
Skilled or not, you're still a lass, huh?
He's such a handful.
Pervert! Predator!
Beast!
Curses!
That's the last of the tests, Miss Shirahane,
but you might have to come back for more.
Right...
Oh, Yukina!
There, there.
Looks like you had a rough time.
Uncle.
Yuki!
Koharu? What are you doing here?
Temple food sucks!
Come home already.
I'd love to if I could.
Hey, where's the samurai?
Oh, yeah. Does that guy work here?
He's pretty hot!
D-Don't! He's pretty dangerous! {don't think you need D-D here, if I time it before kf then it might look super awk}
He's a nutcase!
Huh, really?
But hey, guys are better when they have a bit of a wild side.
Wild doesn't even begin to describe him!
Demons and the Sengoku period, huh?
That is if we believe what Yukina heard from him.
Looks like he's from the early Sengoku period, too.
So what, a samurai from 450 years ago came back to life?
You don't believe it, do you?
Actually, it might be related to what Takehito was talking about.
Seriously, I wish he'd left some actual data behind.
So, where is that samurai boy now?
We have him locked up.
But he runs off every time we try to give him a checkup.
He woke up in modern society all of a sudden.
I bet he's finding it hard to believe any of this.
Very well.
Let me try talking to him.
No! He's violent!
It'll be fine.
He won't think I'm a demon looking at the way I'm dressed.
Yuki, did you see the demons too?
Demons?
You mean that massive geoframe?
Nah, the smaller ones.
Smaller ones?
Apparently they've abducted people.
Yeah, yeah. I heard some strange things have been running around.
Oh, it's those things.
I'm Osho Yakushi, and I run a nearby temple.
Would you mind talking to me?
They tell me I was asleep for a long, long time, but I don't believe it.
I just can't shake off the feeling that the demons' minions could be trying to deceive me.
I would like to see for myself, but the people here refuse to let me out.
I understand that you're worried,
but so are the people here.
After all, nobody knows a thing about you.
I am a mere soldier!
What are demons?
Demons!
They abduct people, and they raze villages!
Where did they come from?
I know not!
They came raining from the sky.
However, we'd never seen these demons you speak of.
The world has changed drastically from the era you lived in.
But I want you to believe in us, as a fellow human being.
How'd it go?
Status quo, for the time being.
We'll keep both the giant and the samurai here to study them.
Not surprising, considering we know more about the artifacts than anybody else.
Great.
I was worried they'd try to take them apart.
Well, there were some morons who might've suggested it.
Anyway, how's our self-proclaimed samurai doing?
The conversation with the monk seems to have worked.
Apparently he's behaving himself now.
That's a huge relief.
I was afraid he'd take my brother hostage too.
A kid?
How did you get in here?
Where's your ID?
I don't have one.
Where are your guardians?
Come here.
No! Lemme go!
To think they raised their hands against a child.
They're a disgrace to warriors everywhere.
You must have been scared.
Apologies.
So awesome!
Girly, what is your name?
Koharu!
Oh, you're Yukina's sister?
Might you be the samurai?
The robot samurai, perchance?
Samurai?
I have no lord to serve, though.
What is your good name, samurai?
Kennosuke Tokisada Ouma.
Kennosuke...
That is a pretty awesome name, I daresay.
This was a barrage?
Barrage? It's a dam.
What's up?
The towns have changed completely,
but I see the mountains remain the same.
You should head back.
What? No!
I wanna keep exploring!
What are you gonna do?
There is something I must confirm.
Wait!
Run away!
Kennosuke!
Huh? Where's Koharu?
Didn't she go with you?
She left on another adventure...
Let's go catch her before she gets into any trouble.
We detected just one, right?
Uh, have you seen a girl around nine years old?
Yukina, look.
Kennosuke?
That's him?
Forgive me!
Huh?
I couldn't save her despite being by her side!
What are you talking about?
Koharu was captured by the enemy!
If I start scaring you, feel free to press that thing.
But help me out for now!
What are you going to do?
Save Koharu!
There aren't a lot of Cacti in hiding.
I doubt they pose much of a threat.
What about our samurai boy on the run?
We know where he is.
We'll have him in custody any moment now.
Yukina? What's the matter?
Koharu got what?
Samurai boy!
Unhand those princesses at once!
Koharu got taken away! Aren't you gonna do anything?
Shut it!
We can rescue as many bunnies as we like after we throw him behind bars.
Get over here already—
What the hell?
About time!
You nearly killed me!
I'll have you commit seppuku for that!
I shall gladly disembowel myself if I have erred.
But do not hinder me until I rescue Koharu!
Hey, you shitty samurai!
What're you trying to do?
Save Koharu, is all!
If you even think about escaping,
I'll unload a clip of .45s up your ass!
What's gonna happen to Koharu?
Well...
Place your faith in me.
I'll save her, no matter what!
Oh, thank goodness.
Her phone's still on.
Go left!
She should be around here.
Koharu!
Do you have shit for brains?
This ain't something you can take on with just a sword.
Don't shoot from that close.
Outta the way, samurai!
Yuki!
Koharu!
There's no mistaking it.
So I really have been asleep for a long time.
Kennosuke?
Let's go.
I'll let you off the hook this time out of respect for your bravery and shit.
Koharu! My baby!
Are you hurt? You must've been so scared!
Did it do anything to you?
Mom, I gand bweedh!
Your adventuring is getting out of hand, you know that?
I went a bit far this time.
Too far! You nearly left this world!
I think that took three years off your sister's life.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, he went crazy out there, right?
So he really is the wild type?
Kennosuke's a super samurai!
He saved my life!
Yeah...
I guess he's not all that bad.
Your face looks to have lost all traces of hostility.
But I have also lost my purpose.
Why do I still live?
I have no lord to serve, nobody to protect...
All I have is the regret that I didn't die when I ought to have.
Purpose isn't something you seek.
It's something you find within yourself.
Spare me your preaching.
Well, I am a monk.
Why don't you try believing in and living with us?
I'm empty.
I have nothing to offer.
All that's left for me is to rot away.
Looks like your tummy's empty too.
Come with me.
And eat some food first.
You can rack your brain after that.
I'm back.
Welcome home!
What were you up to, Unc—
Kennosuke!
Thank you for having me.
You've gotta be kidding me.
This thorny enemy mech is Cactus.
Someone in the UN randomly picked that name 'cause they needed to call it something.
Immorality creaks in the dark
Blurring the advantages of evolution
Sorrow remains silent
Simply praying for the safety of the soul
I'm always just barely behind the times
Surrounded by thick gray clouds
Acid rain pours down on me
Melting away my morals tonight
Everyone's assigned an alphabet
Everyone's called by their code
Acting with no sense of reason
For whom are these battles fought
The scar that remains in the corner of my memories
sheds light to the end
A voice in the distance whispered gently
A new age is coming
Love transcends time
Dreams go the distance
Voices will reach to the ends of the earth
No matter how weak the light
I have the ultimate strength to believe
This is the strength of our bond
Love will transcend time
Everyone's lonely and a stranger to others
The names we are given
Can be easily taken away
The mirror shows our weaknesses
We can't look away from it
It is our feelings that make our hearts scream out in pain
Don't stop
Even if I have to take on the pain of others
I will change the world one step at a time
Acting on emotions won't help us understand each other
But I won't stop believing in my reality
I want to keep on living
Because ever since I met you
Something's taken root deep within my heart
And it is starting to bloom
The Castle Ruins Cannot Turn Back Time
Cactus: 3.8m tall
Unmanned geoframe that the enemy deploys en masse.
It boasts of high-frequency blades in its arms for weapons but has no inherent gravity or inertia control mechanism.
Appears all over the place and seems to be abducting humans.
The Foreign Taste Tells All
Sign: Demons? Bears? Mysterious Creatures
Top: Koharu
Bottom: Yukina