Frankly speaking,
this is impossible for Yukina with her current grades.
You know, "impossible" is a word you can only use after you've explored all possibilities.
And... have you?
She'll have to raise
her standardized score by at least thirty points.
Roughly put,
that means passing 500,000 people in the next 18 months.
Do you really think that's possible?
The young lady says she wants to go.
Are you trying to nip her ambitions in the bud?
It's not even a bud at this stage.
Just a pipe dream buried far underground.
Aren't teachers supposed to encourage their students to chase their dreams?
No. We make our pupils face reality and guide them to goals within their reach.
That's our job as educators.
Facing up to adversity is what makes kids grow stronger!
Sure, but I wouldn't call this adversity.
Stupidity is more fitting.
Her current grades reflect her lack of ability and effort.
Please don't project yourself upon your daughter, Mrs. Shirahane.
No two people are the same.
I guess I'll leave you to do your damn job, then.
Mom!
Sorry about that, sir.
Shirahane...
"Mars" is not a career, you know.
Right.
It's more of a destination, isn't it?
That's not the point.
Besides, at this stage, the Mars emigration project is highly unlikely to come to fruition.
Is that yours?
Yoohoo!
Did you see where my mom went, Mika?
Upstairs?
What's up?
She left her phone behind.
Whoa, a UN phone? Super cool.
Mom, you forgot this!
Mom!
Yukina... Martians don't actually exist, okay?
Jeez...
Talk about awesome.
Your mom's super cool, Yukina.
She's the exact opposite of what you'd want from a mom.
Hey, mine's just a regular old lady.
But yours is the chief of a UN research facility.
So, how'd career counseling go?
What'd you put down?
Mars.
What?
That hotter?
Nah, colder.
But get a load of this.
My mom wasn't against it.
Take your life more seriously, girl.
Why Mars, anyway?
I wanted to go see the Martian canals.
Wait, those really exist?
They don't?
I think scientists proved that they don't.
I refuse to believe their lies.
I bet they're just hiding them from us.
You sure do love your conspiracy theories.
It'd be nice to see the river terraces on Mars, too.
What are you even talking about?
And isn't that your mom's phone?
Shoot, I forgot.
I can't believe she left something so valuable behind.
Like daughter, like mother, I guess.
But now that she has, you gotta take it to her, right?
No way! I don't wanna go!
Quit your whining and follow me!
Let's go!
Step on it!
Yoohoo, Sophie!
Were you here for career counseling too?
Greetings.
And no, I have no need for counseling.
Ah, right. You're too young for that.
No, it's because my mind's already made up.
I'm going to devote my life to what I'm already doing.
How about you, Yukina?
I, uh...
Said she put down "Mars."
Mars as in the planet Mars?
Yeah. Where the Martians live.
I suggest you keep your silliness to a minimum.
Sorry I'm stupid...
Headed to work, Sophie?
Yes.
On that note, I bid you farewell.
Toodles!
That girl sure is something.
Skipping grades and all.
And she works at a UN facility?
She's in a whole different league than us.
Oh, right. I can just get her to take this to my mom.
Take this with you, Sophie!
Milady.
Your friend seems to be chasing after us.
Pay her no heed. Keep going.
As you wish.
Wait, we're getting on!
The rise in water level has changed the river's course!
You're always looking at that. Don't you ever get bored of it?
Not really, no.
Good for you.
Hey, wait up!
The dam!
It always looks so amazing!
Control yourself.
You can stare at it all you want on the way back.
Whoa! Talk about huge!
Your mom developed those, right?
Apparently.
Why didn't you wanna come here?
I don't like the place...
Or that stuff.
Oh, you get treated like royalty 'cause of your mom.
The way the people here look at me really puts me on edge.
Say, what'd you put down for your career plans?
Finding work or something.
Where?
Beats me.
Any place willing to hire a moron with no talents, guts, or brains is fine by me.
It'll be hard with your current grades, won't it?
All my relatives say I must be a late bloomer,
so whoever gives me a chance is bound to hit the jackpot.
Yeah, yeah.
Looking at you always makes me want to work harder.
Why do I get the feeling you're making fun of me?
Just your imagination.
Anyway, I'm gonna go give my old man a surprise.
He works at the mess, right?
Yeah. He's a cook.
And he's probably free around now.
Meet up at four?
Sure thing. See you later.
Toodles!
Sheesh.
Why didn't you just give it back to me at school?
You're always like this.
Never listen to a word others say.
Here.
Thanks.
Anyway, you'd better put in the effort if you want to go to Mars.
I'm not so sure it's a dream that can be fulfilled with effort alone.
Don't worry, nothing is impossible for you. You're my daughter.
Cut it out.
Oh, right.
If you're going to go, do it after Koharu grows up.
How about you spend some time raising your own child?
Hey, I raised you just fine.
No, you didn't. Uncle did.
Ah, teenagers. Always blind to their parents' love.
Well, do your best and show your teacher who's boss.
Look at her, acting like a parent when she feels like it.
How am I supposed to kill time until four?
It's not an ICBM, is it?
Different size.
Possibly a meteorite.
Orbital inclination is at 98 degrees.
Airspeed at two kilometers per second.
Just two?
That's pretty slow for a meteorite.
Object 1 making entry.
Here's the estimated point of impact.
Object 1 dropping multiple fragments!
Did it break apart?
We're unable to confirm.
Object 1 decelerating!
Say what?!
The evil demons shall return.
Return?
Yes, they will return from a faraway world
to devour humans once more.
Oh, no! I'll get eaten!
Crap!
Oh, I still have time.
Mr. Aramata!
Oh, hey, Yuki.
Hello.
Here to see Hiromi?
I guess.
I keep telling her to go home every now and then, but she never listens.
Is Koharu watching period dramas like always?
All the time.
Some taste that girl has.
Who's that?
Yukina, Hiromi's daughter.
Her? Really?
Is that...
I think I've seen it somewhere before.
It's "The Cube."
Oh, I've heard of it.
It was found in a fracture zone during tunnel construction work 60 years ago, right?
Aren't you well-informed.
Is it okay for an outsider like me to see it?
No problem.
This artifact's existence was made public.
Not like we know anything about it.
The giant downstairs is much better than this piece of junk.
Giant?
Another artifact, but not much information has been released about that one.
It's also the reason this research facility was built here.
The reason? Why?
We can't move it.
It's more like a demon than a giant, really.
Demon?
Professor Takehito Shirahane...
Your father was researching local folklore, wasn't he?
That's right.
Did he say anything about a demon?
I haven't seen him since he disappeared eight years ago.
Oh, is that so?
Dumbass.
What's going on?
Is that...
Get back!
What just happened?
Impact confirmed!
Landing point was three kilometers out at sea!
MSDF submarine Michishio, which was conducting an exercise in the area,
is now heading there to investigate.
What about the fragments?
They seem to have landed between Nagano and Toyama.
One has landed near the UN facility!
Are you okay, Mr. Aramata?
Well, I'll be damned!
Glasses... Glasses...
A meteorite?
A meteorite? For real?
Sortie! On the double!
This is a United Nations research facility!
Trespassers will be met with deadly force!
Turn back at once!
What the hell are those things?
It's dangerous outside!
Go hide underground!
What about you?
I need to meet up with Hiromi!
I'm returning to the lab.
You guys hurry up and take shelter underground!
Extinguish the fires pronto!
Don't let them inside, no matter what!
Ignore the big one.
I'm taking over command now.
I trust you have no objections?
Of course not, Major Graham.
You have free reign.
This research facility is hereby
placed under emergency alert.
All orders will be issued from Security HQ.
Squad Alpha, head to the west gate and halt the enemy's advance.
Standby.
Squad Bravo...
I don't want to admit it, but does this mean he was right on the money?
Looks like it.
I just wish this had happened after I retired.
Major, message from Captain Bowden in GAUS1.
Hey, Major!
What do you think these things are? Mountains of shit?
Keeping them safe is only gonna make it stink in here!
Can they be mobilized?
They're not in an ideal state as of yet, but I guarantee they're mobile.
Currently, they have an estimated
operation time of one hour.
But I can't say how quickly they'll burn through energy in actual combat.
You have completed the mass driver tests, yes?
Yes, but only in simulation.
Will you still use it?
I'd rather that than open the gate.
GAUS1, GAUS2, prepare to sortie.
Launch using the mass drivers at minimum output.
Hurry up, you slowpokes!
Send us out already!
The battle's gonna end before we even get out there!
Gravity stabilizers at max output.
Inertia canceler calibrated.
Graviton generation all clear.
The mountains of shit are finally getting ready to rumble!
Where am I?
It hasn't been destroyed?
Princess!
You are all right?
Excuse me?
I'm glad I was simply mistaken.
Wh-Who the hell are you?
I am Kennosuke Tokisada Ouma!
Could you be the demons' minions?!
Once I'm done playing with you, you won't be able to laugh or cry anymore!
Your ass is as loose as a whore's!
And did you lose your head giving too much head?
You trying to kill us, you little bitch?!
Pardon me.
Screw you.
I'm gonna split your coconut and pour the drizzling shits down it.
Nice shot.
A 120mm to the ass was enough to take it out?!
Princess...
Are you all right?
H-He's over there!
You confounded lapdogs!
Wh-What are you trying to do to Yukina?
"Yukina"?
Who the hell is this dude?
I don't know...
Apparently GAUS is short for "Gravity Attenuated Upright Shell."
It was developed at the Kurobe research facility!
Immorality creaks in the dark
Blurring the advantages of evolution
Sorrow remains silent
Simply praying for the safety of the soul
I'm always just barely behind the times
Surrounded by thick gray clouds
Acid rain pours down on me
Melting away my morals tonight
Everyone's assigned an alphabet
Everyone's called by their code
Acting with no sense of reason
For whom are these battles fought
The scar that remains in the corner of my memories shed light to the end
A voice in the distance whispered gently
A new age is coming
Love transcends time
Dreams go the distance
Voices will reach to the ends of the earth
No matter how weak the light
I have the ultimate strength to believe
This is the strength of our bond
Love will transcend time
Career Plans Questionnaire - Yukina Shirahane
1) Mars 2) Mercury 3) Jupiter
Sign: Ministry of Defense
The Sky Raining Demons
Sign: Research Lab #2
19.4m tall.
Research lab prototype developed by analyzing and copying the artifact's gravity control system.
GAUS is short for Gravity Attenuated Upright Shell.
Two-seater operated by a pilot and a navigator.
Is equipped with a gatling gun and a revolver knife.
The Black Corpse Awakened