March 26, 2096 - The Southern Island Group Ogasawara Island
Lagrange Space Telescope 2.
Data link connection successful.
Subject secured.
All vital signs are stable.
All systems normal.
Test subject readings all normal.
The Psion wave activities are above normal.
All vital readings are within the acceptable range.
Psychedelic reality "Watatsumi" series.. Begin synchronization.
Psion waves are normal,
3, 4, 5 ...
All necessary levels have been reached.
Preparing to activate.
Start the activation process.
Activation code readings all normal.
Completed 90%.
Unlock all limiters.
Activate Meteorite Fall.
All limiters successfully removed, proceeding with the activation process.
Activating Meteorite Fall!
Something that has existed since the war?
It has been a century since magic became a modern technology.
Nations have begun arming themselves with magic,
And they have an enormous amount of power.
With the power to destroy a city,
Those who use magic to fight in the military are called Strategic-Class Magicians,
And they've become a symbol of influence throughout the world.
March 27, Albuquerque International Airport - New Mexico, USA.
Silvi!
Did you come to pick me up?
Welcome back, commander.
Now that I'm not on duty, Lina is fine.
Look here, I bought a ton of souvenirs.
Here.
Ah ... Actually ...
New orders from the General, Commander.
Head to Honolulu right away.
Huh?! I just came back from that stupid mission!
What kind of task is it?
Don't know, when you arrive, you can ask the General.
At least let me take a break!
You can take a break in Honolulu.
We don't know that for sure!
Eh, Hold on ...
Sorry, Lina.
Silvi?
Huh?
Silvi! Wait!
Have a good time!
Thank you for the gifts!
Silvi ... YOU LIAR!
March 28, Ogasawara Islands Group of the Mukojima Islands Nadokojima
Delicious isn't it, Onii-sama?
There!
Erika, why do you keep tricking her?
It's more fun that way!
But really, what's the point of hitting a melon with a bat?
Tradition.
Yeah.
Onii-sama ...
Ah ... can I ask you something?
About this new swim suit ...
We chosen it together when we were shopping, remember?
What do you think?
What are you doi-
It suits you very well.
Just as I thought it will.
Thank you very much, Onii-sama.
Shizuku-sama.
I have prepared the dessert.
Thank you very much, Kurosawa-san.
Come on Honoka.
Yeah.
That was really fun.
Erika cut it perfectly.
Cut?
I thought Mizuki was trying to do it?
Um.
Delicious! this is so delicious Shizuku.
Isn't it, that's Kurosawa's specialty.
There's all kinds of fruits in it.
The atmosphere here is so much fun.
Right.
I look forward to that!
Hey, Miyuki you look forward to it too, right?
Hmm.. sure, why not.
Tatsuya-san and Miyuki, thank you.
What's this all of sudden?
Um, what do you mean by thank you?
What's the matter, Shizuku?
For suddenly inviting everyone ...
Thanks to you everyone gathered on summer vacation.
If anything, we're grateful you invited us.
Here you go.
Onii-sama, that's ...
A rare sight.
A special unit of the Ministry of Defense.
Onii-sama?
It's an order from the military.
Miyuki.
My limiters, if you would please..
Huh? But that's…
It's an order that requires the use of Material Burst.
This may also be related to the Yotsuba clan's reputation.
I understand.
What our Aunt says doesn't matter to me, However for your sake, I'd be glad to.
At ease.
Yes sir.
Onto the task on hand.
Between the orbit of the Earth and Mars should be empty space.
However we've discovered an asteroid orbit that changed course recently.
Abnormal.
The orbit suddenly changed course.
And it is now on a collision course with Earth.
According to our calculations, there is over a 90% chance of colliding with Earth.
So your saying collision is imminent?
Right.
Asteroid 2095GE9 codename: Sieg.
The calculated trajectory and point of impact is on the East China Sea.
As for Japan, the Kyushu area will be severely affected.
We cannot let that happen.
Therefore, Special Officer Ooguro of the 101st Independent Magic-Equipped Battalion is ordered the following:
Authorized use of the Third Eye - Material Burst, Obliterate the following target: Sieg.
Asteroid 2095GE9: destruction confirmed.
A sniper from the ground?
So they intervened ...
Although, there's not enough data.
It's not necessary to continue.
Next is the orbital navigation experiment.
One day ... no, tomorrow.
The experiment will take place on March 30 at 19h00.
It's finally time.
If this experiment succeeds,
the Navy will finally have to recognize us.
Wait, Chief!
The experiments take a toll on these kids. They need more time to recover!
At least one more week before we continue the experiment!
Morinaga.
Is there any evidence that the kids recover after a week?
I do not remember having that data.
But, that's ...
A scientist should not let emotions overwhelm him/her
while making important decisions.
The experiment will go on as planned.
It will not be delayed for any reason.
March 29, Chichijima Island, Ogasawara Subprefecture.
Who could this be?
WTF is this mail?!
Mari, get up!
Look at this.
It's still early…
It's morning already.
Look.
Bitter…
This is…?
So that must be the Naval Base Honmaru?
Having a shopping mall built next to it, means..
This is still a private island, right?
Although this is a military area, there are still private establishments that sign contracts for business.
In the same area but still separate.
Yoshida-kun, Leo-kun!
We're going to have lunch.
Oh, finally!
We've been waiting forever!
Huh?! If that's all it takes for you to complain, then you still have a long way to go.
That doesn't even make any sense.
What kind of excercise is this anyway?
Hey everyone! What should we ea-
Mayumi!
Did you find anything?
Nothing yet.
I'll look over there.
Please do!
Mizuki and Tatsuya-kun are together in the Magical Engineering Department.
Miki became a bloom.
Hey Miki ... what's it feel like to be a bloom?
Give me a break please.
Bloom and Weeds are not much any different.
What's the matter, Leo?
There is something ... going on out there.
Guards?
No, military police?
Are the soldiers allowed out of the base?
Unusual.
I feel something is wrong.
It's best we hurry back to the villa.
I agree, it's a bit sooner than expected but.. shall we?
The door is open?
Ah, sorry.
He was sleeping.
Oh my…
Well, he's a good pilot, at least.
Search the plane!
Those inside the plane!
Open the door!
These guys ...
Erika?
What seems to be the problem?
L-Lady Erika?
You…
What do you want with this plane?
I heard something about a search warrant?
Yes ... it seems like a patient has escaped from the base.
Seem..?
Y-Yes!
We've been informed so!
Not on this plane.
But ...
If you could at least let us perform a quick search..
Did you not hear me?!
Or maybe..
... you do not believe my words, is that it?!
N-Not at all, please excuse us!
Hey, that's enough let's go.
Are those soldiers earlier from the Chiba branch?
Hmm, pretty much.
They seem to have forgotten my face.
By the way, Erika.
Why did you cover for her?
Hmm, you noticed too?
You can come out now.
Come on.
It's safe to come out now.
Welcome back, Mademoiselle.
I'm back, Takeuchi-san.
Did my guest arrive?
According to the description provided...
... has yet to appear.
I see.
Instead, two marine soldiers arrived.
They said they were looking for a patient that escaped from the base.
But after finding nothing, they left.
Is that so.
However, where on earth did she go?
She didn't show up in the appointed time.
Any possibility she might've been caught?
Right now, there's still a number of guards around the terminal, probably..
...means she hasn't been captured yet.
Mademoiselle, I have something to say.
What is it?
There was another plane about 100 meters away.
There's a possiblity she got on the wrong plane.
Find out where that plane went!
The sooner the better!
Onii-sama!
You're already back.
Yeah, about an hour ago.
You all came back sooner than planned?
Ah, Tatsuya-san!
Oh, you're back?
Thanks for your hard work.
Yeah.
Who's the girl?
Let see…
What's your name?
Kokoa.
Kokoa?
How old are you?
I'm ... Fourteen.
14?!
I'd imagine her being younger.
Did you run away from the Naval Base?
No..
Experiments...laboratory.
What kind of experiments?
Terrible magical experiments.
Are you a mage, Kokoa?
Mage?
Mages are people with magical abilities.
Are you not a magician?
We are...
... called the Watatsumi series.
Onii-sama.
I know, human cloning ... most probably.
Can you tell us what kind of experiments did they make you do in the laboratory?
Sometimes we are put into a big machine.
A big machine?
Probably ... a large CAD device.
Using the large CAD,
They can activate and control the magical sequences of the person inside the machine.
And they're basically just a part of that CAD.
Kokoa was created for some purpose.
So she's just like a replacement part for a machine?
What made you decide to escape?
Someone told me to run away ...
Who?
Morinaga-san.
A female researcher ...
Why did she tell you to run away?
Yes.
Kokoa ...
Kokoa.
Run!
If you continue the experiments, you'll lose your entire personality...you'll become an empty doll.
But before that happens...
We've got to do something ...
Loss of personality?
Tatsuya-kun, is something like that even possible?
It's not impossible.
Kokoa.
Not like that, Tatsuya-san! You're scaring Kokoa-chan.
Oh, I'm sorry, Honoka. I didn't mean to scare her.
Ask her if she's the only test subject for the CAD experiments?
Kokoa-chan, are you the only one in the machine?
No…
We ...
By we... she probably means the entire Watatsumi series.
When you said we, does that mean there are more of you?
Yes…
There are 9 of us ...
So there's a total of 9 in the Watatsumi series..
After you left the machine, how did you feel?
Feel?
Relief.
It's like I was about to melt away...
What's melting away?
We ...
Missing ... inside
Self-loss, in other words... complete loss of emotions.
No way!
In order to activate large-scale spells,
Forced coercion may be required.
I heard several rumors of certain organizations that are researching it.
Most likely they're the ones responsible for leading these experiments.
That's insane!
With no regard for a persons life, how could they do such a thing?!
Please...
Save.
Rest assured.
They can't take you from here.
I'll keep you safe no matter what happens.
No..
Save...
Us...please.
Us?
You want to help the rest that are still held captive in the lab, right?
Yes...
If we try to rescue the remaining research subjects sponsored by the Navy..
It's certain to cause a lot of problems.
Even so, we need to do something!
If Honoka wants to save them then I'll help too.
You already know how determined I am, right? There's no turning back now.
Of course, I'll be lending a hand too.
I don't mind helping too, but ...
Shibata, Kitayama and Mitsui should stay because it'll be dangerous.
Oh my, so you'll be fine with me joining then?
Eh?!
That's true..
After all, Miyuki is so powerful, it's terrifying.
Erika, is there something you want to tell me?
Nothing … really.
Just kidding.
Yoshida-kun, I'll be fine.
Please go and help Kokoa-chan.
Shibata-san?
Yeah, I understand.
Onii-sama.
I also want to help Kokoa-chan.
Understood, let's do this together.
Order from General Department.
We are ordered to destroy the magic base, the object of study
and all the research assistants for the Japanese Navy.
Do you think that this facility is dangerous to our country?
To the whole world.
This base of research is a kind of spell that goes beyond the Earth.
If it is enabled,
a city can disappear immediately, it is very dangerous.
The commander, we must destroy the research base, but that ...
Should we destroy the brains of researchers?
Order is completely destroyed.
Also I did not hear any more.
That is, depending on your decision ...
Ralph, depending on the decision of the top people here is the commander.
Know the captain. I do not do too much.
That's all.
Start a campaign.
Our mission will begin 27 hours from now,
Me and Hardy will attack directly from the submarine base.
In short, I would destroy the defenses of that place with my magic.
Hardy will help me.
Ben and Ralph will invade the island with Thrust Suit.
Destroy and destroy the rest of the base.
But if all is destroyed then withdraw immediately.
For sure, I'll blow it all up with Heavy Metal Burst.
Are you allowed to use that level of magic?
This is evidence that this threat is extremely dangerous, should be removed immediately.
The superior will not tolerate those who study the magical threat to the whole world.
The Japanese army will also understand that.
Yes.
Tateshima Island has become a military base.
People are asked to leave after sunset.
It is necessary to reduce the number of casualties.
Then prepare for the campaign!
Going too!
True!
Do you see Kokoa-chan?
Let me help you!
Erika is ...
You're out of sight.
Do it clean!
Out of capacity always!
Feeling so happy?
Do not bully him anymore!
Let me wash it for you.
Kokoa, close your eyes.
Is it okay?
Honoka, what is this?
Oil calls it.
Do not you know?
Do not know…
This is also the first time swimming in the aquarium ...
Aquarium?
Kokoa, did not you take a hot shower?
Yes…
Always use sterile tanks ...
Then go try it, it is fun.
With girls washing is not only to clean the body,
It also makes us beautiful.
Today you will make me beautiful.
So quick, huh.
Are everyone prepared together?
Where is Kurosawa?
Going to work is important.
Important?
Actually…
That's beautiful, Kokoa.
Good luck when you wear it.
So have dinner.
Um.
Kokoa, what's up?
Where is Saegusa Mayumi?
Saegusa Mayumi ... Are you Saegusa?
She is not here.
What do you need to find her?
Morinaga says to find Saegusa Mayumi for help ...
Is she?
That plane was not Saegusa Mayumi's?
Remember, there was also a plane with us.
Please tell me soon.
Who cares!
Did she get confused with Saegusa's plane?
It looks like that.
Maybe she is resting after graduation.
Onii-sama.
I think she's worried.
If so, I would like to send a message or call a message.
Yes.
Thanks to you, Miyuki.
I know.
Everybody.
It's time for dinner.
- Looks delicious!
- Let's eat!
Onii-sama.
Can you sit?
No problem. Sit down.
Tomorrow he will go to the Magic Society and Masumigaura headquarters.
Yes.
Obviously, confronted with the Navy.
Is it possible to save Kokoa?
Though it's just sympathy, it's not a temporary feeling, is it?
That…
I want to do it.
He did not want to abandon her.
He was not supposed to be sympathetic, but ...
I think it's not bad for me.
There are some things that make you curious about Kokoa.
Using the human body as part of the giant CAD ...
Such secret scientific research can destroy the most important part of humanity.
This can not be forgiven.
You feel that way.
Thank you for setting up this special clothing.
Captain Sanada.
No problem, this is also a great opportunity to test it.
Did you come to the Association?
Because they want to hear the report from me.
About the next plan, all must go through them.
As a waiter for them, you can not ignore it, right?
Decisions for people over 18 years of military service must pass them.
... but was violated by the military.
I'm only 16.
That's it.
Ah yes.
Take it with you.
This is Deep and Beta memory?
Deep is fine, but Beta is still testing,
Take it to the battlefield is not it?
He also wants to collect data.
Just like thanks for the dedicated clothes.
Clear.
So be careful, Lieutenant.
I'm comming home.
Ừ.
Is she here?
Yes, just before.
Are you Watatsumi Kokoa?
Watatsumi series, code 22, alias Kokoa ...
Is your sister Saegusa Mayumi?
Yes, you are.
Sorry yesterday for not saving me.
Thank you.
What's your relationship?
Morinaga was her mentor during her secret research in the Navy,
But feeling unacceptable, she rescued Kokoa.
So that's it.
So come to Tokyo with me.
About that, I want to discuss with you.
What?
Not just Kokoa, do you want me to bring people to Tokyo?
Except me?
It's correct.
Ah, Shizuku ...
Star?
Can I borrow the Kitayama house?
For what?
There are still 8 other people besides Kokoa.
Tatsuya, what are you going to do?
Did you try to save them?
Yes.
I understand.
Mayumi?
Our mission is to bring Kokoa to Tokyo.
Also, nothing else.
That is, we will only interfere ...
Not.
Tatsuya's idea is that our enemy should not face.
Understood.
Beware that Tatsuya.
I will not get you caught.
Again, I do not think you're alone
Could rescue those 8 children.
It is not enough for one person.
Add me in again.
I do not think you two obeyed obediently.
Of course.
It is rare to see the same opinion.
Me too!
Onii-sama.
Need someone to stay at the Shizuku plane?
If so, I will stay.
Then Yoshida, you and me hold the plane?
Did you see that?
Understood.
Mikihiko, thanks for you.
Um.
A great vacation.
Honestly.
Please do not be too aggressive.
Erika, what is it?
Well, the miniature version of Orochimaru.
Mizuchimaru.
I hid it in Shizuku's plane.
You always prepare well.
Who knows what happens.
Then two people.
Yes, please be careful.
This kokoa, looks good to me.
Cute.
JA8594 aircraft.
Immediately return to Minami Tateshima Island.
How do we do this, lady?
Ignore them.
JA8594.
Come back!
There is no other way.
This is JA8594.
Sorry but we will not come back.
If back there will not be enough fuel.
Do not have a hunch!
Minami Tateshima Island is closer to Haneda Airport!
But if we return, we will not have enough fuel to fly to Tokyo.
JA8594, do not say much. Go back!
But not enough fuel ...
JA8594, this is the last warning.
Next shot will be real.
We are serious.
That's very disturbing.
Just a warning.
Next shot will be real.
I'm not kidding.
Can you wait here?
I got it.
Had two wait.
Both wear this set.
Hey, Tatsuya.
How did you get these?
Curious?
No, no.
Done.
Huh?
Tatsuya, that is ...
Secret weapon.
Erika, Leo, I will send the information to.
I found the research site.
Got it?
It looks like the lab is located in this area.
I will go ahead to rescue you Kokoa,
The two of you will lead the kids to the boat.
Confirmation is still civilians or not?
No sign of civilians.
True to the plan.
So plan your trip.
Yes madam!
Your ship is entering the territory without permission.
Get out of the area quickly.
Remember, quickly leave the area.
No, they are still entering.
Launch missile defense.
Will we destroy it?
It is a threat.
All at my command!
Confirm missile defense.
I will send the coordinates.
Confirm coordinates.
Target:Rocket Launch System.
Activate Heavy Metal Burst!
This shock?
The commander made a little too much then.
Ralph, do not laugh!
But the captain ...
How can we penetrate?
True…
Lina's Heavy Metal Burst?
Why are stars here?
He was still, not holding hands.
Fire?
There's something wrong.
I do not understand, but this is the opportunity!
Have successfully penetrated their communications networks.
Is there a report about the appearance of a strange submarine?
I also heard.
Be informed of evacuation orders for civilians!
It seems they were attacked from a submarine,
It caused damage to the Navy.
An evacuation order has been issued.
Who are you?
Do you know Kokoa?
Is she okay?
Stay safe.
You are Morinaga?
It's correct. It's me.
You were arrested for liberating Kokoa?
No problem.
If I run away, he will not let me live.
We were asked by Kokoa to save eight more.
Will you save the kids?
Please!
Save them all, leave me again!
Please save them!
If you worry about them, why do you experiment?
Linking with such great magic will not produce any good results.
As you say.
We were too arrogant.
No, too hasty.
That magic can destroy the big countries in the Alliance.
The great destructive power that it brings ...
... makes the Navy covet.
We think so too.
But that's our sin.
They are sacrifices.
If I save them, then I have a shelf!
So ...
Where are the remaining eight?
I will lead the way.
They are probably doing experiments.
What kind of magic are you experimenting with?
We make Meteorite Fall, an asteroid bomb.
It can change the orbit of the asteroid towards the Earth.
Small planet?
The strange move of asteroid 2095GE9 two days ago ...
Is your work?
Right.
Why do you know that?
We should not use the elevator.
The experiment is about the ability to move the orbit.
If the asteroid's orbit can be reversed,
In the future, we will avoid the risk of losing control of the Earth,
We will use it to push the satellite out of Earth orbit.
But the satellite will be burned in the atmosphere.
What does it take to change its orbit?
Our goal this time is ...
USNA satellite, military satellite Sevens Plague.
What?
Was the head of this experiment insane?
That satellite contains about 60 tons of uranium.
If it fails and the satellite falls, the damage will not be counted!
Destruction would be equivalent to 30 nuclear missiles and destroying everything,
World war will inevitably.
Impossible!
Wrong step.
It can not be wrong.
What to do ?!
Why is this happening?
Did not confirm wrong?
You are the one who confirmed.
Director, what is this?
Morinaga?
Director, what happened?
Maybe ... he failed?
The Sevens Plague will fall down in 24 hours.
I said that?!
Initially, this experiment required 12 newcomers. Only with 8 is impossible!
The process is completely accurate.
The experiment is perfect.
This data will play an important role in subsequent experiments.
Do not be kidding!
No next time!
That's enough!
This result ...
... was due to a sudden explosion.
Due to the impact of the explosion on the base,
Activation of the magic becomes chaotic.
Is the fault of the flood intrusion!
Do you really think so?
I'm not wrong.
Correct.
The experiment is over.
You do not need to hold them anymore, right?
Sia!
Come back soon, Sia!
Who?
He was asked by Kokoa.
Kokoa?
She wants him to save you.
Is that okay?
Just want them to be ...
Please ... save us.
Tatsuya!
Erica, Leo!
May meet.
Thanks for taking care of these people.
She is Morinaga.
Thanks?
Where are you going?
Brother.
Do we abandon us?
The data is still there so the children are still not saved.
They just need to create more people like you are finished.
If so, go!
Let us worry.
Go ahead!
I will go later.
Still here?
What are you doing here?
Transfer the Sevens Plague data here fast.
What do we have to do?
Let me say this, whether or not I still get it.
But I do not want to waste time asking you.
Finished yet?
Already.
Hey, what are you doing?
Delete!
Stop!
Careful!
Be careful!
No, come back soon!
Oh, military scene?
Not a Mobable Dress ...
Who are you ?!
That young man is ...
Ralph, those are the key men of Meteorite Fall!
So that is ...
Can I kill them?
Do it.
Obey!
Hurry back!
Morinaga, thanks for you!
You, this way!
Do not rush.
They will slowly enjoy it.
Looks like I will be your opponent.
Siegfried!
You made me happy.
Crazy guy
Ralph, this idiot!
Why stop the attack?
Because I felt something was wrong with his sword.
Move like Lina?
Are you Stars?
So that's it.
Ladies of the Chiba family in the command post here.
Shut up! You're so mouthy.
Dead!
Juumonji ?!
Katsuo Juumonji ?!
Saijou, Chiba?
What are you guys doing here?
What is that suit?
This is…
Is this PhalanX of Katsuo Juuminji?
He is the special forces of Stars.
Why come to Japan?
Shut up, Kirikage!
Very sorry, commander.
We have failed.
Ben, are you ...?
No ... was clear.
Move to stage 2.
Mirphak, the system has recovered?
Not yet.
So I will attack directly from the sky.
According to data obtained from the experimental site,
can now see the Sevens Plague.
If you attack with Material Burst, the fragments will fall down.
To prevent the contamination of uranium and neutron emission,
You must destroy them with Beta Trident.
Have not seen Sevens Plague yet?
What's up?
That is?
Rope?
Unlock.
Ready.
At times, but also work excessively ...
There are Erika and Leo, but civilians too!
Heavy Metal Burst, fire!
Disperse mist ...
Fire!
Huh?
Heavy Metal Burst destroyed?
Plasma transmission ...
Target…
What is happening…
All of them were taken to the shelter.
Activated disperse fog.
Looks like ... finished the task?
Satellite image is back to normal.
Put the image on the screen.
Commander, there is a message from the ship's center.
Read it.
Military satellite, Sevens confirmed plague is falling?
How about the following?
Well ... the location is ...
The latitude is 27 plus minus 5, longitude is 142 plus minus 5.
Head office.
What is the directive of the superiors?
All fleet is in the Pacific
Must return to Hawaii base within 48 hours.
Orders can not be made.
Transmit command to withdraw!
As soon as possible.
Clear!
Commander.
What is up?
I would like to use a ground missile.
Can you get closer?
Huh? It's on fire!
Where not.
What is up?
Please stop here.
Then I go ahead.
Tate, shut the door!
I know that he will not have anything ...
But at least this is what I can do.
Freeze.
What's going on?
Is ice
The ship is ...
stuck in a sea of ​​ice ...
This is…?
Command!
Hardy, I'm going to rescue the New Mexico.
Look at the enemy magician.
You can only do this ...
Miyuki?
Did not hear anything ... New Mexico?
This is Sirius.
Commander, this is Canopus.
I will thaw.
Once they are moving, they will withdraw immediately.
Muspelheim!
Rope!
Yes, Lina?
This voice ... Tatsuya?
Do you know the US military satellite?
Why? What about that?
It will fall to Earth.
Is it?
The withdrawal order has been issued.
Come on! Umi no Yamada!
What the hell?
Really?
You can confirm.
Ben, sorry, I disconnected a bit.
Rina.
Please join me to destroy the Sevens Plague.
I need you to work together.
What is it?
I have trouble observing
This is to prevent his Heavy Metal Burst.
What should I do?
Miyuki?
Onii-sama?
I will come to you right away!
Lina will come too so do not attack.
How come Lina?
You need Lina's power?
I have understood.
I will wait for you, Onii-sama.
In 24 hours?
Lina, I want you to take me up to 140km.
In about 10 minutes.
140km is out of space then what?
To stop it, just to the stratosphere is enough?
The magic I'm about to make can not be done many times.
Can only be done once.
So I want to be sure to succeed.
Well ... you can not do it?
Okay!
I'll take you to that height perfectly!
But even when I'm back, it's not enough to keep you.
So I want to ask you, Miyuki.
Miyuki, you will be in free fall.
Can you help me?
Leave me alone, Onii-sama.
I will use my best to catch you safely.
Thanks to you, Miyuki.
Yes.
Finished yet?
Anytime.
Ok.
5.
4.
3.
first.
Shoot!
Beta Trident, regenerate the activation code.
Construction of complete molecular structure decomposition code.
Construction of complete atomic structure decomposition code.
Build the activation code to destroy Beta,
finish.
Beta Trident!
Fire!
Just like you think ...
... Onii-sama!
Onii-sama!
Mission…
Ah no ...
Finish.
Ok.
OK.
Be healthy.