Subtitle edited by - Aorion -
"MOBILE SUIT GUNDAM THUNDERBOLT- Episode 1 (2015)"
^ (Run time : 00:18:24)
MOBILE SUIT GUNDAM
THUNDERBOLT
This is a nice song selection.
Io, pirate radio again?
At least use headphones.
You've got to feel the sound.
The previous broadcast?
This one's good.
Yeah, you got it at a good timing.
Maybe the lightning brings it.
- The Minovsky...
- It's light?
Don't care.
- Copy it for me.
- Right here.
This part is great
just before we sortie.
I know what you mean.
I can see it.
Flying and barely dodging the debris.
The vibration on my butt.
I feel the switches at my fingertips.
They all become my eyes and move.
Can't they improve the air
in the hangar?
It's just your sinuses.
Cornelius, tissues.
Give them back, alright?
- Thanks.
- See you.
Here's the operational objective.
Eliminate the enemy snipers
hiding in our home, Side 4 "Moore".
We've lost over 40 allied
machines this past month.
This Thunderbolt Sector...
We can't forgive the cowards
who destroyed our home.
This war is entering its final stage.
Regaining this sector will
change the tide of the war.
Glory again to Side 4, Moore.
Death to the cowardly Zeon.
The Brotherhood, eh.
Geez. My birthplace
keeps on tying me down.
Free jazz is perfect for Thunderbolt.
I love mobile suits, space,
and the battlefield.
It's free here.
Oh no, our positions are obvious.
When they shoot, we'll
trace back their location.
Now, who'll be the unlucky one?
- Who's hit?
- Ensign Io.
Commander... Commander!
Emergency.
Commander hit by beam cannon.
His machine's demolished.
They're sniping from the debris.
Radio won't work with this
Minovsky particle density.
You search, too--
Dave!
Find the enemy sniper!
How can they see us?
The Minovsky particles
are still so dense!
Calculate their positions!
- It's Side 4!
- Attack our home?
My barrel's past its limit.
Daryl will now be sending
orbit prediction data.
Nice, Chief Petty Officer Daryl.
I got the rest.
This'll earn me the Cross.
Bragging to your lady? Or...
Sean, it's complicated
who Ensign Hoover reports to.
Shut up. I'm gonna get them.
Both the Federation and the girl!
Amazing!
Is Daryl a clairvoyant?
Or one of those Newtypes?
I'll get commended back home.
Then it's vacation!
Ensign Hoover,
is your machine drifting?
Communication's cutting out.
Please check cable connection.
Huh?
Really?
Hey!
Hoover!
It's a human.
A Federation normal suit!
Daryl, can you snipe him?
I can't aim from here!
But Hoover is--
He's been shot in the head!
You saw it!
So the cockpit isn't
that different from Zaku.
Hey, you may be aces of the
snipers division,
but your taste in music
is mediocre.
Big talk for a guy who got lucky.
No wonder a guy with fake legs
sneakily shoots from far away.
Making fun of my legs?
Now I know your firing location.
I'll cruise home via your blind spots.
You won't escape next time.
I'll get you for sure.
I'm Chief Petty Officer Daryl Lorenz.
I'll keep my eye on you.
I'm Ensign Io Fleming.
When you hear jazz,
it means I'm coming.
Patti Page, right? "Tennessee Waltz".
You heard?
I like the Royal Teens.
"Short Shorts"?
Ha ha.
No, this.
I see.
If you're interested, okay?
We'll see.
24 sortied, and this
is all that's left?
That's a loser's operation for you.
To the maintenance hangar.
Top priority!
- Whoa.
Io!
Ensign Io Fleming, reporting in.
Never did like the guy...
Acting like a playboy.
Take the body to the Reuse Lab.
I miraculously found it.
I want to send him to his family.
Get the data from his arm first.
A guinea pig even in death?
It's because of that data
that you can fight, right?
Professor Karla, the body is...
Professor?
Major damage, 4.
Minor damage, 6.
Cockpit block only, 5.
Lost, 9.
I see.
We're now gathering data from
the Rick Dom seized by Ensign Io.
We may get their deployment
and movement patterns.
I see.
We're also loading that item
into the container.
The mechanics we dispatched
have returned along with it,
so they can test it immediately.
Who'll use it?
Who else but Ensign Io?
You're right...
Shall I give the order?
No, I'll tell him.
A prototype mobile suit.
The Moore Brotherhood
paid the Federation?
Everyone who outranked you
died in the last operation.
Otherwise...
I guess we've both advanced
because our superiors died.
Right, Acting Captain?
Unhand me, Ensign Io Fleming.
Captain's orders.
Yes, sir.
I see.
A surprise, right?
Where's the captain?
Quality time with her man.
A captain because she's an elite.
What a privileged class.
I heard Io's getting the prototype.
He's the son of Moore's leader, too.
The incompetent elite let Zeon
invade and destroy our home.
But they're perfect
as human sacrifices.
The young heroes
who die for their ideals.
Those with sinful lineages can be
Moore Brotherhood propaganda.
That's what the Gundam's for.
I won't love you anymore.
Then I can order you to go and die.
That's right, Claudia.
Give me an order to sortie.
I'm captivated...
by these demon mobile suits
that glitter in battle.
I heard the mid-combat
communication records.
The Federation pilot
who killed Hoover...
When you hear jazz,
that means he's coming, right?
Yeah.
Please, Daryl.
You must kill him.
An ace like you
can do that, right?
Professor Karla,
can I get some painkillers?
The legs you gave me...
they hurt really bad tonight.
Confirm the sniper rotation
we got from the Rick Dom.
You got that? Just do it as
an extension of a test flight.
Cornelius, tissues.
Here you go.
Some music too, partner.
Okay.
Amazing.
It's beyond comparison.
This is... Gundam.
This is the best!
This is the power I've wanted!
Gundam...
Become my power.
It dodged?
No way!
Darn it.
What's going on?
It's jazz.
3 Zakus shot down.
All the Big Gun attacks were dodged.
A high-mobility mobile suit
with heavy armor.
This machine is a troubling enemy
for our Living Dead Division.
The Federation's...
Gundam.
It's him.
Subtitle edited by - Aorion -