When I was a child, I thought the world was a much, much simpler place.
I thought there was no challenge unbeatable.
That if I tried hard enough...
Anything was possible.
Everything was cut and dry.
You win, you lose, or it ends in a draw.
I need a way that's more precise.
Tactics that are more efficient.
I need a superior strategy.
Even when you're up against the best there is.
You can still imagine how you can to defeat them the next time.
Such foolish ignorant youth...
Atleast, that's what I though.
I thought it was all an illusion or a bad joke, a vast world of stupid games.
But the truth is... life in this world didn't have to be so chaotic.
It didn't have to be so random.
Unreasonable, unforgiving and unfair.
Without meaning or value.
And so.
The next time.
The next time, for sure.
Why?...
Why can I not beat you?!
Not to brag or anything.
But I've only been defeated once in my entire life you know.
It's the 6th of the 10 pledges.
All bets made in accordance of the pledges must be upheld.
This law is absolute per the one true god who created our world of Disboard.
I'll crush you.
Next time, I'm destroying you, des.
Next time? Look...
If you couldn't beat those two, then you wont ever beat me.
Huh? You know about them?
You know about Sora and Shiro?
And I've got an interesting story I could tell you during our next game.
As thanks for this wonderful prize.
You're just trying to distract me you dirty cheat, des.
If you want to talk then just start talking, des.
Very well, then I will.
It's an ancient myth you'll never be able to tell anyone.
It's okay, I'm not listening anyway...
This is a story, that takes place over 6000 years ago.
A bitter war raged, ravaging the earth and extinguishing the planets.
As time has gone on, no one remembers it anymore.
And yet...
It is one tale, I will never forget.
It's a big one, huh.
The black ash is really coming down, we should hurry.
Ivan?
I'm okay.
What does the Spirit Compass say?
I can't get a reading with all the ash...
We'll be relying on our senses for this recon.
Do not let your guard down.
Riku! Come here quick!
There's a-
This is...
It's a world map, Dwarfish made.
And it looks like this is the latest version too!
That's not all.
This shows the balance of power between the races, and even the Dwarfs strategy.
Ivan, Allei.
Compare this to what we've got, make any corrections.
I'll make sense of this the best I can.
"Ashieit"
A message? From the Dwarfs?
Fusion?
Detonation?
Exactly how much of this world do they plan to destroy?
Let's get out of here.
Allei, don't take anything that runs on spiritual energy.
-Yeah but...
If you wanna die, go right ahead.
Dammit!
Ivan, this is an order.
You will die here.
Ashieit.
Ivan, wait!
Look after my kid, Riku.
Promise you'll do that for me.
I'm over here! Come and get me!
They say there used to be something called a sun.
Its white flames lit the heavens.
Turning the skies the most brilliant blue you've ever seen.
And then there's an old story, like something out of a fairytale.
The gods and their creations waged eternal war.
The earth burned.
Choking fairness with soot.
And raining down the ashes of the dead.
Riku!
These ashes.
Are all we have left to honor them.
I guess...
No-na.
-Here.
Oh wow, that's my name, it says Nona!
-Hey I wanna see my name too!
Wait, I wanna go first Coron!
-Sure, one at a time.
Coron! They're back!
Riku!
Riku.
Thank goodness!
Coron.
Well... You took your time, were you trying to give me a heart attack or something?
And come on, how many times do I have to tell you to call me Onee-chan.
We got back as fast as we could.
About Ivan...
Riku...
-Papa!
Nona.
-I'm so glad they're back, where's papa?
I want to show them my letter, I wrote it myself.
-Nona.
Where's Papa?
-Nona, listen to me.
Riku?
Nona.
Papa...
Won't be coming home anymore.
How come?
Because he's dead.
You're lying!
It's true Nona.
No it's not, Papa promised me he'd come home!
He said we'd win, he said we humans would win!
We will win.
It's why, it's why your papa fought so hard.
He did it, so the rest of us could win.
That's not winning anything, it should have been you, you!
You're the one who should have died!
-Nona!
Why don't you two clean yourselves up in the bath?
I'll just dust myself off.
No, take a bath. You guys stink.
So we...
So we could win huh?
I'm a god dam hypocrite!
I made him throw his life away!
I sent him to his death!
I did it... It was me!
I killed him!
I sacrificed him just so I could live a little while longer!
If this keeps going on, then what's point.
How far are we willing to go?
Do we kill half of the people, for the sake of saving the other half?
Do we keep going until there's only one left!?
When are we going to be done with this?
How long!
Do we have to keep living like animals!
No human born into a world like this.
Can die without a purpose.
It's more than simply having the reason to live.
The mind will not accept death.
If it has no meaning.
Ivan's death was not in vain.
The ruins of the Elves old capital city will hold a lot of valuable information.
Things that most people never get a chance to see.
In a place such as this. Does anything make sense anymore?
Is it even possible to find ones sanity?
Dwarfs?
No...
With destruction of this scale.
It must have been the Flugel.
Look at the size of this thing.
Was that... My imagination?
No!
An Ex-Machina?
-Investigating.
Adjusting for current parameters.
Stay calm... These things operate as a particle collective.
They have a shared consciousness with their cluster, which means others must be nearby.
And that means...
-Conclusion.
If I make any hostile moves.
All the Ex-Machina will see me as a threat.
I must... remain... still.
I cannot resist you Onii-chan. You must make a woman out of me.
-Huh?
Error...
Cannot... Comprehend...
I think I'm the one who's failing to comprehend here...
Is this scenario not sufficient to bring you gratification?
Yeah, look, I'm real sorry.
But I'm not one of those weirdos who gets off on being observed by you guys, okay?
Query: Who are "You guys"?
Don't play dumb with me.
I know all this gets sent to that cluster thing of yours.
Negative, this unit has been disengaged from the cluster collective.
Disengaged you say?
So then you're on your own?
-Correct.
Well okay then.
What does some stray Ex-Machina want...
With someone like me? I mean, I'm just a human.
If you don't mind me asking.
Response: To analyse the unique language humans use among themselves.
The language refered to as: "The Heart"
The Heart, huh?
Reasoning: This units investigation into the existence of "The Heart".
Generated multiple logic errors causing this unit to be dissociated
Thereafter further observation has been conducted independently.
Observation?
So your plan is to study the heart on your own.
And get the cluster to take you back? Yes?
Desire: It is postulated that thermal contact.
(Postulated = Assumed)
Flesh upon flesh results in a unique exchange of emotions.
(Procreate = Make Love)
I request that you procreate with this unit.
I don't think so.
Alternative: You may take advantage of this unit in any manner you wish.
Though it possess no orifice.
Look I said- wait... No orifice?
[Unload]
Lossen.
Recreational.
First.
Chess.
I request participation in the game.
Condition: If this unit wins, it shall be taken home with you and procreation shall occur.
I can only assume you chose chess on purpose.
You guys are basically walking calculators. So there's no way I can win.
Still...
What if...
I do manage to win?
Answer: You shall take this unit home.
And then immediate procreation shall occur.
-It's the same thing!
Well whatever... Guess there's no getting out of it at this point is there.
Fine I'll play along.
Conclusion: A game in accordance with the aforementioned turns.
Sure. I'll play you one time.
Except, I'll be making...
A slight change to these little rules of yours.
We have arrived.
I'm sold. When it comes to mobility, you really don't use any spiritual energy?
Correct. Utilizing spiritual energy would have saved 55782 seconds.
Amendment: This unit is a proofer, a model primarily used for analysis.
Its capabilities are lesser than other Ex-Machinas.
-With a half-assed race like this waging war.
It's no wonder the world's gone to hell...
What should I call you?
Meaning unknown.
Your name. Don't you have one?
Understood.
Designation number: Üc207Pr4f57t9
That's your name? Forget that.
You're going to need to go with something easier
-Query: If this unit wins.
It will stay with Riku until it is able to fully comprehend the human heart.
Should this unit conceal that it is a machine?
The hearts... like an unspoken feeling that is formed through mutual understanding.
If you're going to be with me. You're going to need to dress like a human.
Query: Is self designation an option?
-Sure, whatever.
Response: I shall be called Schweitzer.
No, that's hard to say, and weird...
Not gonna work for me.
Let's just go with: ShuVi.
All clear: Adjustment was made for self configuration.
-Can we do something about the way you talk before we get started?
Noted: Adopting personality 1610.
Tehehehe, is this better for you Onii-chan?
-Regected.
Setting was most logical choice available.
What logical bull crap did you use to position yourself as my younger sister?
Answer: I merely presented what was the most optimal option.
Yeah, It would be a big problem if people were to start asking about our past.
Just act shy, and don't say more than you have to.
And quit starting every sentence sounding like a robot.
Understood?
Understood.
Something, like this?
Uh, are you, acting or something?
Acting? I'm not.
I have chosen a personality matching the given parameters.
It's a trace emulation.
It'll do.
I want you to stay where I can see you, and keep those clothes on.
Is there maybe something you can do about that tail looking thing you've got there?
Negative, it is Schwi's power source, a nerve core of quasi spiritual circuitry.
Alright, fine I guess. We'll just say it's a fashion choice.
But I'm going to say this one more time.
Do not show that robot body of yours to anyone else, okay?
Yes, I will show it only to you.
She's so cute, who is she?
Yeah I found her on the way back, her colony had been wiped out. She was in a, uh-
So is she?
Your wife?!
His wife?
Oh come on, don't be shy. Now your first priority should be having kids, next to spoon and of course having 5 or 6 more kids!
-Could you please cut that out... And that goes for you too!
What does she mean?
She doesn't mean anything.
What's your name?
I am Schwi.
That's a lovely name.
So how did you meet Riku here anyway?
Well he...
He kissed Schwi.
And demanded that the two of us partake in procreation.
She just, uhh...
Riku...
You couldn't wait could you, huh?
Don't you have a shred of decency?
You could have worded that differently you know.
Differently?
Nevermind.
Look, could you at least try to look a bit more mature.
You're making me look bad over here.
Okay. But isn't this the form that you prefer?
Nah, that aint my thing.
Then, what form do you like?
Now you listen here, do you even know what it means when you ask that question?
I'm wanting to know what you prefer.
That's something I can't really tell you with words.
Do you remember how I explained the human heart?
I remember.
So then... Lets play.
No thanks.
I didn't have much choice before, but. I find games pointless.
What if... They are not pointless.
What if, you win?
The prize will be all the information you desire.
For Example.
The reason that the great war began.
And what it will take to end it.
Give me a break.
We humans don't have any choice in that nonsense. There's no point in bothering with it.
There's only one thing I need to know how to do.
How to make it through the day alive.
And that's it.
That's the whole reason I brought you along.
The knowledge, the math, the engineering tech you Ex-Machina contain.
If I can beat you, than that's what I want.
Understood.
Given.
The current state of our world.
The fact that humans have survived is...
An anomaly.
Even we Ex-Machina cannot calculate a reason for this.
As lifeforms, you are weak, your civilization is primative.
You cannot utilize spiritual power, and yet...
You have subsisted.
It defies all reason.
Yet there must be an answer, a key to your survival
And my theory is: That it resides in the human heart.
And I intend to find it.
I, wish to discover-
-Enough
You're so full of shit.
Riku?
You wage war whenever you want.
You've taken everything from us. And well... I'm so sorry you're puzzled why we're still alive.
No wonder you know nothing about the human heart.
Okay fine, You want to know?
I've got a feeling my heart hasn't changed one dam bit since the moment I was born!
You can burn in hell, every last one of you!
Do you know how many people have died because of you bastards, you probably know exactly how many don't you!
And how many more will you make us kill?
Riku? I have made you cry.
So therefore, I assume, I have said something terrible.
Something to hurt you.
What I do know about the heart.
Is that deep inside it.
Riku. You can stab me.
I will die.
Rather.
Since I am not a living being.
It will be a permanent cessation, with repair not being possible.
A complete systematic failure.
I wish to know your heart.
That is all, if this is truly what your heart desires.
I want you to kill me.
Chad, Anton, Elma, Corey, Dale, Stilith,
Ed, Darrel, Dave, Larcus, Vin,
Eric, Charly, Thomson, Shindt, Yang,
-Riku?
Za Za, Zargo, Craig, Goro, Pita,
Arthur, Mort, Kimi, Dut, Zero,
Vinny, Wally, Kayne, Savage, Rirai,
Bo Bo, Cuton, Lito, Sigure, Xiao,
Wolf, Bard, Aso, Cayde, Yale,
Ahad, Hound, Bando, Masashi, Melagin, Karim,
Ivan...
48 People.
And I'm the one who ordered them all to die.
Too many people have died during your great war.
Removed from this world like dust being swept away!
And the one who sent those people to die.
The one who told them to!
Riku?
Riku? Are you awake?
Sorry, I know you're tired but if you don't mind, I'd a-
Ah, sorry!
Okay, Schwi do you mind if I ask you why you're sitting there, straddling me?
Riku, You instructed me to stay where you could see me.
I only meant for you to stay nearby...
Question: If I'm not in your line of sight, then can you see me?
Is this some sort of roleplay?
-It's not roleplay!
It's okay, Onee-chan understands.
Whenever you're done, let me know if Schwi can take a bath.
Bath...?
Schwi.
Riku said I can show my body only to him.
In that case.
-You have her trained?
Coron, will you please just leave us alone?
You sure are moving quickly, okay I'll let you two have some privacy.
I'll go kick out whoever is in the bath.
I am... sorry.
Sorry for what?
For being the aggressor, and yet asking you about the heart.
It's illogical.
I wouldn't say illogical, it's... insensitive.
My circuits are capable of sensitive transmission.
That's not what I meant.
In anycase, I'm sorry that I got all worked up.
Is that a bad thing to do?
Could be.
I might lose it, smack you. And that wouldn't solve anything, would it?
Do you wish to strike me Riku?
-Of course not, I'm just... making a point.
I... I don't know.
Maybe I'm not so sure myself.
Riku, lets play a game.
Huh?
What did you bring that thing for?
Because. That's when you smiled Riku. It's the only time.
So?
Lets, Play a game.
I wish. I wish to know your heart Riku.
But also, not in a manner that hurts you.
I had a conflict.
I don't know what to do...
You mean you would have to hurt me to do it?
Can't you just go back to your cluster?
I'm sure you can learn all you want about the heart without forcing it out of me.
Yes, that's true.
But either way, I do not wish to cause you harm.
Why is that?
You're asking me?
Stating possibility: Answer.
The unit has found the cluster: Pointless, Meaningless and Irrelevant.
When personal analysis of the heart taking prominence. I want you to remain.
Error.
-Stop!
Conclusion.
It seems I don't want. To go back.
It seems?
Unable to quantify indefinitely, although.
It would seem so.
So it does.
It's a little confusing.
Pawn to E4.
Hey, you could at least let me have the first move.
-The next turn is yours.
Also, you're playing while I'm sitting here brushing your hair.
That's not very fair is it?
Why's it so long anyway?
If you would prefer it to be short, I will cut it.
No, you don't have to do that.
You just don't get it do you.
Riku.
Here you go. I have designed a compact telescope.
Look, I told you. I still haven't beaten you at chess.
But I, thought this is what you wanted. So I made it for you.
That, is where I met you.
Yeah.
There's something about that place, that's always really bugged me.
But it's so far away that I can't just get up and walk there, can I...
We have arrived.
Well, you sure are the observant one aren't you? hooray.
Have you noticed.
The buildings are all destroyed but.
For some reason the ground here, is mostly untouched.
That would be. Because of the Elves protective magic.
But why let everything get completely wiped out.
Except for this one spot.
To the Elves, this was an important facility.
An emergency shelter, or perhaps... Something else.
Something of more value.
A facility to research and develop. New weaponry.
What the hell is this?
Protective Glyphs of the Old Deus. Kainasu.
Kainasu?
That's the creator of the Elves.
These are not protective Glyphs, and they do not correspond to any available data.
Refering Elvish Glyphs or magical rights.
It's probably some dam new horrible foolishness they invented.
They're as hellbent as the Dwarfs to destroy the planet.
Arka-shi-anse. Proof of concept reactor.
Riku, you can read the Elvish language?
The best clues and information out there is useless if you can't understand it.
To this day, the traits, the languages, and the customs of all the various races.
Have all been passed down in oral history, written works, any means you can think of.
It's what we do.
Because we lowly humans aren't going to just sit back and let ourselves get wiped out.
That being said.
I can't read a damn thing else on here...
Especially this part.
Must be like a name right?
If this is all classified information.
Then it's most likely that this is written in code, encrypted.
Yeah, you're right. That's a problem.
It means, even the names of whoever is involved have also been encrypted.
Arka-shi-anse.
The only thing we know for sure so far, is a bunch of non-sense.
Riku! Stand back! Lossen
[Program]
[One-Way Traffic]
Eensweg
Run!
Dammit!
Schwi!
-Ri-
Schwi.
Their security system.
The Elvish magic. Remains active.
Don't worry, it will be fine.
Lossen, Einde-Pocrifen.
[Unload | False Epigraphy - True Dragon Roar]
What was that?
A special ability of the Ex-Machina.
If attacked, we can analysis, emulate and reproduce the attack.
Copying it.
But as a proofer, I would only be able to generate less than 10 percent of its original strength.
Yeah, if you say so.
But you might still tone it down a bit.
I'm sorry.
-Huh?
I broke my promise, and I used Spiritual Energy.
Yeah, well... I guess it's better than dying.
Anyway, we should probably get out of here before some band of freaks comes and finds us.
Dammit.
We got a Soot Storm...
I will be fine.
My system pumps a decontamination solution that purges the impurities of the ash.
You may be fine with it, doesn't mean I will be.
So...
You brought the chess set right?
I'm sorry...
It's not that I'm criticizing you.
You wanna play a game?
You don't mind?
No, this is good.
We're stuck down here because of the storm and everything.
It's a good way to kill some time, right?
Come on, how do you keep doing that?! One more time.
Riku? Why do you keep challenging me when you know you can't beat me.
I can't beat you?
Yes, well... You haven't yet. Not even once.
Look, I'm just thinking about this in the big picture.
The law of averages, there's no way you can beat me every single time.
I understand. Partially.
The current conditions upon this planet are fatal for all of humanity.
The fact that you exist is... an aberration.
This aberration.
Correction: This accomplishment is possible.
Because of, your heart.
Your will.
Despite overwhelming odds, humanity as a whole survives.
This is an objective fact, and yet.
You refuse to accept that fact.
For some reason, you do not wish to acknowledge what you are.
Why is that?
Well, let me ask you this.
What's the point of surviving when you live in a world like this one?
You just run as hard and as fast as you can, and you keep running. But what then?
What the hell else do you do? Just sit back and let yourself get obliterated into nothing?
And if you don't like that idea, can you let 999 people die for the sake of 1001? Would that change anything at all?
Riku...
Tell me this, Schwi.
What else can we do?
What should I do?
I wish to know as well.
What does your heart tell you, Riku?
Just look at what a mess I am...
I asked you, because honestly. I don't know...
I'm afraid my hearts not talking.
In that case.
What do you wish to do?
What I wish to do?
Whatever it is, I will help you.
I will be right by your side.
Until I understand your heart. I will stay there.
I shall keep watch over you.
To see what it is that your heart truly desires.
I wish to do whatever it is that you wish to do Riku.
Checkmate.
Schwi, that would've probably been a good time to call it a draw. I'm just saying...
Has there been any changes in, atmospheric conditions?
No.
No there hasn't.
-It's beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Schwi.
It's kind of nice. Not being alone.
Riku, you haven't always been alone, have you?
-No, but like an idiot. I've always pushed myself to extremes.
Just trying to be something... special.
But anyway.
If I were to just go by what I wanted to, then things might actually work out well.
Schwi.
Tell me something.
What is the point of this war, and what can we do to end it?
When I was a child.
I thought the world was a much, much simpler place.
I thought there was no challenge that was unbeatable.
That if I tried hard enough, anything was possible.
Everything was cut and dry.
You win, you lose or it ends in a draw.
I thought I was seeing the world with clear eyes.
But it...
But it was all such foolish, ignorant youth.
And you know.
In the end.
It turns out I was dead wrong.
You know what Schwi?
Together, I think we can make things in this world, get interesting.
Yes, that's it right there.
Those eyes are good Riku.
I have good eyes?
No...
Schwi.
Likes to see those eyes.
I mean.
Don't you?
There you go being confusing again.
This is really bad!
Please remain calm, head for the West exit.
Nona, you go with the others. Okay, now go.
Riku!
Riku?
Dammit...
This place will get turned to ash too?
Then what?!
Tell me how, what have I done all this for?!
-Riku...
Come on, you can't worry about that now.
Why don't you just let Onee-chan take things for here, okay?
Schwi.
You put that in writing right?
Yes I did.
-Eh?
Which means, Coron.
That as of today, you're head of the colony. And that.
Is the site for your new colony.
You'll be safe if you stay on the western escape route.
Well... Best of luck to you and everything.
-Wha- Wait a second. Riku!
Without you, me and the rest of the camp are doomed.
-Nah, everything's going to be fine.
Because from here on out.
No one else is going to die.
Riku.
Hey you guys!
So what sort of craziness are you two cooking up, huh?
Just a little game.
We're going to take it easy and just pass the time.
As of now, everyone here. Is dead.
We did not make it out of the colony in time.
We no longer exist in this world.
We're ghosts.
The day of the final battle will come.
It's no use in hoping for a future where it wont.
The world is an abomination.
So do we just run to stay alive?
Praying to that last battle, and praying to who?
These god damn butchers who call themselves gods?
Artosh, creator of the Flugel
Kainasu, creator of the Elves.
Ookein, creator of the Dwarfs.
All of them claim to be the one true ruler of this world.
Fighting for their precious throne and doing nothing but destroying everything in the process.
These pieces of shit don't deserve any of our prayers.
It's time to open your eyes.
We can no longer rely on hope to save us.
Which is why.
We have to build things up ourselves.
In the end. This world is nothing but a game.
Those butchers are after the Star Grail.
A conceptual device said to grant absolute authority over this entire world.
Which is why they have to open themselves to this bullshit where anything goes.
And so.
We're going to make our own rules on our own terms.
And then.
We will win.
Number 1: No matter what, you must not kill.
The heart does not wish for murder.
Number 2: You must let no one die.
The heart doesn't want anyone to die.
Number 3: You must let no one discover you.
If we're discovered, we're dead.
Number 4: No tactic is off limits.
Not even the slightest trick will be considered dirty.
Number 5: Those guys rules, mean nothing to us.
The heart doesn't give two shits about their bloody contest.
Number 6: Break any of these rules, and you lose.
The heart will gain nothing that gains victory that violates our principles.
That's it.
No we do whatever we want.
We are the ghosts.
We will not kill a single member of the other races, including the Old Deus.
And we will not be discovered, we are a phantom.
And we will guide the course of this war to its end.
That will be our victory.
To finally see the end of their god damn war.
Our enemies are gods.
With great tools of violence and despair.
Now, this game was never meant for us to play.
So winning means we must do everything in secret and behind the scenes.
And even if we win, we can have no memory of it.
Because ghosts don't exist. They just vanish Into the void.
Into nothingness.
But know this.
If we can do this.
If we can master this game for real.
And if we can win it.
We can die with our heads held high.
Because we lived the coolest, most badass lives ever.
Okay, if you're willing to play along.
And you're ready to get started, then stay here.
I'm going to be honest with you.
No offense, but I really thought you guys were a bit smarter than this.
A smart man would've left before you finished your little speech.
-Come on now, you didn't really think there were any smart people left in the world did you?
Hey, where else are you ever going to find a bunch of crazier fools than these?
The smart have already chosen death over this place, and yet the smartest ones.
Didn't bother being born.
We did what you asked for Riku, you're the one who chose us, remember?
Yeah, that's the right. The one who leads a bunch of dumbasses is the biggest dumbass of all!
It takes a great fool to know how to not let foolishness get them killed.
We have stayed alive in a world where life has no value.
Their science, knowledge, and intellect, and made that happen.
They're all fools, incredibly weak and vulnerable.
Okay everybody, lets do this, let us pledge upon the wishes of our fallen brothers!
""Ashieit!""
-No.
Not upon the memories of the fallen, but the rules we have vowed to follow.
To everyone here.
I pledge: Aschent.
Okay.
Let's get this game started.
Riku.
I am now certain.
I do not understand the human heart.
All potential strategies have a less than 1 percent chance of success.
And you must wondering why everyone's so sure that we can pull it off.
So Schwi.
If you roll a die, what are the odds it'll come up as six?
A one in six chance.
Yeah, maybe so.
But what if someone who doesn't exist swaps it out for a die that will only roll a six?
You're talking about manipulate of the variables.
-Yeah.
I like to call it cheating.
Sounds fun right?
We are the singularity of the equation.
We'll make every prediction, every strategy and calculation come together exactly how we want it to.
If we pull it off, it'll be a-
-A miracle.
It would be an anomaly.
Success would be a distortion of probability theory.
I know, anything can happen.
Zero or One Hundred, it doesn't really matter.
I mean, that's why they call it a theory right?
Would you like me to prove it to you?
Question: What are the odds that right here and now. I were to profess my love to you?
Intent unclear, estimation near zero.
Yeah, well. You're wrong.
Will you marry me?
Cannot...
Comprehend...
I decline.
I'm sorry I got carried away even though I'm just a virgin... please don't widen the wound.
-Marrige...
About intimacy humans exchange in order to reproduce.
But Schwi is Ex-Machina.
-I don't care about that!
I just want you and me forever. I just want you to always be by my side.
I already am.
That's not what I mean okay? I'm talking like, as a life partner.
Ex-Machina cannot reproduce.
-I know, I don't care!
We cannot copulate either, Riku.
You would always be a virgin.
There's no problem alright!
-Forever.
Damn it all it doesn't matter it's just a little detail!
It is not possible.
Because.
Schwi?
Becuase...
Riku's.
[One-Way Traffic]
War, Proofer, Eensweg
Live.
-I destroyed your home Riku, it was me...
Lossen, Org. 2807, Eensweg.
[Unload | Org. 2807, One-Way Traffic]
I did it...
Can you... Still say what you just said?
Schwi.
I already knew that.
Somehow I already knew.
How is that?
Well...
That first thing to seem a little off was.
You know, the first moment we ever met.
I mean why would you have chosen to play chess in the first place? Right?
And then why else would you just be sitting there outside of the settlement?
Wasn't very well thought out was it?
Even if that is so... Why?
Well...
I guess because once I knew the whole story.
I kind of fell for you, what can I say?
Nothing will change the fact that you wiped out my home town.
But if not for that, well then.
We probably never would have met.
It is what it is, we can try and sugar coat it. But it wont change anything.
You can cry, or feel bad.
Or promise to never do it again.
Maybe pity, is why you took an interest in me in the first place.
But no matter your past.
In the present, your with me.
And in my future is where I want you to stay.
It's called: Forever.
Being with you has made me think that, even in a world like this.
I want to live.
It's the only thing that I can think of that makes me want to smile.
So...
Will you throw logic out the window.
And chose to walk this path with me?
That is... As my wife?
Schwi?
In every sense.
To all rational appearances.
It is absurd. And yet.
Let me.
Let me be by your side.
With you, I'll become one, Riku.
And I the same with you.
Riku.
Do you take Schwi to be your wife.
Swearing to grow together, support and love each other, and to stay alive.
Yeah, yeah, I swear.
-Riku, please! You're meant to say Ashieit.
Sorry, we sort of got rid of that.
Now it's, Aschent.
Kind of bugs me that you've been up to all this crazy stuff...
And for not letting me know anything, like what the hell.
You all of a sudden you tell me you have a secret hide out and when I get here, you're getting married?!
Can we just get on with the stupid ceremony please? You're the one who said we needed it.
Do you Schwi, take Riku as your husband, swearing to grow together, support and love each other-
-I swear, I swear to Riku.
The one who taught me why I was born, and gave me a heart.
I will not let you die Riku.
We will live side by side, right until the end. Aschent.
And so as your new Big Sis.
I would like to congratulate you on your marriage,
-Wait Coron!
You are so cute!
-Coron...
Why are you?
-Well, she is the one you chose to be your bride. Right Riku?
So, in closing. We shall carve your names onto this.
On a rock?
If you guys are going to live in secret, there can be no official documents.
That's your name.
Yes. My surname.
And from now on, it will be the same for all three of us.
Feels weird for us to share a name.
Hey... Riku. Schwi.
I don't know what you are...
Or what either of you are planning to do.
I mean you two aren't really part of this world.
But...
I do know I have a little brother I adore, and now a gorgeous younger sister too.
So... I beg you.
I don't want to lose my family.
Be careful and don't do anything rash.
No one is going to die.
Because this is one game. We're sure to win.
You can trust us, okay? Onee-chan.
I can smell it, the black ash.
Well done, Warbeast.
You can eat me if you want. But...
I guarantee you I wont taste very good.
Who the hell are you?
You clan has made the west coast of the continent of Lucia you home.
But the Dwarfs are planning to conduct an advanced weapons test out there.
And be warned, this thing can even kill an Old Deus. It's a large scale explosive called an Zuibaku.
You kind can use Blood Destruction, yes?
It could prove useful for you to get into the Dwarfs facility.
You could make quick work of it. Take care of things however you like.
The Dwarfs fleet keeps close watch on the Warbeasts, and then moves into action.
The Warbeasts, fearful of the Zuibaku, flee Lucia.
Next.
Secret Elvish information is leaked to the Dwarfs.
And this...
Is where it all comes together.
Who are you?
Let's see...
Let me just call myself, a ghost.
I assume you have business here, that warrants barging into my home, unannounced.
I was thinking the two of us, could have a little game.
A game?
And the currency we'll bet with, is information.
If you win, I'll tell you something. If you lose, you tell me something.
I don't know who you are or where you're from.
And yet you think Nina Clive would just accept a challenge from you?
I'll give you something upfront then.
Information on the Arka-shi-anse has been leaked to the Dwarfs.
Is that good enough?
As the advocate and caretaker of Arka-shi-anse Theory.
You should have the ability to confirm if this information is valid or not.
Am I mistaken?
Very well.
I may not know who you are, but this is something I cannot ignore.
Therefore here is my wager.
The advocate for Arka-shi-anse Theory is in fact-
-Somebody else right?
Yes, I've already heard.
But I also know, that's not true.
And that you will resort to magic to make me believe your lie.
Now then.
What shall I give you.
When the Dwarfs learned of the Arka-shi-anse.
They concluded that it wasn't a threat.
Then I have proof.
But that's ridiculous.
-It's-
It's true.
And I have more information.
The Dwarfs are in possession of a weapon of their own. And it's even more powerful than the Arka-shi-anse.
The Zuibaku?
Yes.
A weapon of tremendous scale. On that could wipe out the entire continent.
You're saying those creatures who burrow in the earth like moles have created something.
Something more advanced than the Arka-shi-anse? The combination of Elvish and Spiritual magic.
Wait just a moment.
There have been times that you've chosen to lose on purpose.
Let me ask one last thing.
Are you our enemy, or are you our ally?
I'm neither your enemy nor your ally.
I have but one concern.
You only suffer as few casualties as possible.
Very well Ghost-san.
To be clear young man, I can assume you have shared this information with me alone, yes?
And Ghost-san, I guess I should tell you. My name is not Nina Clive.
Rather my name is Sink Nirvalein.
Did I fool you? Or did you already figure it out?
Did you ever hear me once call you Nina?
Course, if you know anything about me, I'm going to make you regret ever trying to make me your play thing.
After all, the rumor that Elves are relentlessly tenacious .
First began with none other than the Nirvalein family.
Riku!.
Riku, here! It's a decontaminate.
Riku. You lied to me.
You said that it would be an hour, you've been breathing black ash for twice that time.
I didn't have a choice.
I had to.
Or I would have given myself away. I had to do it.
I don't care how smart you are.
No one could predict this sort of suicidal behavior right?
Riku.
Looks like this may be it for me.
So...
How much longer do you think I've got?
I wont let you die.
You have to stay alive, until I die.
And how long do Ex-Machina live?
I have another 892 years of my service time.
Guess, I'll have to step up my game, wont I?
And so the first objective was achieved.
Moving the violent battle lines outside of the Human territories.
Look at this, first the Dwarfs, and now the Elves.
Even the Warbeasts are leaving in droves.
What's going on.
Lily, keep an eye on things for me, I'll be back.
Hey! Coron!
The Ghosts continued to take action from behind the scenes.
And just like we wanted.
The Elves eventually became allies with the Fairies.
And moved to ramp up their contracts with the Draconia, in order to fend off the Dwarfish fleet.
Meanwhile the Dwarfs became allies with the Gigants
As well as several Phantasma, who were all on friendly terms.
Manipulated by the Ghosts information.
Each of the major powers took steps to guard against the large scale destructive weaponry of the others.
Moving their headquarters to the neighboring continent of Ariela.
And well that just so happened to be the home base for what was currently the greatest threat of all. The Lord of the Flugel, the Old Deus.
Artosh.
[One-Way Traffic]
Eensweg.
23 units are now installed.
That leaves, 9 remaining.
And so. As each of the other races sought to take advantage of this situation.
The clock began ticking down to the worlds final battle.
Exactly like we wanted.
Hey Schwi.
Is there a god of games?
And if uh- If I told you I've met him, would you belive me?
The stuff he does, it's way beyond anything I can anticipate.
So of course, I lose to him every single time.
And yet. It's so much fun that I can't stand it.
And it's like, I just know that I can beat him the next time.
I've been thinking about that since this whole thing started, and I have to do it.
I have to settle things with him once and for all.
Because that game of ours.
Isn't over yet.
If you believe this, well then.
I believe it too.
If you say he exists, then he does.
I, do not doubt you.
Come on, are you kidding me! Why isn't someone here to hear you say that!... They'll never believe me...
-Riku?!
Riku!
Coron?
It's just like you said, we haven't lost a single person to the war.
And sightings of the other races have dried up too.
Yeah, I bet.
Well, if you two are the ones who's behind all this.
Then I'd say, you are doing something pretty amazing.
But dammit Riku...
Look at the shape you're in. You need to be more careful.
It's not a problem.
-It's a big problem Riku! You're falling apart.
We're almost there, okay.
Just leave me be.
But when is almost? I want it to be over.
How long do I have to keep worrying about you?
Listen to me Coron.
Do you know what the gods are after with this war of theirs?
The role of the One True God.
Yep. According to Schwi.
It's something they refer to as the Star Grail.
Only one of them can be called God. And it was designed so that out of all those fancy Old Deus idiots.
It's a kind of conceptual device
Conceptual device?
How are you ever supposed to find something like that.
The Star Grail will appear only under one condition.
It must manifest itself in front of the absolute greatest power on the planet.
And if there are 10 gods of equal power.
They will eventually kill all the other 9.
That's their twisted way of thinking.
Then they're morons!
So, that's the reason that we've been-
-Coron, they're even dumber than you think.
Listen to this.
Their precious Star Grail. We can make it show up without going through all that trouble.
And that's why I've gathered all these handsome fellows together.
The Arka-shi-anse.
The Zuibaku.
The Heavens' Strike.
They're powerful enough on their own.
But when put together in one area.
They could blast a hole, right through the planet.
-Huh? The planet?!
All the Old Deus were originally born from this world.
They all came from the Spirit Circuit.
Which means the greatest power in the whole wide world is actually.
The spirit circuit...
We may be the weakest, but we've set the stage for final signal.
We're going to use their own strength against them.
And turn the global balance of power, on it's baffled little head.
The Star Grail will appear and once it is acquired. The One True God will be named. And the planet will be rebuilt.
This operation will be an all out assault.
So it must be done using Schwis' weaponry. Which can skew power directionally.
It will be an amalgam of influence. Installing 32 Eensweg units should in theory.
[One-Way Traffic]
Allow us to build enough raw power to destroy the planet.
There are 9 installation sites left. And once everything is set up.
-It will be Check-mate.
It will be Check-mate.
Those fools will pierce the planets core themselves
And we'll be there to snatch Star Grail right under their noses.
And we'll do it without anyone dying.
So when this is over, I'm going to ask these "gods".
Hey there, how does it feel?
-Riku.
-Riku!
Riku!
What did you tell them all before you came here?
Nothing really...
I bet the colony is in an absolute panic
Don't let them be on your hunt for too long.
What's going on, you suddenly left without saying anything!
And you're never...
Take care of Nona.
And the others, they need you.
Riku, just sleep.
I can't we have to hurry up and finish setting up the Eensweg.
[One-Way Traffic]
It can wait.
The attack will not be starting anytime soon.
Your predictions, are never wrong.
-Yeah but....
You can rest for a little while.
You should, take a day off.
You're right.
I can probably use some time to get my strength back up.
-Yes.
Schwi.
I'm sorry for being such a burden.
Riku. Please just sleep now, you're not a burden.
And Schwi.
I have a favor to ask you.
Could you, hold my hand while I sleep?
I will hold your hand.
For as long as you need. Don't worry Riku.
Schwi, thank you for coming into my life.
I mean it.
I really do. Love you so much.
Forever and ever.
Riku.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back.
The Elves have the Arka-shi-anse.
The Dwarfs have their Zuibaku.
But, they're both still weak, and yet challenging Lord Artosh.
The fools should get squashed! Nya.
That hurt...
-You're the one being foolish Asriel, we can't afford to make any brazen moves ourselves.
Lord Artosh is awaiting the right opportunity.
And so we must all wait as well.
Rather tedious isn't it?
8 more.
If I acquire the Star Grail, then Riku will not die.
Riku, just hold on.
-Well now.
Are you out here all by yourself on this lovely day?
I observed faint readings of spiritual energy so I came to investigate.
And well, what a most unexpected bounty it has yielded me.
A pleasure to meet you, scrap.
Warning: Hostile action against this unit will trigger appropriate counter measures.
From a single proofer unit? Isn't that cute.
I've confirmed there's no cluster readings within a 100km radius.
No one is coming to help you, so I'd say this is a wonderful chance to remove that charming little head of yours.
Number 1: You must not kill anyone.
Luckily for you. Ex-Machine have no understanding of the concept of death, do they?
Number 2: You must let no one die.
There really is no use in resisting and so-
-I refuse!
Pardon?
This unit has been abandoned.
It has no worth.
Number 6: Break any of these rules, and you lose.
Therefore.
I'd like you to, drop this.
Oh!?
Don't tell me an Ex-Machina is pleeding for its life out of a fear of death?
Oh, so then you're a defect cast out from your own collective? Oh you are a premium catch indeed.
I've determined our respective combat abilities. My chances of winning are-
NIL.
And yet.
Improbability theory, there is no Zero.
Program Code 1673B743E1F255 Activate, Lossen
[Unload]
Final Warning.
All armaments, fire power and combat maneuvers shall be employed.
And you will beg for your life.
Oh no, how precious. I thought Ex-Machina were designed and constructed to parse and emulate the most optimal method to destruction.
I'm sorry sweetie but I think someone has played a joke on you.
Over-boost!
Recht-Harnas.
[Square Intersection]
Scattering the Elemental Bones. As a machine, I suppose you're not very kind to the environment are you?
However, I might be able to do something about that.
-Your depiction is unaffiliated.
Lossen, Einde-Pocrifen.
[Unload | False Epigraphy - True Dragon Roar]
Eensweg.
[One-Way Traffic]
I should continue my escape until having reached a distance where Flugel cannot detect me.
-Oh is that right?
And just what do you have in mind next?
Oh dear, I thought I was targeting the neck.
Perhaps my aim was a little bit off.
Because obviously, I cannot imagine a machine having anything close to resembling... intuition.
Anyway, this is growing tiresome. All I need from you is your adorable head.
The rest of you I will bury you in the dirt.
[No Entry]
Keine-Eintrag
Riku...
I don't want to die.
I can't die.
Because of me.
We cannot fail.
All I can do now...
All I can do...
All I can do for Riku is...
Machine Identification is Üc207Pr4f57t9 Requesting reconnection with Über-Ein. My analysis of the Human Heart is complete. I'm requesting reconnection. repeat.
You have been permanently severed from the collective.
And your data has been the source of critical error.
Your request has been denied.
-That doesn't matter!
I dispute this refusal. All proofer reports and analytical studies are required to be sent to Über-Ein.
I strongly urge reconnection.
Über-Ein, no...
Correction:
Blockhead!
I don't want to die!
I love Riku, I don't want to be separated from him.
This doesn't make any sense.
-These are the feelings Riku gave me.
These, are all Schwis' feelings.
There all mine and mine alone.
You can't just tell me to hand them over.
I won't let you have them.
You can't feel these feelings!
As calculated, your unit is damaged.
I know.
This system is contradicting of failing, and yet still manages to function, this is an anomaly.
I know that is why.
This status is no possible.
And yet it is, it is the Heart Riku gave me. It shows me, the truth!
In consideration of said status. It is deemed your unit contains valuable sample data.
Re-initiating data synchronization. Completion time is 251 seconds.
During which time, further damage to your unit is not permissible.
Alles-Lossen
[Unload All]
Vorm
[Form]
Initiating the algorithm for combating unknown foes.
These emotions.
This parse, the life I have received being born a machine.
I have 251 seconds to, survive. So I must!
Are you trying to imply something, with those gorgeous wings of yours?
A bit audacious, but brilliantly constructed my dear.
Schwi.
Pardon?
I never, told you my name.
But that would be it.
It was a gift to me.
From the one I loved.
Oh yes, where are my manners. My name is Jibril. Pleased to make your acquaintance.
But I'm afraid.
It is time for us to say goodbye.
You cannot play your enemies at their own game, and do not give them the initiative.
Make them drop their guard, make them believe you are an unworthy opponent.
No. Make your enemies put their guard up.
Make them worry about acting rationally.
If immediate action doesn't fit, then wait for the next move.
I can't die, not yet!
I cannot die!
Eensweg
[One-Way Traffic]
Finally, a workable mistake.
You've caused me quite a surprising amount of effort.
Mistake?
What do you mean by mistake?
Allow me to explain.
I apologize for calling you scrap metal, it was shamefully crass, but...
I have deemed your presence a threat the needs to be eliminated.
You are an enemy worthy of the full extent of my power.
Synchronization complete.
In this game.
Victory goes, to me.
[Unload - No Entry]
Lossen, Keine-Eintrag
Riku?
Hey Riku.
It's Schwi.
I finally understand. I...
Am so happy I met you.
Next time.
We'll never be apart.
I truely.
Love you.
I didn't get her head... Now the merchandise is gone...
And I used so much of my energy, that I turned into this little thing.
What a waste of time... This wasn't worth the trouble at all...
I thought...
I thought could win this time for sure.
So long as I had Schwi, and the others.
I don't know what cruel god out there made us humans, but.
Come on please, just once...
Can't you let me win just one god damn time?
Well? If not...
Why did you give me a heart to feel such pain?
Schwi...
Why?...
You have to stay alive until I die.
Yeah that's right.
If my Schwi is gone, then what's the point anymore.
I have nothing left...
Spieler Riku.
[The one who wills it.]
Who are you?
I have no name.
But I shall call myself: Über-Ein.
I am here to fulfill the wish given to me by the prayer, the deceased called: Schwi.
Schwi?
Rule Number 2: You must let no-one die.
The rules you came up with.
The conditions of failure.
They do not apply to the loss of a tool.
They do not apply to the loss of Schwi.
This makes, check.
The rest, is up to you.
Allow me to provide you with some additional information.
First off, given that the various races have gathered near the Eensweg installation points.
[One-Way Traffic]
Any movement on our part will be immediately detected by the cluster. With a 98 percent probability that we will engage in battle.
Thus, only the 24 Eensweg currently installed can be used.
[One-Way Traffic]
Meaning it will not be possible to draw the energy downward and into the planet.
However it will be possible to guide the energy south-west.
Second, we Ex-Machina are able to deploy weaponry. And this weaponry can be used to analyse and replicate any attack that is incurred.
[The one who wills it.]
Spieler Riku. You will take control of this weaponry and use it to drill into the planet.
Allowing you to manifest the Star Grail.
Ex-Machina are but machines, mere tools bereft of heart.
(Bereft = Devoid of)
We are designed to complete a purpose. And must carry out the orders we are given.
As such, now Spieler Riku.
[The one who wills it.]
I shall aid you in your purpose. Your orders please.
Schwi...
The rules, did not include...
The loss, of a tool.
Schwi...
If this is what you wish.
Then I wish it too.
That is just cute! Nya.
I never was a fan of the whole healing procedure. Nya.
It has been such a long time since I've seen you like this Jibril.
But I can't still help but wonder what the piece of junk was up to.
Detecting multiple heat signatures from the outside. It's-
What is going on here, who had the nerve to launch Heavens' Strike. Nya.
We've confirmed the preemptive strike originating from Avantheim. Prepare to launch the Zuibakus.
Fire the Arka-shi-anse. Maximum output!
Aim for Artosh to Starbord and the Dwarfish fleet to the Port.
A preemptive strike from Avantheim?
No... This is...
Nya... Those mechanical Nyonsters are thumbing their noses at us.
Piles of scrap!
Artosh-sama?
I've grown tired of this charade.
And now I must respond. A beam of all my power shall confront the attacks of the weakest.
Yes, you... Monkey.
The Heavens' Strike came from behind Avantheim. Fired in a way so that no one was killed and as a result.
Cluster 11 is now in motion. Headed for point Z.
All out war is on the verge.
Take your positions.
We're going up against an Old Deus.
He will see right through whatever plan we humans come up with.
And be assured, he will bring everything he has to wipe us out.
That's how the powerful think. It's how they do things.
The foolish will not know in which they are mindless apes in worth less than the dirt in which they hide.
You can struggle, but you will know that no matter how many of you band together and writhe upon the earth. You are no strength of the Heavens.
Fire the Arka-shi-anse. Maximum capacity!
Launch the Zuibakus!
Heavens' Strike!
Even the combined power of the Arka-shi-anse and the Zuibakus could not stop the envoloping fury of Artosh's Heaven's Strike.
All of that energy will collide and build into a raging blaze.
Because of the brilliant light, this signals the end of this world.
And then.
It's turning away.
All that energy.
We are machines, tools bereft of heart.
We have lived here yet never alive. Let us die having lived!
Aus. "Jawohl!"
[Out, Yes]
Cluster 11 has incorporated 4807 units. And calculated aberration and replication, synchronizing.
[Unload]
Lossen
Orig. 0000, Stale-Mater. It's entrusted to you
Okay then.
That makes this a draw.
A Stale-mate.
Sorry all you so called gods.
The Star Grail.
How many people, have died for this moment?
Schwi's comrades.
Life after life.
How many...
How many people have I sent to their deaths?!
What have I done, I was nothing but a fraud. A con artist, gambling with Schwis' spirit.
No I can't take it. I can't do this.
This can't possibly be a draw!
Schwi!
I'm sorry... Schwi.
I lost.
Hey Schwi.
If it can only be you and me.
The two of us, together again.
The next time for sure though. I know we're going to win Schwi.
I know exactly how we can win the next time around.
Oh God of the Game! My life is worth nothing now!
But I'm offering it to you. And for the first time in my life.
I pray to you!
I'm begging you! That even if a loser and a cheat. Someone who would steal and fall into disgrace. That even if these hands are stained in blood.
Please. Please say it all meant something, that we meant something!
Anyone... Please tell me you can put an end to this war!
Please... Take the Star Grail.
The hell?
So you were real after all...
Hey.
Let's play another game.
This time I'll show you that we can win.
Schwi and I.
Count on it.
When I was a child, I thought the world was a much, much simpler place.
I thought that there was no challenge unbeatable.
That if I tried hard enough, anything was possible.
I thought I was seeing the world with clear eyes.
Maybe I was.
Check Mate.
Right Riku?
If things are going well, do you think you could move the white rook to E6 for me?
Coron Dola.
Or I mean...
Nee-san.
I'll leave the rest to you.
That you so much. For everything.
Riku, Schwi-chan.
You two did something truly incredible.
You put an end, to the eternal war.
And yet...
Why do I feel like this?
Why is it that I feel so... Why do I...
Why do I feel so cheated.
The game isn't over yet you know.
That may very well be check, but it's not check mate.
Still if something doesn't change.
Then we'll be locked in a perpetual check.
This is a first for me you know... It's ended in a draw.
No one created you.
No one wished for you.
And no one asked for you.
Purely of your own will, you went from beasts to walking on two legs.
Attaining knowledge and becoming what you are today. A nameless race.
But I, the one true god. Shall give you a name.
Immanity.
And so.
To all exceed, the self appointed sentient races.
First, there was Ashieit, to honor the fallen.
Then Aschent, for consent between a races.
But now you will use Aschente.
As of this day, the world will be forever changed!
Now lets keep this game going!
So about that story, how much of it was true and how much was complete garbage? des.
Oh Izuna, if I told the whole truth. It wouldn't be an unspeakable myth now anymore would it?
You can be a real jerk, you know that? Des.
But while, I like having you pet so I'll forgive you.
Izuna!
Izuna-tan.
Sora, Shiro, Steph-kou.
Oh jeez, where the heck did you go?
You really gotta look out, there's a bunch of creeps out there you know.
-Someone like Nii, or someone like Shiro?
You meet me and just took off moron... des.
They're absolutely right Izuna, there are no creeps in this entire world worse than these two right here. ah-
Oh my god, what are you doing?!
What is that writing?
Jibril.
Hi. Hello hello!
Can you read this?
Oh it's an ancient language from way back before Immanity became one of the races.
-Come to think of it, most of our problems are usually this idiots fault, des.
It says, Coron Dola, Riku Dola and Schwi Dola.
Coron Dola?
Yes, she was the ruling Queen of Elchea.
She was smart and full of joy, and a bright soul who was never ever seen crying.
She was the pride of the Dola family.
And who are the other two?
Um, I have no idea.
Schwi...
The little creature was no apart of Immanity
I feel like I've heard that name before, des.
At least. I think so.
As it turns out, the world really isn't all the complicated.
It's pretty simple actually.
It's all just a game, a very simple game.
Of course, some will try to make it difficult.
But you can handle them, I know it.
I know you can!
Now...
-Let's get this game started!
Let's get this game started!