Pika!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
NARRATOR: The world of
Pokemon, brimming with beauty,
variety, and majesty.
As the most mysterious
and magnificent creatures
on this planet, there are
over 700 species of Pokemon.
And they can be found
wherever one looks.
Pokemon have many different
skills and abilities.
And through a phenomenon
called evolution,
they are able to
grow and change.
Most people and Pokemon live
happy and peaceful lives
together as friends
and companions.
And there are the Pokemon
trainers, join forces
with Pokemon as battle
partners, displaying
their skills in competitive
arenas everywhere.
And because of the strong bond
between trainer and Pokemon,
a new, powerful
phenomenon has arisen.
During battle, a
trainer's Key Stone
can have a particularly
synchronistic reaction
with the Pokemon's Mega Stone.
This results in a temporary
but profound increase
in the power of a Pokemon.
This transformation is
known as Mega Evolution.
The mystery of Pokemon.
Perhaps it is that mystery
that exists at the very heart
of the world itself.
[RUMBLING]
[BEEPING]
Hmm?
I've got it on screen.
What do you know?
Coming back here to get it, huh?
[ROAR]
I don't think so.
I'm not simply going
to hand it over.
Alakazam.
Glalie.
[ROAR]
Mega Wave.
[POKEMON GRUNTING]
Kazam.
(GROWLING) Glalie.
[GROWLING]
Alakazam!
[GRUNT]
Use Freeze-Dry!
Glalie!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Pika!
Great!
All set!
Pika!
Thanks for the help, Ash.
Here, Serena, this too.
NARRATOR: This young man is Ash
Ketchum from Pallet Town, who
wants to be a Pokemon Master.
He and his partner, Pikachu,
along with his friends
are continuing their
training journey.
And today, it's time for
some Pokemon battle practice.
Clemont, don't hold back, OK?
Pika-cha.
Holding back is not what I do.
Pih-pih, Chespin.
Hmm.
Now, Bunnelby, I need your help.
Bunnelby.
Let's go, Noivern.
Bleh, wah!
[THEME - BEN DIXON AND THE SAD
TRUTH, "STAND TALL"]
THEME SONG: I stand tall
'cause I know I'm a winner.
You've met your match.
Yeah, I'm no beginner.
No beginner.
Gotta catch 'em all!
I stand tall 'cause
I know I'm a winner.
Knock me down, I'll
just get up again.
You've met your match.
Yeah, I'm no beginner.
Pokemon, Pokemon.
Gotta catch 'em all!
You've met your match.
Yeah, I'm no beginner.
Pokemon, Pokemon.
Gotta catch 'em all!
I've got all my
friends beside me.
I'm keeping my eye on the ball.
With the wisdom of
years to guide me,
I'm gonna catch 'em all!
[COUGHING]
No!
I'll have to rewash these.
- Too bad.
Serena, did something just fall?
Huh?
Ugh.
Hey, Pikachu?
Pikachu!
You OK?
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
[GASP]
What was that?
Pikachu.
Pika.
Wah!
[GASPING]
Aah!
[GRUNT]
Pika!
Oh.
Whoa!
[GRUNT]
[GROANING]
Look, human.
How many times are you
going to bump into me?
Hey, you can talk.
Pika.
Is it telepathy?
Well?
Huh?
Wait.
[GRUNTING]
What is this?
It's stuck!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Huh?
Amazing!
An electromagnetic pulse!
I've got no time for this.
[YELLING]
[GRUNT]
Stop banging into me.
Aah!
[GRUNT]
[SCREAMING]
Knock it off already.
I'm not doing anything.
It's the EM pulse.
An electromagnetic pulse is
flowing between those bands.
TOGETHER: Huh?
What's that mean?
CLEMONT: Basically
they're being linked
together by an invisible force.
[ALL GASP]
Oh, that's just great.
Hold on!
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
Cut it out!
Are you listening to me?
[ALL PANTING]
Poor Ash.
[GASP]
[PANTING]
Slow down!
Man, my stomach hurts.
Quiet, human.
This is none of your concern.
[PANTING]
[SCREAMING]
TOGETHER: Yummy time!
[EATING NOISILY]
Man, that's delish.
[ASH SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
What are you doing?
Because of you, I
can't get my balance.
Not again!
Whoa!
TOGETHER: It's Twerp Time!
Oh, yes.
So we finally meet.
This way, please.
I am the prince of
the Azoth Kingdom.
My name's Raleigh.
[ROBOT NOISES]
Hmm?
Magearna, Magearna.
NICOLA: Your heart
and soul will be
the fortress that will protect
the people of our kingdom.
At least, that is
my fervent hope.
[SOUND EFFECTS]
I'm sorry if you had
any trouble getting here.
Please forgive me.
[ASH SCREAMING]
Huh?
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
Mm, mm.
Is that the Pokemon,
the one who wants
to take you back, Magearna?
Magearna?
[GRUNTING]
[POKEMON GRUNT THEIR NAMES]
Mega Wave.
[POKEMON GRUNTING]
Huh?
Glalie.
Alakazam!
[GRUNTING]
Gengar.
- Mega Evolution?
- Why, you!
Gengar, psych him.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
Glalie, Ice Beam.
Now, please,
don't get worked up.
Magearna.
Flamel, any other information?
Extrapolating from
witness reports.
What came flying
in was a Pokemon.
It's called Volcanion.
Volcanion?
FLAMEL (THROUGH DEVICE):
A mythical Pokemon
that is said to live in
the midst of Nebel Plateau.
A mystical Pokemon.
Princess, please be careful.
I will.
Volcanion?
That's what you're called?
Magearna represents the
very future of our kingdom.
I want you to understand that.
Hey, it takes
nerve to freeze it
and then ask it to understand.
Oh, it's a
pleasure to meet you.
I am Raleigh, the
prince of this kingdom.
Prince, huh?
So then who might you be?
I'm Ash from Pallet Town.
I'm a Pokemon Trainer.
Well, then, please
let me explain.
See, Magearna was
built by someone
using arcane science long ago.
Magearna is a Pokemon.
A Pokemon?
RALEIGH: That's
correct-- a Pokemon!
Magearna was created
over 500 years ago!
It is the only one of its
kind in the whole wide world!
Huh?
Way back then, a great
master of arcane science
named Nicola lived
in our kingdom.
He created many
wonderful inventions
based on the skills of
Pokemon, which brought
great riches to our land.
Magearna was created by
Nicola, who presented
it to the royal family.
Then it is said Magearna lived
happily with the princess
at that time.
But sadly, amidst the chaos
of war, Magearna's whereabouts
were lost.
But today, we have finally
found it once again!
Mm-hmm!
[SHATTERING]
- Huh?
[GRUNT]
[SCREAMING]
[POKEMON GRUNTING]
Pika-pi!
[INAUDIBLE].
Magearna, let's go.
[BLIP]
Raleigh and Alva too.
Could it be?
Hmm.
[GASP]
[PANTING]
Could this be?
[INAUDIBLE].
[AMAZED GASP]
Whoa!
Huh?
[INAUDIBLE].
Clemont, we've got to hurry!
Over here!
Clement?
Serena, Bonnie,
this is incredible!
This is the Azoth Kingdom!
The Azoth Kingdom?
It's an ultra-mechanized city.
We'll find the great
scientist Nicola
using arcane science and art.
[LAUGHING]
Mechanized?
Nicola was a genius.
He's truly one of
my all-time idols.
He used Pokemon
skills as inspiration
for his many inventions.
Truly a great man.
[INAUDIBLE].
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
Huh?
[CHUCKLE]
Pikaboo.
[STOMPING]
[GRUNT]
[ROBOT NOISES]
For you, I would walk
through fire and water.
Pika-pi!
Pikachu!
[ROBOT NOISES]
So they call you
Volcanion, don't they?
Mm, and what do they do?
[ROBOT NOISES]
Magearna, you really are
a one-of-a-kind Pokemon.
Pika.
Hahaha.
Magearna, everything OK?
[ROBOT NOISE]
My name's Ash, And
this is my pal Pikachu.
Pika, Pikachu.
[ROBOT NOISE]
[GRUNT]
It's nice to meet you too.
Don't touch it!
[BELL DINGS]
Pika.
Hey, what are you doing?
I can't blast
anything without water.
You can't?
Pika.
Don't worry.
If those guys show up again,
we'll chase them away.
I don't from humans.
Pikachu.
Stay out of this,
electric nuisance.
Pika.
Pika-eh-kachu!
Listen up.
I'll tell you just one.
I will never trust humans.
To Pokemon like you
that cozy up to humans,
I don't trust them either.
Pika, Pika.
What, Pipsqueak?
What to fight?
Come on.
Everybody just calm down now.
[GRUMBLE]
[ROBOT NOISES]
Pik.
Pika.
We found them!
[PANTING] Ash!
everyone!
Huh?
[ROBOT NOISE]
JARVIS: I see.
You say that you know
that young boy trainer.
Boy, do we ever.
Quite-- for a very long time.
Too long.
You have no idea.
And you call
yourselves Team Rocket.
I'll need more information.
TOGETHER: More?
Sure!
Just meeting the
mythical Pokemon Volcanion
would've been amazing.
But to actually meet Nicola's
greatest creation of all time?
I'm honored!
[ROBOT NOISE]
Mm.
[CRACKLE]
Huh?
It's never coming off.
Pika.
You humans are useless.
That's not nice.
[INAUDIBLE].
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Huh?
[GASP]
[ROBOT NOISES]
[DELIGHTED GASP]
Thank you, Magearna.
You're a Pokemon treasure.
Don't touch it!
Huh?
Look out!
Wah!
Pika!
[GROANING]
Why me?
Ugh.
(SADLY) Pika.
Hi, there!
We're back!
Huh?
Magearna?
[ROBOT NOISE]
[AMAZED GASPS]
Amazing!
Incredible!
[LAUGHING]
Kind of like a Poke Ball.
- Pikachu.
- Ash?
Huh?
Tada!
Since your clothes are a
mess, how about you try these?
Hmm.
Uh-- hmm.
Wow, you look great.
Really?
Pikachu, Magearna, do I?
Pika-Pika!
[EXCITED ROBOT NOISE]
Stop it, Magearna.
Don't get involved
with these humans.
[ROBOT NOISES]
I refuse.
Leave me alone!
[ROBOT NOISES]
[POOF]
[GASP]
[GEARING UP TO SNEEZE]
[ROARING]
Choo!
[GRUMBLE]
Hey, I told you to
quit it, didn't I?
OK, fine.
I'll doing my best.
[ROBOT NOISES]
[SPLASH]
Aah!
Magearna!
[ALL GRUNTING]
Are you all right?
[ROBOT NOISES]
Magearna, you're soaking wet.
We'll get you all dried up.
[ROBOT NOISES]
Well, that's a relief.
Though you've got to
admit, Magearna's heavy.
[ROBOT NOISES]
Gearna?
Pika?
It looks embarrassed.
Because it fell?
I don't like Magearna
likes being called heavy.
You're kidding.
Of course it
doesn't like that.
[GASP]
I'm so very sorry.
Please forgive me.
Clemont means
well, but he just
doesn't understand some things.
[GIGGLE]
We should go.
The sun is setting.
[ROBOT NOISES]
No.
I said, no!
I won't bring humans along.
Hey, where you going?
Come back!
Huh?
Not again.
[YELLING]
Pika-pi!
Huh?
[MURMURING]
We need to get away right now.
[ROBOT NOISES]
Get moving, or I'll
leave you behind.
Raleigh, wait.
Chymia!
What is it?
I saw you standing up
on the tower wall before.
And you were with Alva, as well.
What were you up to?
A scientific investigation.
Many of the amazing
machines built by Nicola
are operating even now.
Oh, is that all?
Listen to me.
If you really want to
learn, look to the future,
not just to the past.
The future?
To do that, you need to
learn about the past, see?
Father is worried
about you, as well.
Alva was with me, so
there was no need to worry.
But that's why he's worried.
Now, you know that
father trusts Alva
completely, just like I do.
He thinks a lot more about our
kingdom's future than you do.
So if you'll please
excuse me, I have to go.
1, 2--
BOTH: Ta-da!
Whoa!
Isn't it cute, Volcanion?
[BLOOPING]
[SIGH]
Huh?
Well, that went over well.
Maybe it's shy.
Could be.
Right, Magearna?
[BEEPING]
Getting friendly, aren't they?
Sure are.
Since we're stuck together
now, might as well have fun.
- I agree.
- Nonsense.
I just want to
get away from you.
Nothing good comes from
interacting with humans.
Huh?
You fell out of the
sky with these bands.
Remember?
Look, humans
made these things.
Well, it sure wasn't us.
All humans are the same.
Pika!
Hey, you.
What are you doing
hanging around like that?
Get your filthy
human hands off me.
No, I won't!
Cut it out, I said.
No, you first!
I'll blast you off.
Agh.
JARVIS: If they're
headed somewhere,
it's probably Nebel Plateau.
Oh, the place with the field
of flowers where Magearna was
found.
Yes.
Members of Team Rocket,
please go investigate.
Count on us, sir!
[GIGGLING]
It's all finished!
What is?
Have a look for yourselves.
The future is now,
thanks to science.
I made this protective
suits inspired by moves
like iron defense and protect.
It's called Mr. Iron Defense.
Whoa-ho!
You're protected from
any kind of attack.
Huh?
What do I see?
It looks like a camp fire.
Maybe they're setting
up camp here tonight.
We have to tell Alva.
Wait.
Our real boss is the prince.
Once we can get our hands on
what he wants, we'll be rich.
Brilliant!
And that's rich.
Let's make some dough.
[SNORING]
Huh?
You sensed it, too?
Pika.
Pikachu!
Ah!
Huh?
Uh, Magearna!
[BEEPING]
JAMES: Yoo-hoo!
ALL: Huh?
From now on,
Magearna's our guest.
Team Rocket?
What are you guys doing here?
Huh?
Heracross and Pinsir?
Hey, where are
your normal Pokemon?
We're not your
normal Team Rocket.
Check this out.
TEAM ROCKET: Mega
Wave Team Rocket!
What?
Key Stones!
We joined forces with
the good Prince Raleigh.
No way!
See?
We're Mega Wave Team Rocket!
[GASP]
Pika.
Mega Wave!
[SNARLING]
Mega Evolve?
But how?
To Mega Evolve, there
must be a close bond
between trainer and Pokemon.
It's thanks to what Alva
calls-- er, what was it?
Mm.
Neo arcane science.
With this technology, we
can use Mega Evolution
and we don't need
any stinking bond!
I see.
So Gengar and the others--
[SNARLING]
Gengar!
What about how
the Pokemon feel?
That's not Mega Evolution!
Arcane science was
developed to make
people and Pokemon happy!
You're defaming the
memory of Nicola!
Hey!
We call it neo because
technology passed
through by science, guys.
Now, Heracross!
Pinsir, too!
Turn them into goo!
[SCREAMING]
You, take Magearna
away from here.
I hate relying on humans,
but I have no choice.
Go!
Everyone, do it.
All right.
Let's go, Magearna.
Leave it to us.
Let 'er rip.
Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
Pikachu!
Get him, Volcanion!
I don't need a cheerleader.
Yes!
Pika.
[SCREAMING]
Success!
It worked like a charm.
Mega Evolution
drew Volcanion away.
[SCREAMING]
Gardevoir.
The nerve!
Gardevoir, Mega Evolve!
Gard!
Gardevoir.
MEOWTH: Now there's a
Mega Gardevoir in my face.
Use Dazzling Gleam!
Gardevoir!
TEAM ROCKET: We're
blasting off again!
[SCREAMING]
Wow!
Nothing.
Pikachu!
PIKACHU: Pika.
Let 'em have it, Volcanion.
Don't blame me
for the results.
Don't worry.
Pika Pika!
Science is so amazing.
Pika?
Huh?
So this is your real power.
Ha.
If I showed you my real power,
it wouldn't be just this.
I've leveled a whole mountain.
Awesome.
Pika?
Hey, Ash!
What exploded?
Hey, guys.
Pika!
Now I've got even more humans.
Magearna, I'm Chymia,
princess of Azoth.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm a descendant of
the Azoth royal family.
Princess?
Whoa.
[BEEPING]
[GASP]
Oh, my.
They're beautiful.
Thank you.
Volcanion, you were
protecting Magearna, right?
Hm.
CHYMIA: For the kingdom?
That's what Raleigh said, huh?
SERENA: Right.
One thing's for sure.
Raleigh believes everything that
Alva tells him-- that it's all
for the good of the kingdom.
Does Raleigh really trust
this Alva person that much?
Yes.
Ever since Raleigh was a
boy, he always adored Nicola.
Many times, he would spend
the entire day in his room,
reading old texts and
performing experiments.
And because of that, when he
found out that Councilor Alva
was an arcane
science researcher,
he started to spend more
and more time with him.
So now, since my brother
is involved in this,
that means that I am, too.
[YELLING]
Hey, why don't we
just get on board
the thing they're riding on?
Why would I board
something humans built?
Oh, come on.
Ah!
[GASP]
The princess.
I know.
Dedenne.
Wow!
A field of flowers!
Come to greet us, huh?
[FRANTIC CHIRPING]
What?
[CHIRP]
Ah?
Ah!
Huh?
[CHIRPING]
Up ahead.
Is that Amaura?
Amaura's badly injured.
Hold on.
[WHIMPERING]
Hang in there.
We'll take care of it.
I don't need your help.
I'll carry Amaura myself.
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
Now this big one
will fetch me an even
better price than that Amaura.
A Pokemon hunter.
[POWERING DOWN]
[GASP]
All right,
Pikachu, Thunderbolt!
Pikachu!
I'll fix all of you.
[GROWLING]
[CHIRPING]
What a bad man.
Pokemon hunters
only want one thing--
to make money stealing Pokemon.
So bad things like this--
do they happen a lot?
Yes.
But I can usually drive
them off by creating mist
long before they get this far.
[GASP]
Pika.
VOLCANION: This is
Nebel Plateau, our home.
So many Pokemon!
And they're totally cute!
[BEEPING]
- Drill.
- Pika, pika.
Pika!
Dedenne.
Pika?
Everybody seems
pretty afraid of us.
You know why.
You're humans, right?
It does look like they
don't trust us at all.
I wonder why that is.
All right.
I'll treat Amaura.
Don't worry.
Treat.
Don't just do whatever you want.
Don't be so angry.
You've got to trust
us a little bit.
[BEEPING]
You help, too, Bonnie.
BONNIE: Sure!
CHYMIA: Let me help, too.
I could help, too.
Does it sting?
It'll all be over soon.
You've just got to be strong.
Pika.
CHYMIA: The bandage is freezing.
This sort of thing happens
with ice type Pokemon.
It's proof of the healing.
That means the
medicine's working.
Amaura, that's so great.
Dedenne-ne.
Amaura.
Forget all the bad times.
You're in a safe place now.
You have food here.
You have friends, too.
'Maura.
Sleep now, Amaura.
[BEEPING]
[LULLABY MUSIC PLAYING]
Pika!
Pi?
Huh?
Pika?
Pika.
It must be that they're
scared because we're here.
Well, we may be humans, but
Pokemon are still Pokemon.
All right.
Now, everybody out!
Pancha-cha.
Yeah!
Great idea.
I'm in.
Hawlucha.
Talonflame.
Bla, bluh.
Bun!
Bunnelby!
Luxray.
You see?
You don't need to
be afraid of us.
Help us show them
we're friendly.
Pikachu!
Ch-ch-ch cha-cha-chu.
Che.
Eee!
Chu!
Hawlucha.
Cha-cha.
Lucha.
Lucha!
Pikachu.
[BEEPING]
Wow, this is great!
Yeah!
Argh.
Huh?
Volcanion, are you OK?
Hey, wait a minute--
the Pokemon hunter.
You need help, too.
I need nothing.
Magearna, stay out of the
flower field for a while, OK?
But what about you?
Hey!
Wait for me!
Bonnie.
ASH: It's a hot spring.
BONNIE: Like a giant bath.
A bath will fix me right up.
Wow.
Quick, Ash, you've got to
get out of there right away.
Wha?
Whoa!
Your suit's
absorbing the water.
[YELLING]
Eugh, and then some.
Hm.
You humans are an
annoying bunch.
Wrench, please.
Bunnelby.
Che.
Thanks a lot.
Working on gadgets
along with Pokemon.
I'm sure it must have been
like this for Nicola, too.
Nicola thought the world
needed both humans and Pokemon
to be in harmony, which I
believe is what inspired
him to create Magearna.
Magearna's the living
embodiment of the philosophy
of arcane science.
At least, that's the way I
prefer to interpret that.
It's such a beautiful idea.
ASH: So you're always here,
watching out for everyone.
Ha.
That's because I never
know when I might explode.
You've got that right.
Pikachu.
Why don't you
two get some sleep.
You're keeping
watch, I am, too.
Pika, Pikachu.
Do as you like.
I will.
Pika-Pika.
[CHUCKLING]
Ta-da!
Your clothes--
they're all clean.
Wow.
Thanks a lot, Serena.
Pikachu!
[BEEPING]
Oh, boy.
This won't be easy.
Gulpin.
Bunnelby.
Yes!
It worked!
BONNIE: Yay!
They brought those
berries for us.
Hm.
Incredible.
I never thought I'd
see humans and Pokemon
getting along together here.
All these Pokemon--
they've been hurt by humans,
haven't they?
Yes, they have.
You, too?
Don't worry about
what happened to me.
All fixed!
Good as new.
Next time, we're going
to be working on you.
Working on us?
Pika?
Watch what this one can do.
It's about time.
It worked!
Thanks so much, Gulpin.
Huh?
Pika?
This Gulpin has its reasons.
Anyway, the bands are gone.
Leave.
Even after all
that's happened?
After everybody's starting
to get along so well?
Doesn't mean anything.
It does, too.
You only did that because
we were stuck together.
Hey, I really like Pokemon.
I want to protect them, too.
If you're going to
be a Pokemon trainer,
then you've got to learn how
to make Pokemon feel safe.
Right, buddy?
- Pika, pika!
Spare me your pretty
words or I'll blast you.
You try it!
Pika!
Bunnelby.
I'm going to sleep.
Aw.
What?
I brought Poke Puffs.
Serena and Chymia made them.
Pika.
Huh?
You were surprised
back there, weren't you?
They just didn't understand.
Please forgive them.
Sorry, Gulpin.
Pikachu.
This little one
came here after being
abandoned by its trainer.
Pika.
I don't know if anything
happened before that.
He doesn't tell me,
and I don't ask.
The only thing I know is that,
right before its trainer left,
he gave Gulpin a big hug.
All of the Pokemon here have
been wounded by the selfishness
and lies of humans.
They may be laughing now, but
their wounds are deeply-rooted.
And that's the reason
I can't trust humans.
Pokemon are incapable of
lying, but humans are.
And do.
Pika pika.
Pika.
Pika pi.
Really?
This one doesn't lie?
Pika!
Pikachu!
Pikachu.
He fights with all he has
to protect the ones he loves.
Pika pika.
Thank you for that.
You're right.
Pikachu!
Both of you are spewing
nothing but flowery sentiments.
I'm sorry.
Before the others get used
to you, I want you to leave,
though I'm very grateful
to you for what you
did for Magearna and Amaura.
Here.
Go ahead and eat.
Not bad.
If you like it, then why
don't you say you like it?
Pikachu.
Eat.
Both of you.
[RUSTLING]
- Pi?
Pika?
What is that?
[GROWLING]
[ALL SQUEAKING]
[GRUNTING]
[ALL PANTING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[ALL GASPING]
[GROANING]
Grexit, Talonflame!
Luxray, Greninja!
Woo!
[ALL SHOUTING]
[HOWLING]
Everyone!
[GASPS]
Kanu!
Dreberon.
Jiyoo!
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
Huh?
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
You two.
Well, well.
[CLICK]
[ALL MOANING]
If you resist--
[CLICK]
[ALL MOANING]
You're the worst.
Bega!
They're humans.
They think nothing of
the lives of Pokemon.
Hey!
I'll blast you!
Manectric, electrotrain!
Steelix, use stealth rocket.
Mey, nethra.
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[GROWLING]
How dare you?
[SQUEAKING]
If you want to help them,
then you should come with us.
If you do, then
everybody is happy.
No!
Don't go, Magearna.
[GROWLING]
Then I've no choice.
[CLICK]
[ALL SCREAMING]
Oh, you'll pay for this!
Oh!
[BEEPING]
[GASPS] Magearna!
Heeda.
So now you understand.
[LAUGHS]
Use psychic.
Zob.
Oog nay.
Googi.
Magearna!
Ah.
[ALL GASPING]
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
[BEEPING]
Rollie, Alva.
Everything's OK.
All of this is for our kingdom.
[CHUCKLES]
[SCOFFS]
[ROARS]
Oh.
Alva, why don't we
tell them everything,
What an incredible creation
Magearna really is?
Fine.
Gengar, mean look.
Gah.
[BEEPING]
Huh?
Ah.
[BEEPING]
Gah.
- [EVIL LAUGH]
- Wait a minute.
You don't have to
remove its soul-heart.
That's just as long as
Magearna becomes a spear.
Nicholas said that-- ah!
All that I really
need is its soul-heart.
You can't!
If you remove it, then--
[CHUCKLES]
Alva, what happened?
It's gone.
[GASPS]
Gengar, kindly
return Magearna.
[SNARLS]
[GASPS]
[SHOUTING]
Chymia, your presence is
not required for my plan.
Farewell.
Use hyperbeam.
[SHOUTING]
How could you lie to me?
It wasn't for the kingdom!
Yes, it was all done for the
glory of the Kingdom of Azoth,
my ideal one, of course.
[GASPS]
Gengar, hypnosis.
[SNARLING]
They used dig and safeguard.
Thank you, everyone.
Re pow.
Magearna!
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
Volcanion.
Weepa.
If it's soul-heart
is returned,
Magearna should be revived.
[GASPING]
Everyone on board.
Prince Raleigh, I thought
that you would understand,
that you would be
able to comprehend
my noblest of dreams.
There's no reason to
make such a big fuss.
We're only talking
about one Pokemon.
[GASPS] It's Magearna.
I can sense it right from here.
Oh, Magearna.
It's crying.
In that case, it's
retrieved the soul-heart.
[INAUDIBLE]
Gengar, psychic.
Gah!
You're even less
than useless to me.
[ALL MOANING]
[SCREAMING]
VOLCANION: That
field of flowers,
that's where I met Magearna
for the very first time.
Wasn't it 500 years ago?
I don't know how you
humans measure time.
But it's a story from
the ancient past.
Then, as now, the
plateaus. was my home,
and that of many, many
other troubled Pokemon.
Oftentimes, I would check the
area for Pokemon that were lost
and had collapsed
from exhaustion.
Magearna was the first
one I met that wasn't
blown away by my explosions.
Magearna liked to
take care of others.
It seems that even
within the kingdom,
it was always caring
for other Pokemon.
i promised I would save
Magearna for its sake
and for everyone who
lives on the plateau.
[MOANING]
They're still kicking too.
Liftoff!
What is it, Flamel?
Princess, I have
something to report.
A previously unseen
design diagram by Nikola
was found in Prince
Raleigh's room.
Design diagram.
ELIPHAS: Nikola designed
a number of gadgets
for defending the
kingdom, the strongest
of them being the wall that
presently surrounds it.
Part of the wall that
defends the Azoth kingdom
can separate and turn
into a floating fortress.
It was designed as protection
in times of an emergency.
However, an uprising
broke out over just
who would claim that power.
ELIPHAS: To stop the fighting,
Nikola sealed the fortress so
that it wasn't able
to move, sealed
in the darkness of history,
along with Magearna.
Sealed it?
What do you mean, sealed?
Huh?
500 years ago,
Magearna was not
simply the princess's playmate.
It had another role,
to defend the princess,
as well as defend the kingdom.
How was it done?
Using this.
Its power has been sealed off.
But by using neo arcane science,
it will finally be reawakened.
[BIRDS CALLING]
[CREAKING]
[GEARS RUNNING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALL GASPING]
Is that--
It's Nikola's
floating fortress.
And to move the tower,
they required the soul-heart.
Still here, princess, I see.
Very well.
After 500 years, I know what my
fortress's first prey shall be,
the princess.
[GASPS]
[INAUDIBLE]
[GROWLING]
[CALLING]
You can do it, Pikachu!
Let's get going.
- Right!
[GRUNTS]
[CHUCKLES] Now fire!
I said fire!
[FIRES]
[WHIMPERS] It's suffering.
Magearna is suffering.
ELIPHAS: This power
was purposefully
created to make all the
people of the kingdom happy.
But all it did was
insight war and hatred.
Our citizens are wounded.
[BEEPING]
Magearna, I'm afraid
I have no choice
but to hide away so that
people aren't able to find you.
I did my best.
I'm sorry.
[BEEPING]
Magearna's still in there.
It says it doesn't
want to do this.
It's suffering!
Magearna, so a piece of
your heart is still remaining.
[ALL GASPING]
Torpedo.
[ROARING]
Megawave!
[ALL MOANING]
[EXCLAIMS]
[ALL ROARING]
Yeni!
Pika!
Pika da!
Hason!
[ROARING]
Ya!
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
Ya!
[MOANING]
[SCREECHING]
[GRUNTING]
Pika!
[SCREAMING]
Chun di.
[ROARING]
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
[ALL SQUEAKING]
Greninja, let's power up!
Bon zaa!
You're not going to
get into mega evolution
without real [INAUDIBLE].
[ALL GRUNTING]
Ta pi!
[GRUNTING]
[SCREECHING]
Pi gone!
[PANTING]
Pi gone.
Help me!
[PANTING]
Pikachu!
Squishy, away!
[HIGH PITCH]
[PANTING] Pika!
Yeehee!
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
[SHOUTING]
Oh, Squishy!
Go on.
They'll take care of this.
Let's lead the rest
of the Pokemon.
OK.
Let's get inside quick.
Run!
Stop!
[GRUNTING]
Right under here.
OK, stand back.
[SHOUTING]
[ALL MOANING]
Let's go!
Grab on!
Yeah!
It feels like we're moving.
Huh?
What?
[EXPLOSION]
Why, here come the guys.
Oh!
Aw.
Raleigh.
Princess Chymia,
you're looking well.
The Pokemon of Nebel
Plateau protected me.
So they did.
[ALL GRUNTING]
I'm warning you.
If you move around too
much, they'll tightened up.
That's nonsense.
[GRUNTING]
Oh, yes.
I was going to show you the
magnificence of Magearna.
Unfortunately, I'm
unable to demonstrate
its true power in present time.
See?
Part of its heart still remains.
[GASPS]
Mean look, if you please.
[GROWLING]
See?
It is no longer able to resist.
[GASPS]
What are you going to do?
Please behold the magnificence
of Magearna's power.
It's struggling.
Magearna's resisting
with all its got.
[GRUNTING]
When either humans or Pokemon
lose the things that they truly
love, their hearts will break.
Firing now!
[FIRING]
[EXPLOSIONS]
It missed?
This is the power,
what Nikola feared.
[GRUNTS]
That voice, Magearna's
voice, I can't hear it anymore.
Meowth, what?
Magearna, poor Magearna,
it's really gone.
[GASPING]
What did you say?
Meowth, I must thank you.
It was worth the trouble of
keeping you around after all.
Its troublesome heart is
finally out of the way.
It isn't Magearna
that I require at all,
but merely it's soul-heart.
You.
You all better prepare yourself.
I can't hold back anymore.
[ROARING]
[EXPLOSION]
Soul-heart, this time we
will wipe out everything
that remains on the plateau.
[REVVING]
[GRUNTS]
Hey, Squishy!
[FIRING]
[BARKING]
[VOCALIZING]
[GROWLING]
[EXPLOSION]
Now what?
All right!
Ee na!
What?
What's happened?
The Pokemon of Nebel Plateau.
They all protected it!
It can't be.
What can those pathetic
little sniveling Pokemon do?
Watch your mouth!
[ALL MOANING]
We're not.
We're not!
We're not pathetic!
[ROARING]
Gengar, shadow ball!
[SNARLING]
Quick, Pikachu.
Use thunderbolt!
- Pizar!
Pika!
And use electroball!
[EXCLAIMING]
[GROWLING]
[SHOUTING]
[GASPS]
[SNARLING] Gengar!
Huh?
Gengar.
What?
[GROWLING]
[GASPING]
I don't think Alva
is doing too well.
[MOANING]
Alva pusom mray.
Eh?
It looks like
they've all woken up.
[GRUNTING]
Oh.
You're awake.
[GASPS] Chymia!
Dear Meowth.
It's James and Jessie!
Volcanion!
We got it.
[GRUNTING]
[BEEPING]
Huh?
Unfortunately, it
seems my plans end here.
It's quite obvious it's
time to give them up.
[CHUCKLES]
I'll simply find a new puppet
to replace Prince Raleigh.
[GRUNTING]
Quick, Greninja,
water shuriken.
Rup, rup!
[SCREAMS]
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
Ninja!
[GASPS]
[ALL GROWLING]
Ah, cut it out.
Ash!
Everybody OK?
And the soul-heart?
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[GRUNTS]
[CLANKING]
Magearna, we're here.
[ALL GASP]
MEOWTH: It's heart
is still broken.
Sure it can move
and all that stuff.
But now, Magearna's voice,
I can't hear it at all.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL SIGH]
[CLANKING]
[ALL GASPING]
Oh, no.
The fortress is set to
fall onto Nebel Plateau.
Can it be stopped?
It can't it looks like
the control system is out.
All because of Alva.
And even if we were
able to escape--
Isn't there any way at all?
We can't change course.
The only way would be
to explode the fortress
into a pile of dust.
Explosions are my specialty.
Hold on.
You're out of water.
Part of the fortress runs on
steam so it has water tanks.
Volcanion, I'll take you there.
Please do.
Everybody, wait on my
sister's flying machine.
I'm going with you.
Pika ka.
Over here!
I can smell water.
[GROANING]
This thing is really stuck.
I've got it.
Go for it, Pikachu.
Irontail!
Pika!
Ah, pika!
Hey, thanks.
[GROANING]
It's moving.
All right.
Yeah!
Excuse me.
You said your name
was Ash, right?
That's right.
I've been acting
like such a fool,
spending so long shutting
myself up in my lab.
That's why Alva had such an
easy time tricking me that way.
You know what I think?
You should head out on your
own journey with a Pokemon.
Huh?
Mm-hmm.
Pika te.
[CRASH]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
Volcanion?
Say, perhaps I should create
an explosion right here.
ASH: It is the center
of the fortress
so I do think it
would be effective.
But then you won't
be able to escape.
Vita vio.
Yeah, that's the truth.
You said you're powerful enough
to level a mountain, right?
So why not follow the plan
and blow it up from outside?
Hmm.
Agreed.
We should all go back together.
Yeah.
Pika!
[CRASH]
Let's hurry.
[ALL GASP]
OK, Volcanion.
Go get them!
[GRUNTS]
Get on board after the blast.
All right.
Just go!
[ALL MOANING]
CHYMIA: Volcanion!
No!
You can't do that!
[GRUNTS]
Well, I'm going
out with a bang.
Time to blast!
Magearna, I couldn't
protect you.
Forgive me.
[ROARING]
Volcanion.
[HIGH PITCHED SOUND]
[EXPLOSION]
You lied to us.
You said we'd all
go back together!
Heego bego.
Magearna?
The Nebel Plateau
Pokemon are safe.
Volcanion protected them.
I wish you could
hear what I'm saying.
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[ALL WHIMPERING]
[PURRING]
[CRYING]
[GASPS]
[ALL WHIMPERING]
[GASPING]
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
Look at the mist.
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTING]
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
Magearna.
[BEEPING]
Chesnah.
[GRUNTING]
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[ALL GASP]
Volcanion, hang in there.
Volcanion?
Oh.
Pika.
[WHIMPERING]
[GASPS]
[SQUEAKING]
[GASPING]
[SNEEZES]
[POKEMON SCREAM]
I told you not to do that.
[POKEMON SQUEAKING]
You, you're still here?
I said I want to
protect Pokemon, right?
I would never tell a lie.
Be davi ya!
[CHUCKLES] All of you.
You know what?
Huh?
I'm going to make you all
honorary Nebel Plateau Pokemon.
Honorary Pokemon.
Hey, I think that
sounds really cool.
Yeah, I want to be one!
Yeah, right, Squishy?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I'm happy to accept.
It's a real honor.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Hey, electric nuisance.
Pika.
Your friend, Ash,
he always seems to be
getting himself into trouble.
Pika?
Take extra good care of him.
Pika, me gatsu.
[LAUGHS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
WOMAN (SINGING):
One of a kind, forged
of steel from a beautiful
night with a mighty heart,
drove men apart.
Forgotten plain, where
only the damaged remain,
that's where I found my destiny.
One more lost refugee, come
with me, feel my soul-heart.
If you've been
seeking a new start,
let me be your guiding light
till the end of the night.
Close your eyes,
know my soul-heart,
keeping watch over the rampart.
Let me be your
shining star, leading
voice from afar from whoever
you were to whoever you are.
Feel my soul-heart now.
Dry all your tears.
I've returned after so many
years Let the creatures
I cherish flourish so now.
This is my vow.
Know forever my soul-heart.
Anyone seeking a new start,
let me be your guiding light
till the end of the night.
(GUITAR SOLO)
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)