When I was a kid,...
...I used to think about
the kind of man...
...I'd grow up to be.
I never thought my life
would turn out this way.
So you're Chris Redfield.
The expert on the living dead.
The big hero.
Bet you killed a lot, huh?
So, Mr. Expert,...
...any advice
on dealing with them?
Yeah.
You got friends?
Heh, heh.
Sure. I got friends.
Family? Yeah.
Got a wife. My folks.
A little sister.
There's corporations
out there creating viruses...
...turning people
into bioweapons.
People like you and me.
Your friends. Family.
There will come a day when
you'll be faced with a decision.
Kill them...
...or be killed.
Doesn't sound
very heroic, does it?
Sorry.
We're approaching the target,
so let's go over everything...
...one more time
so there's no mistakes.
The target is Glenn Arias.
He's wanted internationally
for weapons trafficking.
And we're not talking
about M16s and IEDs here.
We're talking
cutting-edge shit.
He likes doing business...
...anywhere there's
a major conflict.
Intel says that Arias is now
in possession of a B.O.W.,...
...a.k.a. bioorganic weapon.
That's why
the BSAA is here.
They know
how to handle those things.
One of our undercover agents,
Cathy White,...
...went missing weeks ago,
along with her son, Zack.
We have
two objectives today:
Find them...
...and grab Glenn Arias.
Comm check.
No movement outside
the compound.
Split up into three teams.
We're going in.
Clear.
Jesus.
Are you okay?
Go!
Zack?
Yeah.
Go!
Redfield, come in.
Anybody.
What the hell's going on?
Emergency evac.
Get the chopper now.
Get out of here!
Arias.
Thanks to you, I'll have to move
my business somewhere else.
You son of a bitch.
Please.
I'm a businessman.
I make good products available
to anyone who wants to buy.
And at reasonable prices.
For example, this...
...exquisite specimen.
Cathy.
Bastard.
The last moments on Earth...
...are the most beautiful,
don't you think?
The wonderful thing
about my products...
...is that they know
the difference between ally...
...and enemy.
- Congratulations!
- Congratulations.
No!
This is all for you, my dear.
My Sara.
Is that it?
Is that the virus
that's making everyone flip out?
Yes.
It keeps getting
worse and worse.
Attacks are happening
all over the place.
Where'd
you get this?
I haven't seen
this footage before.
It hasn't
been released yet.
They don't want
the public to panic.
Are you kidding me?
There's been like 20 attacks
in the U.S. already.
The BSAA is working
to keep it under control, but...
But it'll
just keep happening...
...until we find
the cause and stop it, right?
Exactly.
This is being done
intentionally.
If we can just find out
who's behind it...
Caramel macchiato?
Did you remember
the chocolate chips?
And the whipped cream
on top.
Good boy.
That's dessert, not coffee.
You know that, right?
Your point?
Nothing. Nothing at all,
Professor Chambers.
The dead coming back to life
and being used as bioweapons.
These insane corporations
have caused...
...far too much tragedy
in this country.
You think this is
more of the same, then?
I don't know.
Based on
what's happened before,...
...this time it feels different.
Someone new
could be behind it.
Is that the vaccine simulation?
The infected are exhibiting...
...different traits
this time around.
I'm attempting to suppress
the artificial virus...
...because it seems
to be the base of the infection.
I saw the computational
chemistry system running.
Are we making
a test drug already?
Of course.
Our technology's come so far
over the years,...
...making a sample
doesn't take that long.
Oh, by the way,...
...we got another delivery
of infected bodies.
A lot.
More than 30.
Who's getting the samples?
The students
are all out today.
And...?
Oh, no. I'm postdoc.
I don't do that.
Fine. Anything you say,
Professor Chambers.
My hero.
What the...?
Aaron.
No.
Why? Why now?
Here?
It's like
it was planned.
Rebecca.
Chris?
You all right?
It's been a while.
You should be wearing
a clean-suit or at least a mask.
Yeah, well...
How you doing?
I'm fine for now.
But shouldn't I be
in quarantine?
Look...
if the virus really
was that contagious,...
...we'd all be dead already.
Besides, quarantine takes
too long, and I need you now.
So don't worry.
We'll get you to a hot shower,
and everything will be okay.
Same old Chris.
Police reports say
the suspects
were armed terrorists.
So far, the number of dead
is reported to be over...
The mass killing in this town
outside of Chicago is under...
Sudden outbreak of violence
claimed many victims today.
Ontario's special task force
has declared
the situation under control.
While that might be
the official statement
on the incident...
It's me.
That doesn't look like
you're resting.
A hot shower
does wonders.
Is that the data you
took from the lab? Yes.
Now that we know the test drug
works as a vaccine,...
...we have to send this out
to other labs ASAP.
The faster
we get this mass-produced,...
...the more lives we can save.
Yeah, maybe.
There's a reason you're here,
isn't there?
You're after someone.
Yeah, a man
named Glenn Arias.
Who's that?
He took over Neo Umbrella
and Tricell's operations.
He's selling the weapons
they created...
...to crime syndicates
and countries at war.
He's a merchant of death...
...using mercenaries and B.O.W.s
to do his dirty work.
And now...
...the dead are rising again.
And you're sure
Arias is behind it?
Yes. After I found out
that your research...
...was the most advanced
in the world...
You hopped on a chopper
and came to see me.
Yes.
And after I saw
how trashed your lab was,...
...it looks like the bad guys knew
about your research too.
Oh...I reported our initial
findings to the WHO.
And then they sent it
to facilities...
...all over the world
that specialize in vaccines.
The leak could've come
from any of those places.
Exactly.
Arias wanted
to disrupt your research.
And now that he's got your data,
he's even more dangerous.
I compared
the new virus's DNA...
...to all the bioweapons
we have on file.
The sequence is extremely close
to the parasitic weapons...
...used by
the Los Iluminados cult.
You think Arias
might be one of'em?
Based on information I have now,
I'm not sure.
Looks like we should go talk
to a real expert.
Real expert?
I can't believe you can read
a book at a time like this.
I guess it's one way
to pass the time.
Well, someone once said,
"Knowledge is power."
Francis Bacon.
It only takes one bullet
to bring your enemy down.
But with knowledge,
you can defeat all evil.
Hey, is it true
what they say?
You switched from special ops
to science geek?
Man, the BSAA's chock-full
of people with weird résumés.
Bet you were pretty brainy
to start with.
So why'd you switch?
That's a story.
I used to be a medic in the
S.T.A.R.S. Unit in Raccoon City.
I guess, in a way,
I've always been
interested in medical science.
Then one day,
I decided to make it my duty
to stop people
from abusing it.
"I thought, "Here are
these corporations,
run by scum,
preying on the weak."
They're like
a disease on humanity.
I want to find a cure,
same as Chris.
The difference is, he uses
his brawn while I use my brain.
So brains and brawns working
together to save humanity.
What do you think
your chances are?
What's that supposed to mean, Damian?
Nothing.
It's just, like, uh, what if
this disease don't got no cure?
The assholes we're after,
they treat life and death...
...like they shooting craps.
Bunch of dicks.
Hey, I just realized
D.C. and Damian...
...aren't talking
about Breaking Bad for once.
Hey, don't go there, Chris.
That shit's ahead of its time.
It's a goddamn masterpiece.
Careful you don't
scare the locals.
Your stealth's for shit.
It's a little early to be
that deep in the bottle, Leon.
Well, look who it is.
The BSAA's golden boy
and Dr. High Hopes.
What the hell do you want?
I got a job.
We need your help.
I'm on vacation.
Let's talk about
Los Iluminados.
Remember the type
of B.O.W.s they were using?
That's so long ago,
I don't remember.
So what, you just gonna
sit around here...
...another week
and do nothing?
I never make plans
that far ahead.
Hey. Another bottle here.
Cancel that.
Hey, who the hell do you...?
Enough! All right?
What do you want,
Redfield?
What do you want, Leon?
Heh.
Cut the shit.
Guys, come on.
Leon, I'm sorry...
...to interrupt your vacation,...
...but we wouldn't be here
if it wasn't serious.
We think you might have
some intel, and we need it now.
What intel?
Second target confirmed.
She stays alive.
Finish the rest.
Copy that.
Look, this shit's
spreading fast and thick.
All of the researchers and staff
at my university were infected.
This again, huh?
It's like I'm stuck
in a goddamn loop.
What?
What are you talking about?
You know that bomb
that went off in D.C.?
Well, it was my mission
to stop the terrorists.
We got to
our rendezvous point...
...and some asshole
ratted us out.
The bomb went off
and everyone on Metro SWAT,
my whole unit, gone.
I keep fighting
and fighting, and fighting.
And instead of seeing an end
to this shit,
it just keeps getting worse.
Is this what
my life's supposed to be?
Fighting the living dead
and the bastards that make'em?
What's the point of it all?
Look...
This is Glenn Arias,
an arms dealer.
His deals
on the black market are so shady
they landed him on a certain
government's hit list.
A smart bomb was dropped
on his wedding.
He lost
his family and his wife.
And now he's got a grudge.
After the attack,
he went underground,
but now he's back with B.O.W.s
and a score to settle.
He said his products
have targeting
capabilities.
From what I've seen,
I believe him.
So you got
an arms dealer on one side,...
...and on the other,...
...a government
dropping bombs on weddings.
Who's the bad guy here?
Arias!
And it's our mission
to bring his ass down!
Your mission, not mine!
Goddamn it, Leon!
Stop! Leon.
With everything
that's going on,...
...you just sit here
and feel sorry for yourself.
And you? You're letting
a grudge get the better of you.
God...
I cannot believe
how alike you two are.
What are you talking about?
You're acting like a couple
of selfish brats right now.
The virus
is right under our noses.
Always has been.
I don't follow.
We don't need
to look for some new virus...
...that Arias
is infecting people with.
The virus is lying dormant
inside of everyone.
Even you.
What we need
to find is the trigger.
Something activates
the latent virus,...
...and only Arias knows
what it is.
But until we find that out,...
...everyone, living and dead,
are his potential weapons.
If we don't
figure this out now,...
...there won't be
little towns like this...
...for you to drink
your sorrows away in...
ever again.
I created a vaccine,...
...and I tried it on myself
and it works.
But until we find out
how Arias triggers the virus,...
...who knows if it'll work
the same for everyone else.
My blood holds the answers.
If I die,
get this to a lab you trust.
I can't imagine
what you two have been through.
But I know that neither one
of you are the type of person...
...who would sit here and argue
while the world dies.
That's not who you are.
Or is it?
That wasn't very nice of me.
Leon!
Patricio!
Wait, wait!
Let me explain. Unh!
Leon!
That guy I told you about.
The one that sold out my unit.
You don't understand. Unh!
This is the guy.
Please, stop.
Hey! What do you...?
Official business. It's okay.
Leon, come on!
What do you want?
Please. You're the only one
I know from the DSO.
It's my family.
You've got to save them.
What?
My wife and my daughter
are in Spain.
An arms dealer
is getting paid...
...by the surviving members
of Los Iluminados...
...to launch a large-scale
bioterror attack.
I know too much. They're going
to kill me and my family.
Did you hear what he said?
It's our lucky day.
"Lucky"?
Are you crazy?
He's gonna lead us to our guy.
What are you talking about?
The name Glenn Arias
ring a bell?
How do you know?
I'm psychic.
I need your help!
My family!
Let me get this straight.
You try and get me killed,...
...and now I'm supposed
to save your family?
Well, how about this?
You tell us
what you know first,
and then
we'll decide if we help.
Son of a bitch!
He was followed!
This is my family.
Please.
Save them.
Damn it.
Rebecca!
Target one down.
Target two secured.
D.C., they hit us at the hotel
and took Rebecca. Track'em.
I know the big guy.
He's with Arias.
What's Arias want
with Rebecca?
I don't know.
I just want to get her back.
There goes my vacation.
Again.
Hi, honey, it's me.
Were you able to get the man
you said would help?
I'm so scared.
Selena misses her daddy.
- Patricio? Hello?
- Can I talk to Papa?
Patricio? Who is this?
Can I talk to Papa? Please.
Where's Patricio? Put
my husband on the phone right...
There's a reason he gave that
to you before he died.
It might have the answers
we need in it.
We have Rebecca's laptop.
We have leads.
Look, man,
I need you.
I succeeded
in reanimating them,
but I haven't figured out
how to keep the bodies
from rotting away...yet.
Practice makes perfect.
Meet my guests.
My family and some of
my dearest friends.
Professor
Rebecca Chambers.
Welcome.
I'm Glenn Arias.
I heard you found a cure
for my merchandise.
For someone so young,
you're quite brilliant.
A cure isn't
the only thing I found.
Really?
Please, tell me more.
I figured out how
the latent virus is activated.
Animality Virus, Professor.
A-Virus, for short.
Your B.O.W.s can tell
who they're supposed to attack.
That's a good selling point
for a weapon.
Engineering them
with that trait
must have
been difficult for you.
But I know how you did it.
There are three strains
of the virus.
One infects them.
A second acts
as a trigger.
The third
gives you the option
of choosing
who your target will be.
A sort of
inactivation virus.
The vaccine...
Bring up the map again.
She must have thought
these outbreaks were related.
See how they're all concentrated
around the Great Lakes?
If what she said is true,
and this thing
can lay dormant inside people,
God knows
how many are infected.
You mixed the base virus
in drinking water.
I'm impressed.
How did you figure it out?
I noticed
a huge concentration
of outbreaks
around the Great Lakes.
Which
just so happens to be
a major source
of drinking water.
But they weren't planned by you.
They happened by accident.
It seems
under certain rare conditions,
the latent virus can activate
without the trigger virus.
Speaking of,
the trigger virus
is probably distributed
through the air...
by a gas.
By themselves, these viruses
either have no potency,
or they run the risk
of activating on their own.
But when combined,
they become an effective,
controllable bioweapon.
Nicely done, Professor.
It's no wonder
you survived Raccoon City.
If the trigger's airborne,
it's harder to control
where it goes
or who gets it.
So then Arias has to be using
some type of vaccine.
That's how he controls
the spread of an outbreak.
He vaccinates anyone
he doesn't want infected first.
Which makes
for a more accurate weapon. See?
You've done your homework
on the A-Virus.
So now what's next?
It wasn't hard for me
to engineer a test cure.
And now
that I know it works,
my team
has my research and my blood.
Your "merchandise,"
as you put it,
will soon be obsolete
on the marketplace.
I hate to say this,
but your research is incomplete.
If you had found the cure,
you wouldn't have been attacked
after you took it.
But you were, weren't you?
Not that it matters.
No, you and your vaccine
will soon be out of time.
Tomorrow, the world will be
a different place.
Arias is planning something big.
Patricio knew
way too much about it.
And that's why
he was killed.
I know what happened.
They came to kill you,
but killed everyone
you loved instead.
It was your wedding day.
The day
time stopped for me.
That's Sara,
my wife.
You look so much like her.
It's not a coincidence
that we met.
It's fate.
Wait.
Where are you going
with this?
I'm redoing the wedding.
This time with you.
I'll rewrite the past.
Rebecca,
meet Sara.
We're going to be so happy.
On second thought...
I'm going to replace
your arm with Sara's.
Maybe that will change
your mind about me.
He's gonna use
the trigger virus on New York?
That's what
it looks like.
He's out of his mind.
"If the outbreak is deemed
uncontrollable,
"tanks labeled
with a green A
"contain the vaccine
and are ready to deploy.
Location classified."
All we have to do
is find that stuff,
and we can
change everyone back.
Like flipping
a safety switch.
But if you were Arias,
where would you keep it?
Someplace he can get to fast.
Someplace secure.
His hideout in New York.
And I bet we'll find
Rebecca there too.
We need
to expedite the release.
We're set for
morning rush hour.
I have a feeling the BSAA
will be heading our way,
so we need that
countermeasure.
You're planning
another attack.
I'm planning our future.
Our time starts now.
"Our"? Yes.
With the last
of my remaining friends,
we will begin
our new life together.
It's time.
Dad...
Wish me luck.
Oh, my God.
Alex! Alex!
I'll call the ambulance.
Not now, goddamn it.
Everybody get a dose
of Rebecca's vaccine?
Good.
What's the status
on the reinforcements?
BSAA and N.Y.P.D. SWAT
are on the ground
in the thick of it.
The state police won't get there
for another three hours.
So that means we have
to nab Arias all by ourselves.
Fantastic.
Yo! The signal's
getting worse.
They're using tanker
trucks to spray the virus.
He's not trying to turn
a couple thousand.
He's trying
to turn them all.
We need to take out
those tankers.
Professor Chambers'
research says
the virus can't handle heat.
It's got the same flash point
as gasoline.
Perfect. Let's light
a match, watch it burn.
I wish we could get
to Rebecca first,
but the priority
is those tankers.
So we got
three things to do.
One, blow up the tankers.
Two, get Rebecca.
Three, grab the vaccine
and deploy it on the city.
And grab Arias. Four things.
Whatever you say, boss.
D.C., Nadia,
you guys work from the Osprey.
Roger that, C.
Gifts from the BSAA.
They said that's the best
they can do for us for now.
Dibs on the bike.
Once the tankers are down,
rendezvous at Arias' place.
Depending on the situation,
we might have
to put Rebecca on hold
until we find that vaccine.
Got it.
Well, you ready to rock?
Are you kidding?
Let's do this.
Damian! Shit.
Damn it.
Any ideas?
I'll lead the dogs away.
You go blow up
some more tankers. Good?
Yeah.
Here, boy. Come on!
This version of the trigger
virus is better than the last.
Stronger.
Your blood was the key.
Thank you so much.
Unfortunately,
increasing the toxicity means
it can't be administered
via gas anymore.
So it's back
to the old needle, I'm afraid.
My apologies.
If our simulations
were correct,
it should start working
in half an hour.
- Three down.
- Going for the next one.
Nice to see you
again, Mr. Redfield.
Arias.
Thanks
to Professor Chambers,
we made
the virus much stronger.
If you can stick around
for, oh, another 20 minutes,
you'll see how strong.
I can't wait for you to meet
the new and improved Rebecca.
The question is,
do you have it in you
to kill her?
My army of the dead
will change
the world for the better.
It will correct the imbalance
caused by recent wars.
If you stay alive long enough,
you can watch with me
as my B.O.W.s
bring down
the most powerful nations,
one by one.
You belong
in a nuthouse, asshole.
Unfortunately,
I'm not crazy.
I want revenge.
I'm hitting
the reset button on the world.
And my merchandise,
my B.O.W.s,
are the right tool
for the job.
Leon.
Sorry I'm late.
I had
to take the stairs.
Maybe this is
what I've always wanted.
A world in flames,
where only the dead remain.
Rebecca's
running out of time.
Then let's split up.
Rebecca.
You okay?
Chris...
No, no, no.
Wait, wait.
Where's the vaccine?
Tell me!
You just had to try to save her.
You're so predictable, Chris.
That's your weakness.
Shit.
Rebecca.
You have to kill me.
No.
We'll find the vaccine.
Just hang on
a little longer.
Diego,
the final stage.
Unleash it.
Redfield!
Found you.
I'm going to spill
your guts all over.
Nadia!
Diego!
Shit.
Catch.
Bye-bye, asshole.
Rebecca?
One more thing
left to do.
So let's do it.
When I was a kid,
I never thought my life
would turn out this way.
And once again, we find
ourselves back where we started.
What do you mean?
We got the bad guys.
Hope we made
the world a little safer.
Hey, Chris.
Yeah?
How much longer
can we keep going on like this?
I don't know.
I never make plans
that far ahead.
Katie Radford