Subtitles By: mxian
w w w . z o o c i n e . o r g
Presented by
Next Entertainment World
A Studio DADASHOW production
in association with FINECUT
Co-presented by
FINECUT and MYUNG FILMS
Executive Producer KIM Woo-Taek
Producers SUH Young-joo, LEE Eun
International Distributor
Finecut
A film of YEON Sangho
We particularly need
national social protection.
You're right.
That old man seems to be injured.
I think we should help him.
- Let's check him out.
- OK.
Sir! Sir! Are you alright?
What a stench!
What happened?
Just a homeless man.
Really?
I would have helped him
if he's injured.
SEOUL STATION
Ki-woong?
Can you get me some water?
Ki-woong!
Are you there?
Where is he?
Why did he go out without telling me?
Country Inn
Where are you going?
How about the rent?
You're several days late!
I'm sorry, ma'am!
Sorry, my ass!
My friend will pay you today,
just give us until tonight, please?
- Tonight, guaranty.
- You just say that for days already!
If you don't pay by tonight,
all your stuff will be in the trash!
Tell that to your boy-friend!
Understand?
Yes, understood.
Excuse me.
You say...
Where the hell is that S.O.B?
What an insolent youngster...!
Oh, I'm broke now, man!
Really? I'll make you an offer.
- Do you have 4 dollars?
- No.
I've worked on some 80%
of new houses in Seoul.
- What?
- I built them.
Motherfucker!
Damn it! I'll throw it in your face!
I'm serious! That'd be a bomb!
It'll kill you!
What are you looking at,
you dirty bald shit?
- Son of a bitch!
- Hey!
- No, look.
- Stop your act.
I mean it. He's an asshole!
- A ruthless jerk!
- Stop! Get lost!
Go somewhere else!
- Go, go!
- No, go...
Too early for that.
A shitty jerk...
It makes me mad!
It ruined my day!
I've seen the other S.O.B today.
Why did you lie down like that?
Why? Blood?
What happened to you?
Have you been bitten?
Oh no, that's bad! Really bad!
What to do now?
Help Center
- Sir, don't you feel well?
- It's awful!
My friend is in a very bad shape.
Blood... He's bleeding badly....
He needs help!
Where is he injured?
Do you know?
What I meant is...
he bleeds here.
His neck bleeds?
Like he has been bitten by something.
Our facility is already full tonight.
Some patients might be better,
I'll ask them to go home.
Please enter.
Thanks, thank you very much!
He's saved!
It was delicious, with extra pieces.
Really?
Mr. Lee!
Have you felt better now?
Yes, why?
His friend needs immediate treatment,
could you let him have your bed?
I'll go prepare the medications,
would you please make the bed neat?
I'll go prepare the emergency kit.
You can bring him in.
Thank you! Thank you!
- You're welcomed.
- I'll wait here.
- OK.
- Thanks.
We're overloaded today!...
Hey.
Who are you?
Pardon?
Are you deaf?
Eh... it's just...
my friend is hurting.
He bleeds...
Where do you live?
I'm kicked out because of you!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to cause that.
I just hope for some
medics to check on him!
- I'm sorry...
- Get lost!
Get out!
- Stupid ass.
- Fool!
That's bad
Really bad!...
Summons the sorcerer.
- Shut up!
- You need the sorcerer..
F/19, approaching Seoul Station
- When did you get up?
- What are you doing here?
Wait, I'm almost done.
You want to have fun?
Do it with my photo.
I've told you that I won't do it!
Not so loud!
We're in a public place!
That's annoying...
Then go outside!
I'm going to call the police!
Hey! Hey!
I'm fed up! What a bum!
Hye-sun! Hey!
Come out here, damn you!
Coming!
That's embarrassing,
what happened?
You have found nothing better than
to turn me into a whore?
- I'm serious...
- Then what?
How to pay for the rent?
We don't even have enough
to pay for the cyber-café site!
About being a whore on the cyber-café site,
I told you I would not
do it again.
- So what?
- What?
You like to sleep under the bridges?
Go to the train station,
ask the homeless
and join them. They know
how to keep you warm!
You said you're gonna get
a part-time job, right?
Even if I work the whole month, we still
won't make enough to pay the rent!
Because you waste your time
at the cyber-café.
Hye-sun, just this month, OK?
You always said
"just this month"!
You don't have to sleep with them,
just steal their money
when they are taking the shower.
And it's in your pocket!
Anyway, you better do something!
I will get a job next month, OK?
How?
You know my pal,
the guy with a tattoo?
He works as a bouncer
for the club with a dome
at the Korean House.
He can hire me.
We can be happy,
Hye-sun, please!
No way!
I won't do it anymore! Never!
What are you talking about, damn it?
Your body is made of sugar or not?
It melts when being kissed?
Answer me.
Do not hit me, asshole.
You think you're strong!
No need to go back tonight.
Wait...
You want me to say it?
You ran away from home
and lived on the street.
I've taken you in,
given you love and hope.
And you don't even want to help me?
Hye-sun, you and me, we're done!
What a selfish bitch!...
Hey...
I don't want to see you again.
Ki-woong!
Hey!
Dad... I'm sorry...
Mr. Hong
What again?...
- Hello?
- Suk-kyu.
Can you talk? How are you?
Is it better?
Speak.
I don't know if I should tell you...
Go to the point.
I found a girl on the Internet
who could be Hye-sun.
What?
You want to have fun?
Do it with my photo.
- What's that?
- That's her?
That's Hye-sun, isn't it?
But how...
Looks like she sells her
services, isn't it?
How can I reach her?
- Hey, calm down.
- Hello?
Calm down, Suk-kyu.
That's bad, very bad!
My boy, go away!
- Go away!
- It's bad, it's awful!
Awful indeed.
It's you that looks awful.
Go away!
No, that's not it.
My friend bleeds a lot from the neck.
If he's injured,
go help treat him.
Get out!
- I say the truth!
- Get out!
We'll close soon!
Get out!
It's bad...
Hurry up!
This fool came to see me,
and said: "Are you
the person in charge here?"
Where is he from?
I don't care, drink.
Pharmacy of Seoul Station
Excuse-me...
It's closed. Go away.
I... I would like
to buy some pain killers.
I have money,
I don't lie to you!
That's true...
- Wait a minute.
- Thank you!
Energy D
Here.
I'm sorry, but...
I don't have enough on me.
Could you sell me just a few tablets?
And a bottle of Energy D.
I can't believe it...!
Hold on, it's bad, really bad...
You must drink this, OK?
Hey?
Hey!
My friend is dead!
He's dead!
The economy is bad,
forget real estate.
Sir! Sir!
My friend is dead!
He's dead because
you didn't want to listen to me!
- Let's take a look.
- OK.
- Where is he?
- There's nobody here.
I'm not in the mood for a joke!
- Strange...
- There's nothing strange here.
Where has he gone?
He lied there, dead,
just one minute ago.
What a waste of time,
in this heat!
What annoyances, these homeless!
Let's go have some cold noodles.
You already ate that.
Good evening, sir!
Sorry I'm late.
It's you who called me earlier, right?
I have to apologize,
she's a little late,
you know, with her popularity.
There's a motel nearby,
please wait there.
Son of a bitch!
Where is Hye-sun?
Who... Who are you?
- I'm her father!
- Father? Daddy?
Hey, ho?
Brother?
Where did you go?
Old man?
Damn it...
Old man!
Hey!
Hey, brother.
There you are? How do you feel?
What are you doing here?
Ki-woong
Son of a bitch!
She does not pick up.
Why not?
If we don't find her tonight,
you're dead.
Understand?
Because she doesn't have any money,
she'll have to return to the inn.
Maybe she's there already,
that's her typical way.
Is it far?
We're almost there.
Here, enter the alley.
Ah yes. All cars stop here.
From here, we walk.
Sir, I have to tell you...
What?
If I wasn't there,
she would be dead by now.
I was like her guardian angel...
Motherfucker!
What right does that gives you, bastard?
Be happy that I don't
break your neck right now!
If anything happens to my daughter,
I'll break your legs.
Is that clear?
Yes, that's clear.
Release me, please!
You son of a bitch!
- I'm almost dead...
- Quick!
Country Inn
Ma'am!
What's the matter with you?
People here are like that.
Don't be surprised.
Holy shit hole!...
Stop!
Quick delivery service, how nice!
Hye-sun! Hye-sun?
Not yet returned.
She hasn't returned yet.
She should be here soon.
Do you like to enter?
She lived in this rat hole?
Sir, help me!
What's this madness?
What happened?
What's that?
What...
Is there something to use as
a weapon here? Anything?
I don't have any weapons...
A weapon, a weapon!
Damn!
Shit, who's that?
Don't open!
Madam, what happened to you?
Shit!
Madam... madam...
You've killed a person...
Hurry! Quick!
What happened to these two people?
All people in the station,
please be calm!
If you don't stay calm,
I'll call the police.
I repeat.
Don't make noises!
Go! Run!
Help!
What happened?
Help us! We're almost killed!
What happens to you?
You fought?
No, no fighting...
Everyone has become crazy!
Look at you!
What a stench!
Get the hell out of here!
Listen to me!
Where do you think you are?
- Get them out!
- Yes sir.
Out! Out!
Jin-young! Jin-young!
What are... these people?
Sir, what happened to them?
Oh my god!
They just cannot stay...
- What, these people?
- Go find out, idiot.
Calm yourself and follow me!
Come on!
Move your ass!
Hit him! On the head!
A little more, catch my hand!
What's this, holy shit?
Call Hye-sun!
Call her now!
No answer! Her phone is dead!
Shit!
Let's go to the car, for now!
Raise your ass!
Over there!
Calm yourself!
Come to your senses!
Look over there!
Compose yourself and look!
Do you see the car?
Descend through this roof,
and draw them into the alley.
No, I can't!
Listen well, you asshole!
Attract their attention by shouting.
Attract them.
I'll take the car and
run to the main street.
You run through the alley to there.
I'll meet you there, understand?
No, I'll get myself killed!
We have no choice.
Otherwise we both will be dead!
Pity...
What are these people?
This is the post of Seoul Train Station!
The homeless are attacking other people!
There are many victims!
Requesting arm force backup!
I repeat. The homeless
have become lunatic.
There are many victims,
many victims!
Hey! We have nothing to do with that!
These monsters suddenly attacked us!
Don't move, asshole!
Son of a bitch... Don't move!
Sir, I'm not a homeless person!
Help me, please.
- You whore!
- I beg you, help me!
Bitch!
Don't move, or I'll take you down!
Dirty monsters, I'll kill you all!
Have attention!
Jump!
Hey!
Go ahead!
Continue, stupid!
OK, OK.
Don't stop!
Dumbass! Look where you're going!
Are you blind?
You owe me an apology!
Hey, boy!
Come back here!
What a stupid ass...
Damn!
Fucking shit! Damn it!
Main street! Where is it?
Shit!
Hop on! Quick!
Quick, sir! Go on!
Jin-young!
Are you OK?
Hey!
Jin-young!
Jin-young...
They can return to life?
Don't move!
Not a gesture, you bastards...
Don't come nearer!
Dirty sons of bitches!
Die, asshole!
Die!
The gun...
The gun?
Give it to me!
Say, mister,
you won't kill me?
Give me that!
2 bullets...
That's it!
We'll be all dead!
Ki-woong...
I am in trouble...
What should I do?
Ki-woong...
Hey, are you OK?
What was this thing?
If you've lived on the streets,
you must have been through many things.
Calm yourself.
Have you ever seen something like that?
First let's find Hye-sun, OK?
Don't worry.
That's it! It's the end...
It hurts...
What's here, holy shit!?
In here! Save us, please!
What happened?
Where do you come from?
Have you been inside?
You are not injured?
Go in there!
Come on!
Let's go!
Mister, mister!
Are you OK? Are you injured?
What happened?
Madness! They've all became mad!
These sick people, suddenly...
It's OK, sir. Calm yourself.
Breathe.
Lie down, and keep calm.
- Here.
- OK.
Breathe.
Very well.
Relax.
Is that your blood?
21 Missed calls: Ki-woong
Hye-sun!
Ki-woong! I'm in a mess!
Where are you?
It's the chaos everywhere.
Your dad is looking for you all over!
What? My dad?
Yes, I'm with him now.
Where are you?
I'll come to get you.
I'm in an ambulance,
on the way to hospital.
Hospital?
OK, we'll go there.
Don't turn off your cell phone, understand?
Sir, Hye-sun just called!
What? Where is she?
Hop on!
What happens?
Sick people, everywhere...
Pardon?
We're bombarded with calls
of victims being bitten.
We are in a critical situation.
I don't know if we can
handle more emergency calls.
Where are those bitten people?
They are in the emergency room.
They must be over-crowded,
I really don't want to join them.
Stop! Stop this vehicle!
Stop right now!
- Why?
- Because they will transform!
Stop immediately!
We must not go there!
Sir, please be calm!
- Don't be upset!
- They all have become crazy!
- Stop! Stop now!
- Sir, please!
- Sir! Calm down!
- Let me out!
- What are you doing?
- That's dangerous!
- Stop this damn vehicle!
- What's the problem?
What happened to him?
- Stop! Let me out!
- Release it!
- Sir, that's dangerous!
- Stop, I said!
Grab him! Pull him off there!
We'll get killed!
Son of a bitch!
Fucking bastard!
I have to run away from here...
We must get out of this place.
We have to pass through here...
Through here...
Quick! Quick!
Pass through below, quick!
Your turn, hurry!
Sir!
Go!
Quick!
Hey, you bums!
You are too noisy, bums!
You run away together?
That makes me sick!
Everyone makes me sick!
The world has gone to shit,
nothing good to live for anymore!
Die! Die, all of you!
Ma'am? What happened to you?
Don't leave me.
No signal.
What can I do now, Ki-woong?
Ki-woong...
It's too quiet.
Hey.
- Call her.
- Yes, sir.
I cannot reach her.
I'll go check out the emergency room,
don't go anywhere, OK?
Yes, I can do that.
Too quiet...
Nobody around...
EMERGENCY
Don't do that, sucker.
Mister...
Kill him! Kill him!
Seriously!
Quick! Jump in!
Go! Quick!
- Sir, quick!
- Shut-up!
- Try call her.
- Yes, sir.
Where could she have been?
Your call could not go through...
No connection!
Damn it!
Mister...
You are a man, right?
We have to run away,
far from here.
Sir, I want to go home.
I have only met bad people.
The bar has only made my debts grow...
Ki-woong, my boy-friend,
he and my dad are looking for me.
We have to run far, far away...
I got to go home.
I want to go home!
Go home?
Me too. I want to go home.
But I have no home!
I want to go home!
Daddy!
What happened?
How can we find her?
We have to find a place above the city.
OK.
Which way?
I think that way.
There!
We're almost there! We're near!
There must be people over-there.
We must go farther, much farther.
Oh, no! Look at that car...
There!
Ki-woong
- Hye-sun!
- Ki-woong!
Hye-sun, are you OK?
Ki-woong, help me, go find me!
Stay calm, OK? Where are you?
I am...
At Station Hoehyeon,
Exit 4, come quick!
What's the matter?
- Hoehyeon, where is it?
- Hoehyeon?
Do it fast!
There! The Hoehyeon station!
Hye-sun, we're coming,
stay where you are, all right?
How can I stay here?
It's very dangerous!
Go find some place to hide!
Hello! Hello! What happens now?
Hye-sun! Hye-sun!
Damn it!
Hey! Over here!
Run! Come on! Quick!
Climb up!
Be quick!
- Son of a bitch!
- Get lost!
Bunch of assholes!
Hello? Ki-woong?
Hello?
- Hello? Hye-sun!
- Please leave a message...
It's disconnected.
Shit!
Let's search the station, hurry!
This is an illegal gathering.
Disperse, or we will have to use force.
That's the end...
Everything's gone to shit...
I need back-up!
Send all you can!
What happens here?
We have to go to Hoehyeon,
can we pass through?
Go away, go back.
I beg you! We have to go there!
Stay away!
Get lost, we're in an emergency now!
Tell us. What is happening here?
There are un-infected people down there!
That's a state of emergency!
You cannot go in there!
- Son of...
- Back off!
People down there could die!
Please let us go through!
What a pain! Stay away!
What a rash!
What's the racket here?
They want to go to Hoehyeon station.
Pardon?
Sir, my girl friend is trapped down there.
I have to look for her.
Please let us through.
- Just us, OK?
- Do us a favor, please.
We must wait for the order.
Please leave, all right?
You intend to let people die?
Please take your son and go away!
Make them go.
Go away, quick!
You think you are the police?
A bunch of invalids!
What are you doing?
Don't move, bastard!
Let me go!
Don't move, asshole!
- We are having a crisis now!
- Are you all right?
He has... a gun...
Hey, hey.
All's well!
Put away your weapon.
Listen, the whole situation
is rather unusual.
The martial law could have been declared.
Go home, and watch the news.
You understand?
Go home.
Get lost, damn shit!
Break up!
Fucking bitch! Go away!
You all right?
She bit him,
he will turn shortly.
It's just a scratch, I'm fine.
It's a small bite, all right?
What do we do now?
I'm OK.
This is an illegal gathering.
Scatter and go home.
Why it has stopped working?
Come on...
Work, please...
Why can't it work?
Forward!
On the double!
Sir, why you send for these soldiers?
What are you going to do?
Yes, sir...
The Commander of
the Capital Defense Force...
has taken control.
Clear out! Disperse yourselves!
Shut-up!
Bunch of bastards!
I've worked for my country!
I'm not like you,
a bunch of craps
You're all good for nothing!
I don't know why
I'm mixed up with you!
Maybe the communists
have manipulated all that!
But not me!
I don't deserve to die here!
I've dedicated my life for this country!
I'm a good person!
I'm someone to do good!
Go away!
Damn it!
I think the same way!
I've given my life to this country!
So how could I get there?
You know what?
This country has nothing to do with us!
We killed ourselves for our jobs,
a bunch of idiots!
But one thing's for sure.
I must survive!
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
Don't go there!
Get lost!
Die!
Shit!
Where's that?
Mister...
Mister!
If I had had a place to go,
I would not have stayed
at the Seoul Railway Station...
Mister... mister...
Quick! Quick!
A little more, quick!
You're almost there!
Quick! Quick!
No!
Don't look down there!
Over here!
You can do it!
No! No!
That's it! Try one more!
Faster!
Come on!
A little faster!
You're almost there!
Be brave! A little more!
Help! Help me!
Hello? Anyone there?
Anyone in here?
Help! Please!
Rubber Wood Table $180.
Made in Vietnam
Hello!
Hello? Hye-sun?
Are you all right?
Ki-woong, Ki-woong,
I'm still alive.
Where are you?
I am...
Appartment Darim
Witness Building
Appartment Darim...
in Witness Building.
- Everything all right.
- Ki-woong.
I know how to go there.
I'll come right away.
Hurry.
Quick...
Hye-sun, Hye-sun.
Hye-sun...
Ki-woong.
It's over. We can go home now.
Ki-woong, Are we saved?
Yes, everything's fine,
we can go home.
And daddy? Where is he?
Don't worry, he's fine.
We go different ways
to look for you.
- He's really OK?
- Yes.
- He didn't feel well...
- He's fine now.
That's good, really good.
Look! There he is.
- Sir!
- Dad!
I've found her!
Hye-sun, my dear!
There you are!
Hye-sun! At last I found you!
I almost die to find you,
little whore!
That's not my father!
What?
That's my...
You must repay
when borrowing money.
How could you make me wait like that?
Everything, just because you ran away...
Oh my god!
Shit!
You're deep in shit to your neck!
No, wait... You said you're her father!
That's right, idiot!
I'm daddy of all whores
that work for me!
Call me daddy!
Come on, go home, quick
Come on!
Let me go!
Don't do that, OK?
Son of a bitch!
Why dare you?
I'll kill you!
Come here, asshole!
Get up, bastard!
Bastard, I'll kill you!
- Boss...
- What?
- I beg you...
- Why do you cry?
Please let me go back home.
I want to go home!
Go home?
Sure, as you wish.
After you've paid me my money, bitch!
Until then, you will not
go anywhere, filthy whore!
Stupid bitch!
Poor idiot!
How pitiful!
- Let me go!
- Shitty whore...
Pitiful!
You are pathetic!
Motherfucker!
Holy shit!
No, I beg you!
Ki-woong!
Go there!
Motherfucker...
Fuck, where...?
Where did she go?
Damn!...
Eh?
Where dis she go, damn it?
This viper...
Where is she?
Why is this place so big?
When can I live in a place like this?
Hye-sun! Because of
runaway debtors like you,
I'll never could live
in this kind of luxury!
Wow!
Look at this! What wealth!
If only I could fuck here.
Hye-sun!
If you haven't taken my money,
I could have paid for this place.
My dear, let's go eat.
I'm dyeing of hunger.
Hye-sun.
Hye-sun!
Listen. You keep saying
you want to go home,
you want me to make
a confession to you?
After you left, I came to your home
to request my payment.
Your dad was very ill.
You know what I told him?
That you've taken my money
and run away,
so he has to pay for
the debt of his daughter.
He asked me to return next week.
He needed one week.
You know what I did?
I patiently waited one week.
But he never came
to see me after one week.
So I came back to his home.
Holy shit!...
You always said
you wanted to go back home,
but do you know what I saw over there?
Your sick father had fled.
That's what kind your father was!
The daughter disappeared
with borrowed money,
and the father set sail
to abandon his child.
Hye-sun,
the home you knew doesn't exist anymore.
Die!
Filthy whore!
Sneaky rat!
Poor connection!
What's this, holy shit?
Hey!
Hey! What's wrong?
Wake up. Hey! Hye-sun?
My god!
Don't die, baby, Hye-sun!
Don't do that to me! I'm sorry!
Hye-sun! All is my fault!
Don't die!
Pay back my money, whore!
Shit!...
Hye-sun...