Subtitles by explosiveskull
Captain Sakaki, please respond.
We should be able to communicate.
My demands are to leave
Planet Tau-e immediately,
and abandon the emigration project.
Until I hear from the captain,
I'm not moving from here.
The Tau-e emigration decision was made
by the Central Committee.
Your interference will be classified
as a first-degree crime.
People will not survive on that planet!
If I'm a criminal,
then the Committee members are murderers!
Look at this.
The emigration list is made up
of volunteers.
Why do you interfere?
Shut up!
You gathered old men and women,
coerced them, and call that volunteering?
You're going to kill them!
All you want to do
is reduce the mouths to feed!
Watch your words, Captain!
We're communicating
through an open channel.
Everyone on this ship can hear us, right?
Right now, this ship is trying
to abandon the elderly people.
We may be low on resources.
But can this be forgiven?
Weren't we looking for the promised land
that would save us?
Can you really abandon the weak
and continue to hold your head up high?
Captain Sakaki.
I'll wait one hour.
If this ship doesn't change course,
I will blow up this shuttle.
I'm not bluffing!
Please stop already, Captain Sakaki.
It's true that we, the volunteers,
really do want to go to Tau-e.
We're not being chased out or anything.
Don't be foolish! This is suicide!
We've been on this ship for over 20 years
while wandering through space.
The young people may be able
to endure this.
But for us, we're at our limit.
But... if you give up, then...
Haruo.
- ...then it's all over!
- Haruo!
It's okay.
At least, when I die,
I'd like to be standing on land.
It could be on any planet.
Grandpa.
PLANET OF THE MONSTERS
It began in the last summer
of the 20th Century.
Look at that! It's a monster!
This is an unbelievable scene.
For the first time...
humanity realized they weren't the rulers
of this planet anymore.
Monsters.
From the depths of the earth and sea,
or even from a forgotten divine myth,
they kept appearing, relentlessly.
In order to bring an end
to humanity's prosperity.
The UN Countermeasure HQ
has named it "Godzilla."
And then, in the end,
our worst nightmare appeared.
Godzilla.
Human or monster,
it burned everything in sight.
The avatar of destruction.
At 2:30 EST, a large-scale nuclear attack
was launched against Godzilla, but failed.
At midnight, the EC Allied Forces
announced they have begun evacuations...
The earth collapsed
and the skies rained fire.
And then, it was not only Earth's humans
who feared its destructive power.
Above the UN building,
mysterious flying objects...
People of Earth, we are the Exif.
We are observers and predictors.
We have come to tell you of your destiny.
The time of destruction is nigh.
You must discover a path to devotion.
We are the Bilusaludo.
Our home planet, the third planet
in the Bilusaludia Binary System,
was swallowed by an accursed black hole
and destroyed.
We are requesting immigration
to this solar system's third planet.
If you accept, we promise to eradicate
your greatest threat, Godzilla.
Those from a far away galaxy, who were
after this blue planet for themselves,
didn't wait for this paradise of oxygen
and water to become scorched earth.
- Godzilla has passed the defense line!
- The walls will give us some time.
A3 and A5 blocks' AIs are silent!
- Mecha-Godzilla won't activate!
- Why won't it activate?
Atomic breath detected! Incoming!
The fourth armored wall is gone!
It's over!
We have no choice. Evacuate!
All units, evacuate! Hurry!
Wait! If we can activate Mecha-Godzilla,
we can defeat it!
We're leaving, Galu-gu!
However, even with the humanoids'
gathered intelligence,
the destroyer's powers
overwhelmed us completely.
Where's Mom and Dad?
They'll catch up soon.
See? That's the bus.
Hey, what's that?
It's Godzilla!
Godzilla's here!
Haruo! Hurry up!
I remember the flames that burned the sky,
and the sunken, despaired faces
of the adults.
We departed hoping to find
another inhabitable planet.
However, we would soon pay the price
for such foolish optimism.
In the frozen, black space,
this was a kind of hell
worse than our planet destroyed in flames.
There were endless days of suffering
from hunger, thirst, and cold.
Some fell to disease.
And others gradually lost their sanity.
Our brethren's numbers plummeted
in the blink of an eye.
Even those still living had no time
to mourn the dead.
Kindness and pride are now
long-gone stories of the past.
A fairy tale from the time we each had
unlimited access to water and oxygen.
Where are we going... and for what reason?
Must we endure the misery
of having prolonged our lives
by sacrificing others?
Why are we alive?
Why?
Were you having a nightmare?
So, you're here, Metphies.
It's also my job to listen
to a prisoner's confession.
So I should repent to your god?
I'd settle for a fake confession, too.
Here's the data you asked for.
Thank you.
You have quite the persistence.
I don't have anything else to do.
Won't you get in trouble
if they find out you're helping?
I have an interest in your enthusiasm.
Why are you so curious
about digging up forbidden data
that anyone would otherwise
wish to forget exists?
"Why," you ask?
I've also been thinking "why."
Ever since I was thrown in here,
that word won't get out of my head.
Why have we become so miserable?
Was it inevitable? A justified punishment?
No.
The reason we're suffering
is because we lost to that bastard.
We didn't fight to the end,
but gave up and ran away.
Everything is destiny.
We humanoids had no way
of fighting that monster.
I disagree.
And I'll show them.
We just needed the right strategy
and planning,
and humanity could have defeated it.
I'll prove it.
It's a strange thing.
Unlike the young ones, your generation
experienced the calamity firsthand.
And yet, it's as if
you want to see that creature again.
Based on the Gematron calculation,
the predictions look disappointing.
The possibility of finding
a habitable planet in 20 years is 0.1%.
If we want better results than Tau-e,
the outlook is even grimmer.
The lack of resources is severe.
Even doubling the discomfort index,
life will be unsustainable in eight years.
The landing ship explosion the other day
was a significant psychological blow.
- This is getting...
- Indeed.
We need to examine scenario number three
in a realistic way.
Returning to Earth.
It's already 11.9 light years away.
There's no precedent for traveling so far.
It's too risky.
Gematron's guidance isn't bound
by time or distance.
As long as the nuclear reactor
has sufficient energy, travel is possible.
According to the ship's simulator,
it requires 170% of its operation ratio.
I don't know if we can mobilize
the manpower.
Would it be a constructive decision
to abandon the emigration?
That's the problem.
If we return to Earth,
would we be able to survive?
It is currently impossible to calculate
how much time has passed on Earth.
At the very least, a few thousand years.
Since we fled Earth,
the environment should have calmed down.
It's possible it could've gotten worse.
The problem is that strange thesis
published on the shared server.
Why would that research thesis appear
at a time like this?
The writer remains anonymous,
but it contains information that requires
special log-in credentials to access.
The author aside, there's probably
an informant in the Central Committee.
R-Ridiculous!
There's an electromagnetic shield
under the body's surface?
It's not a normal organism?
No, its whole body is like a giant coil.
Is that true?
So, what happened in the end?
It's kind of weird.
A new Gematron code is using 80%
of the calculation server's power.
Eighty percent?
Isn't it the analysis for predictions?
Still, for a simulation, it's too much.
So, the rumor
of returning to Earth is true?
It's 11.9 light years in one go.
Is a subspace jump-warp even possible?
It's not a problem
if we use Gematron calculation.
I heard it directly from Navigation.
Gematron, huh?
The ship leaders turn to the gods,
as usual.
Maybe even that new anti-Godzilla tactic
was a leak from the higher-ups?
Man, are we going to fight it again?
It's a monster that withstood an attack
of 150 nuclear warheads at once.
That's 40 megatons of nucleoplasm total.
But the thesis contained new strategies
on how to fight it.
Huh?
It's me.
Hey, come in.
So, the Central Committee is leaning
towards going to Earth, huh?
Not entirely.
To give up searching
for a habitable planet
means someone has to bear
that responsibility.
If they're so weak they give up drifting
after only 20 years, it can't be helped.
Well, I do sympathize.
They haven't dealt with the loss
of their home planet as long as we have.
And then, there's your practical joke.
Obviously, it's a headache for Mori.
I uploaded a new version this morning.
Did you read it?
Yeah. When I downloaded it,
it already had over 400 views.
Though the file was deleted
three seconds later.
Our delinquent captain sure is popular.
When there's rumor of returning to Earth,
we get more talk of Godzilla.
It's effective for ridiculing
the Central Committee.
Haruo is unaware of
the Central Committee's expectations.
He was researching Godzilla
purely for personal interest.
But this thesis has content that will
support our plan to return to Earth.
Its claim is that
Godzilla can be defeated by human hands.
If you can't understand its contents,
it just sounds like crazy prattling.
Earthlings harbor that much fear
of Godzilla.
So, do you think
it's just crazy prattling?
This analysis report?
No, it's actually quite interesting.
So much so, I think better of him.
Godzilla is not invincible.
It's humanity's fault for giving up
on the fight.
That's what Haruo thinks.
He analyzed that old data because
of you Exifs' Gematron calculation.
It was impossible for Earthlings
at the time.
Are you saying that, if the weak-point
analysis had been made in time,
that humanity
still wouldn't have been victorious?
And if they did defeat Godzilla,
then it was only a matter of time
until Exif's cult took over Earth.
Even if Bilusaludo's Mecha-Godzilla
had defeated Godzilla,
no one knows
who it would have bared its fangs at next.
However, we failed in the construction
of Mecha-Godzilla.
And you couldn't brainwash Earthlings
with your religion.
That's history now.
The what-ifs are only fairy tales.
Subspace jump-warp procedure,
now entering phase two.
Activating shields for all ship sections.
Bypassing electricity
for the gravitational coil engine.
Initiating Gematron calculation
and gravitational coils controller.
Begin cluster connections with Gematron
calculation crystal and central AI.
Gravitational coil engine
for all sections functioning normally.
Preparations for spin complete.
Subspace coordinate system render
will be displayed on the central hologram.
Attention all personnel.
This ship, Aratrum,
will soon initiate subspace jump-warp.
Estimated emergence coordinates are near
the solar system's third planet, Earth.
Based on the ship's time,
22 years have passed since our departure.
This subspace jump-warp
will be the longest we've traversed.
Finally. The real Earth!
I wonder if we can see the ocean?
That'd be awesome if we can!
The longest? Is this really safe?
...no idea what changes
Earth's environment has undergone.
After an investigation,
if we conclude the environment
has become unfit for human survival,
we will collect resources...
Hey, is the real Earth
prettier than the hologram?
Yes, it is.
Entering Gematron-predicted coordinates.
Suspending main propulsion drive.
We now have all the Gematron numbers.
Irrational numbers converted to integers.
Computing time-space recon point.
Chances of a wormhole appearing is 440%
in a simulated observation.
Releasing gravitational coil output
for each section of the ship.
Maximum spin.
Captain, on your order.
Initiate jump-warp.
Jump-warp initiated. Commence shift
into phase one space travel.
Gravitational coil at max speed,
running stable.
Arriving at launch point
required for final trajectory.
Breaking through subspace.
Amazing.
Hey, it's really blue!
- That's the ocean?
- It's beautiful.
That's Earth?
Yes, that's right.
It really is blue!
To think that I'd see it again.
Disabling shields in all sections.
Normal travel mode stable.
Distance from Earth, 1,800 kilometers.
Recalculating low orbit entrance errors.
Our Earth that was taken from us.
Orbit errors corrected.
Now entering low Earth orbit.
If we can't land on Earth,
we'll have a revolt on our hands.
It's too soon to be pessimistic.
Let's just wait for the scouting report.
Unmanned recon drones
launching in sequence.
All drone feedback systems are stable.
Begin dispersion to specified areas
for surveillance.
Entering the stratosphere.
Drone temperature stable.
Altitude 30,000 meters, beginning descent.
Altitude 15,000 meters,
entering the troposphere.
Stellar observation parallax calculated.
Elapsed time for the solar system
is approximately 10,000 years.
It's been 10,000 years? That long?
It's more than I imagined.
This could be good news.
With that much time,
the ecosystem must have changed.
Not even Godzilla...
I wonder.
It's possible it could've multiplied.
That thing is a genetic aberration.
It's impossible!
Recon drones are at a scouting altitude
of 2,000 meters.
Receiving visuals.
Drone six displaying sound signal monitor.
Just the sound of the wind?
We can't see anything.
Can you lower the altitude?
All drones descending.
There are thick particles floating
in the atmosphere.
Average visibility less than 300 meters.
This is...
Picking up electromagnetic interference.
This isn't just a normal fog.
Switching drones to sensor monitors.
Each drone's altitude at 500 meters.
Atmospheric density is increasing.
Further descent by remote is impossible.
Is this a forest?
Or some kind of complicated terrain.
Can you increase the scan power?
Its reflection is diffused,
so this is the limit.
What's that?
It's moving.
Drone six,
switching to sound wave reconnaissance.
Temperature around drone six
is increasing drastically!
- What?
- What's happening?
Drone six, lost!
Estimated energy output around drone six
approximately 180 gigawatts.
High probability of high-energy
electron particles, or atomic breath!
M-Maybe it was thunder or...
Idiot! No one would ever forget that roar!
Damn it. It's still on this planet.
You're there, aren't you?
You're still there!
If the characteristics match this closely,
then that was Godzilla,
or a threat similar to it,
and it must be eliminated.
Our one advantage is that it acts
independently rather than in a pack.
How can you say that for sure?
The concentration of radiation.
As you're aware, Godzilla is a creature
that scatters heavy radiation in its wake.
However, even though the terrain
has undergone change,
the toxins present in the atmosphere
are maintaining stable numbers.
If we reverse calculate the emission data
gathered in the past three days,
multiple Godzillas seem unlikely.
Even now,
Godzilla is a unique genetic defect
and cannot be considered
a normal living creature, is what I mean.
However, it's been 10,000 years.
How can it still be alive?
There are cases where lotus seeds survived
for 2,000 years.
It also may be repeating cycles
of dormancy every few thousand years.
Or, over 10,000 years,
it could have multiplied
and diminished in number,
with this being the last surviving one.
Godzilla's biology is beyond
every known aspect of life science.
And we can't ignore the possibility
that it could be immortal.
Studies and research
aren't this meeting's main subject.
We humanoids cannot coexist with Godzilla.
However, if that is indeed Godzilla,
and the last one,
then there is only one option.
Complete extermination.
Are you utterly insane?
As you are all aware,
we have drafted anti-Godzilla strategies.
You mean that anonymous thesis?
We don't even know who wrote it!
It's from a specialist's investigation.
It's deemed as promising information.
I am also prepared to release the name
of the person who wrote it, right here.
However, there are conditions.
And what would those conditions be?
To drop the charges regarding
the stolen secret information, and then...
release Captain Haruo Sakaki on bail.
Captain Sakaki? It was him?
You got us, Metphies.
All shall be according to God's will.
It's your turn.
Haruo.
It's here. This waveform is generating
the electromagnetic metamaterial.
Since each of Godzilla's cells
can function as a powerful electromagnet,
it emits a high-output,
high-frequency electromagnetic pulse
and generates
an asymmetrically permeable shield.
A physically impervious shield?
It may be enormous,
but can a creature even do that?
And if that were true,
how can we even begin to fight it?
It's only for about 1/10,000 of a second,
but it emits a noise periodically.
If we use an interference wave,
we can amplify that noise
to fracture the metamaterial,
and we'll target that point.
So by attacking a single point,
we can take that colossal thing down?
There should be an organ
amplifying the electromagnetic pulse.
If we destroy that,
we can neutralize the shield.
And where is it?
Unknown.
There isn't enough data
in our visual records.
We need to observe Godzilla
and analyze the emission pattern.
As you know from past battles,
we can confirm Godzilla has
tremendous regenerative abilities.
The destroyed organs will regenerate, and
in the seconds before the shield goes up,
we need to shove an EMP probe
into its body and destroy it from within.
The main issue with this operation
is the changed atmosphere,
and the electromagnetic wave interference.
To observe and find Godzilla's weak point,
we need detailed coordination
with accurate attacks,
so close quarters combat is required.
And for each process,
we need manpower,
otherwise we cannot succeed.
Preposterous!
Even if we gather all the races,
there are only 4,000 of us.
I cannot approve an operation
where lives can be lost.
Captain Sakaki.
I'll be blunt.
In order for your operation to work,
how many people do you need?
Combat engineers, infantry,
and special forces, so three battalions.
If I form two companies from each,
we're looking at about 600 people.
Out of the question.
Those who do not fight,
know not how to fight evil.
Those gathered now, unified as one,
shall come to know God's mercy.
Give praise to God.
All shall lead down the devoted path.
Garbetrium guidance be with you all.
This is Colonel Elliot Leland,
commander of the Earth Landing Brigade.
Everyone, continue your tasks and listen.
All 600 gathered here
are the chosen elite forces
who have decided to give their lives
to fight against Godzilla.
Everyone correctly understands
that there will be no constructive outlook
if you're trapped in an old society.
Instead of a fake promised land,
we will take back our homeland,
and promise prosperity
to the next generation.
For the sake of humanity's future,
I look forward to everyone's efforts.
All assembled landing ships
have exited the gates.
Now closing the first launch gate station.
That speech sounded like you wanted
to pick a fight with the Committee.
Hey, Haruo.
Didn't you also want to get
the Committee members frustrated?
With the current system,
those members will just dry up and die.
There aren't any comfortable chairs
for us.
But if we defeat Godzilla,
then the story will be different.
A new hero will arrive.
Our era will come.
A hero, huh?
You're just like when you were a kid.
Don't take it the wrong way.
You're still on bail status.
We went through a lot
just to get you back out.
Commander.
All landing ships have assembled
in low orbit.
All ships, enter in sequential order.
Roger.
All ships,
begin entry in sequential order.
Ship ten, ignite engine.
Deploy anti-aerodynamic drag
and heat shield.
You look unhappy.
Even though your wish is being granted.
I wonder if everything will go
according to plan.
It'll be okay. As long as we have the hero
who will guide them.
Are you a Leland sympathizer?
Well, the one I put my hope in
is you,
Haruo.
The one true path to glory
can only be opened through devotion.
This is our, the Exif's, creed.
There are only a few Earthlings
who embody that.
You're a rare exception.
You overestimate me.
You are the one who is worthy
of fighting Godzilla.
The time will come soon enough
when that can be proven.
Ship temperature stable.
Passing the stratosphere.
Altitude 30,000 meters.
Igniting arc jet thrusters for cruising.
Once we go under those clouds,
we won't see the sun anymore, huh?
This planet has been
completely changed, too.
Now entering the troposphere.
Altitude 2,000. All ships,
begin navigating towards landing zone.
The visibility's terrible.
Switching the ship's probes to ultrasonic.
Begin image processing.
Company A, landing zone confirmed.
Obstacles detected.
As the reconnaissance drones reported,
this is a thick forest.
Securing landing point now.
Prepare the thermobaric bombs.
Roger. Dropping thermo-pressure warheads.
They're being grandiose over there.
Well, the special forces will land
on impeded terrain.
What?
An obstacle collided
with the ship's exterior.
No issues so far with power and steering.
An obstacle?
Lieutenant Colonel Galu-gu,
Company E has also landed.
We will now set
the combat engineers' traps.
Okay.
The old Tanzawa Pass, huh?
If it was sunny,
it would've been beautiful.
With this heavy fog,
a visual battle would be impossible.
Lieutenant Colonel Galu-gu, please look.
This is...
Doesn't it look like
something scratched it?
I hope the others are okay out there.
Get the transmission balloons!
You don't need to unload
the medical supplies.
Transmission balloon reception favorable.
Companies B and C special force units
will reach their destination on schedule.
Companies D and E will deploy artillery
as the combat engineers lay down traps.
Okay, the first battle formation
is going according to plan.
Whichever company finds Godzilla first,
open fire with the special forces.
Provoke it and divert its course.
What's important is to observe Godzilla's
electromagnetic waves when it's attacked.
We'll analyze this data to see which organ
emits the electromagnetic wave.
Once we destroy that, we can neutralize
the asymmetrically permeable shield.
And finally, we'll chase Godzilla
into this Tanzawa Pass,
and slow it
with traps set by the engineers.
The artillery unit will then open fire
from a close range.
We'll amplify the pulse noise,
attack all at once, and destroy the organ.
The shield will go down for a few seconds,
and then we'll use EMP probes to end it.
If we can't find the amplifying organ,
we can't place the infantry.
Exactly.
The special forces analysis of the pattern
will influence the plan.
So they'll spread out into a wide area,
and advance while analyzing the enemy.
Cooperation is key.
But who knew we'd have to rely
on something this pathetic to communicate?
If we can transmit
through this convection cloud,
the drones in the stratosphere will relay
our communication with no issues.
But in this fog,
electronic communication will be limited.
What is going on
with this planet's atmosphere?
That's what we're trying to find out.
Colonel, I'd like to form
an investigation team.
If I can borrow three teams, as planned.
The scouting team takes priority.
I'll give you two teams.
All right, then.
I'd like to go, too. I want to see with
my own eyes how this terrain has changed.
You heard him.
- Master Sergeant Yuko Tani, you're up.
- Yuko?
You'll be his handler.
As you know, he's been released on bail.
So be careful handling him.
Understood.
Unbelievable. Are these really the plants
growing on Earth?
Is this what I saw in the ship's records?
Trees, was it?
They look different, though.
Don't touch it!
In some places they're sharp as razors.
It'd be deadly
if your airtight suit got a hole in it.
Why did you request to join this mission?
Because you're involved, Captain Sakaki,
and set up the operation.
Please don't call me that.
Just Haruo is fine.
I've always wanted to meet you
so we could speak in person.
I wondered if it's because of you, Cap...
Haruo, that grandpa died at Tau-e.
I...
The bombs that you brought
inside the shuttle,
I heard from security
that they were definitely all removed.
But then the emigration group...
Do you think it was an accident?
You don't think it was?
You said the Central Committee
wanted to reduce passengers.
They could have used some trick
so the emigration group wouldn't...
The Central Committee isn't that corrupt!
That's what I want to think. I don't
want to be suspicious of my comrades.
Haruo.
No, that's not it. I couldn't forgive
myself for wanting to be suspicious.
I don't want to be so judgmental
of humans.
But being on that claustrophobic ship
and living on minimal supplies,
it's normal for people
to become mistrustful.
Godzilla didn't just steal Earth
away from us.
Justice, faith, and the basic pride
we have as humans...
we've come to lose them, too.
And that's why
we need to fight Godzilla again.
So we can take back the dignity we lost.
This is...
Professor! Please come!
Over there!
Ruins?
But they couldn't have lasted
10,000 years.
Captain Sakaki!
I see.
The lichen used the building's surface
as a seedbed and became fossilized.
Afterwards,
the building materials weathered away,
but the fossilized fungus
must have retained the shape.
This is Earth's civilization.
People used to live here?
Haruo?
It remembered.
Although we've forgotten,
this planet has always remembered us.
Of course. Even after undergoing change,
this is still our Mother Earth.
The planet that belongs to humans.
We'll take it back... no matter what.
With our own hands.
Where's the scouting team?
Haven't they responded yet?
It's probably the electromagnetic waves.
The reception area
is five kilometers, right?
Yes.
Unexpected atmospheric changes
are also possible.
There are reports of geomagnetic storms.
But we're connected with
Martin's investigation team. It's strange!
Hey, what's that?
Is it the scouting team?
What?
Damn it! Kill it!
- What?
- Something happened at the camp!
- Professor Martin!
- Let's go back, now!
This doesn't correspond to any
of Earth's primary species records.
It must be a sudden variant,
otherwise, how could something evolve
into a form like this?
Would living organisms
go through such a change,
even if 10,000 years have passed?
We collected
and analyzed the forest's plants,
and by using carbon dating,
I know how much time has passed.
And it looks to be within a 50-year range
of 19,200 years.
So our time away keeps increasing.
The special cell characteristics of this
beast and the plants are interesting.
Okay, it came off.
The flora and fauna have differences,
but also similar, wide-ranging traits.
Along with characteristics
very similar to metal,
they have bodily functions
that exert powerful magnetism.
The same as Godzilla?
Yes. This beast is small, but it may be
in the same family as Godzilla.
What's surprising is that the plants also
have strikingly similar characteristics.
So this fog causing
the electromagnetic disturbance...
The particles in the air
are the pollen of this forest's plants.
It could also be their natural chaff.
If the fog's caused by the organisms
and not the weather,
we have to burn the entire forest down
to disperse this fog?
So, we have no choice
but to abandon our first plan of waiting
for the weather to clear up a bit
before we attack.
That's not all.
If dangerous beasts are wandering around,
I have to split up our troops
for camp defense.
We can reassign groups
to join the special forces.
Don't be ridiculous!
You want everyone to wander in
this unknown environment without a plan?
Then what's your plan?
Retreat.
Logically, that's our only choice.
What are you saying?
The water and plants are toxic,
and the wild animals are hostile.
The only benefits here
are air pressure and gravity.
It'd be the height of stupidity
to fight Godzilla to reclaim this planet.
This is our home!
You're giving up?
Not only once, but twice?
We can settle on the surface of the moon,
and collect resources from Earth.
If we're thinking about safety,
it's a more realistic plan.
Weren't you going to defeat Godzilla
and become a hero?
I underestimated the situation.
My eyes are open now and I've learned!
You're going to be a coward now?
From wild beasts alone,
we have 12 dead and 35 critically injured!
Without even seeing Godzilla,
this is the outcome!
We can't play war with new soldiers
who've never fought in actual combat.
Retreat?
I do agree with the commander's decision,
but the problem is, how do we retreat?
That attack just now
left us with heavier equipment loss
than human casualties.
Is that so?
Frustratingly, those lizard things
destroyed four landing ships.
Ship one and two's fuel systems and
ship three and four's engines are dead.
We can't return to the mother ship
orbiting this planet anymore.
If that's the case,
we need to gather Company A,
and join the company with enough
transit power to get us all back to space.
Companies B and C are special forces
like us, so they can't do it.
So we must join the artillery unit
and the trap materials unit,
which are Companies D and E.
In order for us to escape
the wild animals' habitat,
we must move through
this old Tanzawa Pass.
And our first plan was to go through
the projected encounter area for Godzilla.
That's correct.
We need to pass the area
where Godzilla appears frequently.
Of course, if we run into Godzilla,
that would be extremely awful for us.
In order to secure safe passage...
We would need backup
from Companies B and C.
However, if we join up and form a cluster,
we'll be open to an atomic breath attack.
What's the safest plan?
While remaining spread out,
repeatedly reciprocate the threat
and keep securing each other's safety.
Yes. This is, however, quite close
to Captain Sakaki's original plan,
with very few changes.
Listen here.
This is a retreat tactic, no matter what.
We will not take any action
to lure out Godzilla.
Once all units reach the gathering point,
we complete the mission,
and return to the mother ship.
Be careful of that crack.
Okay, that's good. This way!
There's no fuse,
but it could still explode, so be careful.
- That's a high explosive. Be careful.
- Yeah.
Company B, C, and all landing ships,
heading to Company D camp.
- Confirm landing zone.
- Landing zone confirmed.
All ships rotate bearing
to 202.5 degrees.
- Marker lock.
- Roger.
So what's the situation?
Company B, Company C reserves,
and Company A hover squads
are to join with Company D and stand by.
What's going on? Is the plan a go, or no?
Based on Commander Leland's orders
to the hover squads,
special forces
will abandon the base camps.
After all units reach the final
gathering point, we'll retreat.
We'll follow our original path,
but we won't search for Godzilla.
So, what? Did we come down to Earth
just to display our marching orders?
Company A's damage
must have been that severe.
I heard there were
smaller Godzilla-like creatures.
They were strong enough
to destroy a power suit.
Leland, that coward. If he's going
to go along with Haruo's madness,
he has to resign himself
from the beginning.
They had us design this,
and now we have to abandon it
because of overcapacity?
Approaching Godzilla's
projected contact area.
Hurry! We need to
get through this area quickly!
Can't this thing pump out any more speed?
By shifting parts around,
we got ship two moving.
It's all we can do to keep it hovering.
I guess I'm thankful that it's moving.
I wouldn't want to walk through
this forest at all.
Are you having foreboding thoughts?
If this ends without us encountering
Godzilla, then why did I come here?
Were you hoping to depend on luck?
It's fine if we're actively searching,
but if we pass by in a rush,
then we won't even find anything.
That's if we were actively searching
for Godzilla, right?
You and Colonel Leland
still don't understand one crucial aspect
of that thing.
It will never let humanity escape.
Even more so if we've come to provoke it
without a trace of fear.
So, it will be searching for us?
Is that some divine message from god?
It's a legend.
We Exif have been wandering
through space as vagrants
far longer than Earthlings have,
and we've witnessed
many civilizations destroyed.
Many have been regretfully destroyed
by creatures similar to Godzilla.
What's that?
He is the punishing iron hammer
for the arrogant.
For the species who pronounce themselves
as lords of creation,
a divine avenger will pay them a visit.
And so, he will...
What was that?
An earthquake?
Sound wave analysis!
All units, prepare for battle!
Movement detected at two o'clock!
It's approaching!
Evade! Evade, now!
We can't evade in time!
Run, Haruo.
Do as your soul cries out to do.
Yeah.
The propellant is leaking!
It's going to explode!
Hurry!
I'll get you for this!
That idiot.
Haruo, why?
He's going to record the moment
Godzilla activates its shield.
And to do that, you have to attack it.
Damn it, the electromagnetic sensor
isn't responding. Why?
What are you doing? Let's go!
But then, Captain Sakaki...
Then, get out.
Again! This time, at a closer distance!
Damn it!
I see.
Such light damage
won't cause the shield to activate.
Professor Martin!
Please record this next attack
with the sensor.
Captain! What's your plan?
I'm going to nose-dive
and slam into it.
What?
You bastard, I will...
This planet can go to hell.
Leland.
Colonel Leland was killed?
Yes. According to rank,
the command will now fall to me, though...
Can you do it?
I'll need to reassign a subordinate
who has disobeyed military regulations.
This is an emergency,
so please understand.
For this occasion, fine.
Bring back as many people as you can.
Understood.
Did you analyze the data sent to us?
Finished just now.
The electromagnetic metamaterial's
output has been recorded.
Just as you surmised, a shield exists.
The noise in question was confirmed.
It's not unified across its body.
There's clearly a concentrated spot.
The dorsal fin?
This is where the shield is generated.
Leland gave his life for this information.
Everyone, during that earlier encounter,
Colonel Leland died an honorable death.
And so,
as the Central Committee's direct priest,
I have accepted full responsibility
for this operation.
However, I cannot say that I am
the best man for this job.
All people are born to accomplish the task
they were meant to do.
This has been established
in our scriptures,
and as I shoulder the burden of a priest,
I cannot turn my back to this truth.
With the premise
of taking full responsibility,
I will now entrust all decision-making...
to Captain Sakaki, as the commander.
Okay, Haruo.
Your orders.
But that's insane!
The situation is dire,
so I'll skip the pleasantries.
I don't have an outlook
for humanity's future,
and I don't have enough of a strategy
to estimate our chances of winning.
However, I can say this.
Those who didn't yield to Godzilla
can proudly welcome another day.
This is not only a battle
to kill Godzilla.
What we are about to fight
is a humiliating future
with no choice
but to accept despair and resignation.
If we can reject and fight that,
we can once again dream of hope and pride.
Just as our ancestors did,
who thrived here before us.
That's right. If we don't retreat now,
if we don't show fear,
and if we put our lives on the line,
we've already won.
All we need to do is finish it.
Humanity's 22-year-long nightmare,
and Godzilla's 20,000-year era.
I look forward to your brave efforts.
That is all.
We'll begin our operation.
Yuko, you know Godzilla's position, right?
Yes.
It's about 80 kilometers north-north-east.
Moving southwest
at 40 kilometers an hour.
Set up transmission balloons
every 3,000 meters on the battlefield.
- We need optimal communicative reception.
- Roger.
Major Belu-be, provoke Godzilla
from a distance and watch its reaction.
Maintain that distance.
Sure, leave it to me.
Adam, watch for the atomic breath.
If electric potential rises,
escape immediately.
Understood.
Galu-gu.
I'll move to the trap point
and command the power suit team directly.
What?
I'll determine the EMP probes'
target point on-site.
However...
Galu-gu, how are the trap placements?
All according to plan.
Its weak point is the dorsal fin,
its back.
Since we need to concentrate our fire
at a close distance,
we have to let it pass the line of fire,
and lure it deeper into the valley.
So we only have one chance.
To make this plan work, we need
to place the traps deeper in the valley.
Artillery units are all in position.
We're ready.
Can we really lure it
all the way out here?
We have no choice but to believe in them.
Power suit team, move to the trap point.
We'll stand by.
I'm leaving the diversion to you, Belu-be.
Roger.
All squads, ascend to planned altitude.
Cross-delta pattern formation.
Godzilla detected
at the projected contact area.
All units, commence the diversion plan.
Right wing, squad one, attack!
Godzilla sighting confirmed!
Fire!
All units, turn!
Ascend in battle formation.
We'll attack as long as possible!
Target successfully diverted.
We can do this!
Evade!
Damn it! Adam! Take the left wing!
Roger, left wing, squad one.
- The impact area is bigger!
- It's hard to evade!
The evading maneuvers
are just a second delayed. Let's go!
- Right wing, squad two, follow and attack!
- Roger!
These guys aren't part of the plan!
What's wrong?
Major Belu-be!
It's what attacked Company A!
What? All squads provide cover fire
from a higher altitude.
Shoot them down
before more come from the forest!
Left wing, squad two, counterattack!
We have no time for the small fish.
Left wing, squad two,
continue the diversion!
Belu-be, are you okay?
It seems like you're in trouble.
Like the simulations predicted,
we should be able to lure it to the spot.
But we need more firepower.
It'll be night soon.
Can you hasten the process?
Ten have gone down.
Ammo and gas are almost depleted.
Adam. Do you copy?
Yes. Captain, I copy.
- I'm reassigning you.
- What, right now?
I'm shortening the time allotted
to lure Godzilla.
What? How can we do that?
I'll use the landing ships
for a bombardment to create a path.
What? Send the landing ships
to the frontline?
It's too dangerous.
If they get shot down,
how will we return to the mother ship?
But we're already home.
There's nowhere else to return to
but here. Isn't that right?
Have you lost your mind?
Let's do it.
It'll be useless
to prepare an escape route.
In order to win,
we need to play every hand.
This is why belligerent species
are difficult to deal with.
Adam, select five elite pilots.
Prepare the landing ships for takeoff.
Roger.
Major Belu-be, Second Lieutenant
Adam Bindewald, withdrawing!
Hurry and go! We'll handle this somehow!
Right wing, squad one, charge again!
Don't fall behind!
Six elite pilots, standing by!
We can go anytime!
Load all ammunition, even the reserves.
If we mess up, that's it.
Roger!
All landing ships, depart!
Starting from Godzilla's position,
create a path until the signal is given.
Fire at will, if you must.
Eliminate any obstacles in its way.
Commencing final diversion.
This is the point of no return.
We'll end this, now.
Listen up, the landing ships' mobility
can't evade an attack in time.
Once you know you're targeted,
abandon ship!
Captain, you're being lavish!
Hover squads, save ammo until
the route is open. Minimize losses.
Roger. We're almost out of gas.
So there's no second chances!
Turn!
The landing ships are almost here!
Spread out to avoid the bombardment!
All ships, drop the thermobaric bombs!
Scatter all that you have!
All landing ships, disperse! Spread out!
So who drew the short straw?
It's me, huh?
Okay! Godzilla is on the diversion path!
Now! All hover squads,
fire everything you have! This is it!
Roger! All squads, resume the diversion!
Increase attack frequency!
Damn it!
It's no good! I can't speed up!
All squads! Join the left wing!
Just a little more!
Diversion is in progress.
Godzilla is accelerating
toward the trap point!
Haruo, please hurry and board.
Yuko!
Why are you here?
I've always been on the power suit team.
Do you understand?
This is practically a suicide mission!
I want to become stronger!
That's what I thought when Grandpa died.
Godzilla entering Tanzawa Pass.
Only 500 meters to the trap point.
Damn it, I'm running out of gas!
Keep provoking it
and lure it to the last point.
Stay calm, this is the critical moment.
Trap point arrival, 100 meters!
You will return Earth to humans.
Fifty more meters!
Damn, I can't stand this.
At times like this, I'm jealous of those
who have a god to pray to.
All units, disperse!
Ten meters!
Godzilla is at the trap point!
Set off the trap!
Trap detonation complete!
Godzilla's movement stopped.
Did we succeed in capturing it?
Artillery unit, begin concentrated fire!
Asymmetrically permeable shield,
generated!
All gun ports, synchronized attack!
Body surface electromagnetic pulse
alignment sync at 75%!
At 75%? Is the pattern changing?
Alignment incomplete.
Unable to predict shield collapse!
Damn it, we can't attack like this.
Search for the noise. Hurry!
Noise detected.
The next shield collapse is in 20 seconds.
Twenty seconds?
Will the restraints hold?
Sync at 100%.
Detecting resonance with noise wave!
Shield collapse in ten seconds!
Artillery unit, fire!
If we can destroy the dorsal fin...
The shield is dropping!
Electric potential rising!
It's an atomic breath!
It can still attack?
The tissue on Godzilla's back
is regenerating!
The shield will be restored.
Shield will be up in about 200 seconds!
The restraints are no longer holding!
Damn it.
I'll finish this!
Haruo!
- What is he...
- With a close-range EMP attack,
he'll disrupt the noise pattern.
The pulse is changing. It's syncing again!
The next shield collapse
is in ten seconds!
Don't worry about me!
Destroy the rest of the dorsal fin!
But then you'll...
Doesn't matter! Fire!
The shield is now collapsing!
Fire! Fire until the gun barrel burns up!
The shield is dropping!
Okay, power suit unit, attack!
The EMP probes are entering its body!
All units, retreat! Retreat!
Electromagnetic concentration
in the air, rising!
It didn't work?
It did, the electromagnetic waves
are running wild inside it.
You bastard, I have...
killed you!
He really did it.
Haruo!
Look at this.
This body structure...
Yeah. Indeed a monster.
You've accomplished it, Captain.
Because everyone believed in
and supported me,
I could be so daring and get this far.
Even though we defeated it...
What was it, really?
How was it able to live for 20,000 years?
This is just my opinion,
but I think this is a different Godzilla
than the one that drove us from Earth.
But its appearance and abilities
were almost identical.
And that's exactly why.
Life's true nature is found in change.
No matter how gradual
the renewal cycle may be,
it's impossible to maintain
the exact same appearance.
So this one may be an offspring
that inherited Godzilla's form and nature.
Such a guess would actually
be the most natural.
Although the question remains
of why there was only this one. Also...
So, there's no guarantee
only one of them survived.
I apologize if what I'm saying
spoils the victory, but that is correct.
That's fine. Thanks to this battle,
we proved that we can defeat Godzilla.
Even if another one shows up,
we have nothing to fear.
Since we've established a valid strategy,
we can be more effective next time.
Personally, I would never want to cross
a tightrope like that ever again, though.
What was that?
Did anyone measure the vibration?
I'm picking it up on this sensor!
Find the origin using Gematoria analysis.
Yes, sir.
No, it can't be. Is the meter damaged?
- What is it?
- It's within two kilometers?
It's nearby!
That's ridiculous!
Electric potential, rising.
The numbers are unbelievable!
They are far greater than Godzilla's!
Underground heat source...
Wait, a plasma reaction? This can't be!
What's happening?
Is that...
Wh-What is that?
Godzilla?
Height over 300 meters and rising.
Surface vibroscope estimates a mass
of about 100,000 tons.
This is impossible!
Can that be a living creature?
Unbelievable!
No, according to the rules
for living creatures, this is correct.
Professor?
Indeed, the changing form of life
isn't just about decay.
If it continued its life activity
for 20,000 years, growing earnestly...
When those fleeting lives destined to die,
forget their humbleness
and sing praises of their glory,
such will shake the very heavens
and split the earth,
and they shall know the wrath
of the divine.
The inevitable incarnation of destruction.
So, you show yourself at last.
Since we last saw each other, it has been
20 years for us and 20,000 years for you.
It's been a while...
Oh, King of Destruction.
All landing ships, take off immediately!
Emergency retreat!
But we're still withdrawing!
Just take whoever's already onboard
before that thing attacks us!
Everyone, do whatever it takes
to get far away from here! Hurry!
What's that? A super oscillatory wave?
Estimated electric output
is measuring over 900 gigawatts.
Damn it!
What do you intend to do?
I'll divert its attention!
I'll buy time so people can run!
You don't think that'll work, do you?
You bastard... I will...
Subtitles by explosiveskull