I'll never forget that summer.
I spent a week in the old house
where my Mother grew up.
Planning Screenplay: Hayao Miyazaki
Production: Toshio Suzuki
Based on "The Borrowers"
by Mary Norton
Almost there now. Feeling all right?
Yes.
Directed by Hiromasa Yonebayashi
The Secret World of Arrietty
Ah! How many times have I told
Haru not to block the driveway?
I'll be back in a sec.
Okay.
Haru!
You're blocking the driveway again.
Sho?
Where are you?
Don't touch!
These aren't for you.
Arrietty!!
Yes?
You been outside again?
And you might clean up
this room, young lady.
It's my own little garden.
If you were to ask me, looks
like a great big mess.
Oh! Look is that a bay leaf?
Ah! This means your birthday
has come a little bit early.
That will do for a whole year.
The bay tree's so far away...
What if a human being saw you?
Please be careful..
I'm always careful.
The world is full of
dangerous creatures.
Your great uncle...
Was eaten by a toad,I know..
Don't these flowers smell just lovely?
So they do.
With a bit of sugar, I could
make some juice out of this.
Wait till tonight.I'll
borrow some for you.
What?!
It will be my first borrowing!
I've been practising night and day.
Father's home.
Hello Father...
Father, I want to ask you about...
I've seen a boy in the house.
What?!
I saw him too.
No! Arrietty...
There is no way! He couldn't have seen me!
I was safely hidden behind the bay leaf.
Father, are we still going borrowing this evening?
I won't hear of it.
It's too dangerous.
But he's only a boy!
It will be fine.
Father, I've been looking for it
for this for so long.
Children can be more terrifying
than grown-ups.
It will be fine!
Young boy needs to go bed early.
oh Thank you, Father!
But Pod...
But this boy seems to be ill.
So you needn't worry.
But still...
It will be alright, Mother.
I will be extra careful.
Arrietty is going to be 14 soon...
She is going to have to learn to get by
the world with or without our help.
Sometimes I feel that we're the
last Borrowers left in the world.
And if there is anything you need,
just ask Haru to help you.
All right.
Haru, I'm depending on you.
Yes madam.
Let's pull down the screen.
Keep the bugs out.
Shouldn't you wear something
a bit darker?
No, this will be alright.
Try and remember to borrow
some tissue paper.
And even a cube of sugar, perhaps?
We could happen to sweeten the juice
as I should be serving tea later.
But only if you can.
We'll be back home soon.
Please be careful.
Ofcourse.
Arrietty!
Bye...
Excuse me...
Arrietty would you hold these for me, please?
Yes Father.
Arrietty, hold on tight!
Arrietty?
Ready?
Yes
Ah Father! It's so big.
The world of the human beings.
The sugar's there in that pot.
Just wait here.
Father, you're great!
Now let's get that tissue.
Father, look.
and let that be your first borrowing.
But be careful, it's sharp.
Yes!
Father, borrowing is such fun!
Look down there.
Rats. Stay clear of them.
They're trouble for us.
I'm not afraid.
If they were to come,
I will defend with this!
Sometimes it's best not to
go looking for danger.
What is this place?
Human being made it to
house all of their dolls.
Ah! This would be perfect for us!
I'm sure Mother would love
that dresser over there.
These things aren't for borrowing.
Anything goes missing, they'd know
right away, so don't tell your Mother.
Oh...
Don't need to be afraid of me.
Hey...
I saw you out in the garden today.
My Mother, she told me about you.
She saw little people here
when she was young.
Was it you she saw?
Was it?
I'm so sorry, Father.
The boy saw me outside the garden today.
I should've been a bit more careful.
I hope he didn't frighten you.
But it's the best to not tell your
Mother. It will only worry her.
All right.
You don't always have to run. Take
the time to watch first then decide.
We're back.
Safe and sound.
Something wrong?
Things didn't go well this time.
This light gave out so we have
make out way back early.
Oh dear.
It meant we couldn't get your sugar.
Not to worry. At least you're
home, safe and sound.
Arrietty, you found something. Show
your Mother your very first borrowing.
What a pretty pin.
Time for bed.
Well, Good night then.
She looks completely worn out.
Shall I make us some tea?
Sho!
Come in the house.
You'll catch cold out there.
What? A cube of sugar?
Where was it?
It was left by the grating.
It's probably the same one
I dropped last night.
What?
What do you mean,
you dropped it?
Don't touch it, Arrietty.
Is that understood?
It's a trap.
They're gonna track us and
then try to catch us!
We'll have to stop borrowing
for a while.
Maybe they already
know where we are.
Pod, we'll have to move!
Ah!This was such a lovely house.
Now we'll have to start again.
Well, shall we see how things go?
Now eat, soup's getting cold.
Ah! Why did it have to be the sugar?
Thank you Arrietty.
I wanted to hang the clothes
while the sun's up.
It's pleasure. I love doing laundry.
I'm going to take a little nap, see you later.
Alright.
"You forgot something"
So you came back to me.
Hey..please..don't go.
You have to leave us alone.
I just wanted to tell you that.
I want to talk to you.
Human beings are dangerous.
If we're found, we have to move away.
My parents told me so.
So you have your family then?
I envy you.
You don't have one?
I suppose I do but I
never see my Father.
My mother is always working and
barely has time for me.
Is that so?...
I would really like to know your name.
You can call me Sho.
Do you even have one?
Well do you?
Of course I have a name!
It's Arrietty.
Arrietty... Arrietty...
That's a really pretty name.
Would it be possibly to see you?
Even if just for a moment.
Ah just a little peek. Ah please?
What's going on in here?
Arrghh!
Can't come in here!
Get out!
What got into that bird?
I never seen one behave like that before.
Perhaps it's time for
their nesting season.
Now I have to replace this screen.
Where do we keep them?
Are you all right?
Master Sho it's high time that...
you should take your medicine now.
Thank you, Haru.
I really feel fine, thanks.
The nesting season, eh?
Have yourself a lovely long rest.
Father...
I told you to stay away.
I'm sorry.
I thought I should take
care of it myself.
Father, he really didn't see me.
Your action put your family in danger.
I won't say it again.
Understood?
Yes.
I think it's time to start looking.
Huh?
For a new home.
Oh! Pod...
"You forgot something"
Hello! Got a package for you.
Thanks alot for the drink.
It's really hot today.
Do you know of any good pest
control companies around there?
Oh! Let's have a look.
Here's one! Squeaky Clean Services.
Pest control.
Squeaky Clean Services?
I'll write it down.
You having problems with mice?
Maybe it's mice or maybe it's
something more interesting.
Eh?
Between you and me, it's little people.
I've seen them myself.
I hear a crow tried to
fly into your room?
I hope it didn't scare you.
I am fine, Aunt Sadako.
Haru chased it out away.
I never seen anything like it.
A huge great beast of a crow...
Excitement's is the worst possible
thing in the world for his heart.
Haru, Sho came here for
some peace and quiet.
If anything were to happen
before the operation...
Ofcourse Madam.
Gracious! I realize Sho's mother's
work is terribly important...
but to go abroad on business and
leave a sick child behind?
It never easy for a young boy
to be without his mother.
You shouldn't worry
about it I don't mind.
I suppose the divorce was inevitable.
But why can't she be here,
when her only child needs her?
Aunt Sadako, who made that
little wooden house in my room?
Looks amazing.
Oh! You mean the dolls house?
It belonged to your mother
when she was a small child.
She had to leave it here years
ago when she moved away.
It was mum's?
My father had it made specialy to order...
As a place for all little people to live in.
Little?
Father always said he saw
little people in our home.
He waited years in the hope
of seeing them again.
He always said that house
was a present for them.
I'm afraid they never
showed themselves again.
Not in my father's lifetime,
regrettably not in mine.
Master Sho, I suppose you didn't see
any little people in your room?
Hmm..Unfortunately... not.
The dolls house has been passed
down from my Father...
Sure your mother will be very
happy for you to have it now.
Do you mean that?
Yes.
Have you looked inside?
It's really quite beautiful!
Haru, would you be so kind enough
to please turn off the lights?
Yes'm.
This is the living room.
All the furnishings were hand made
by a real furniture maker.
Beautiful don't you think?
Here's the library on the first floor.
There's even a study!
Wait until you see the next room
It's my personal favourite.
Haru, would you be so kind...
Quite certainly.
I think it opens this way.
It's wonderful!
It's perfectly detailed and
just like the real thing.
even th oven works.
You could use it for baking.
Ah.. It's beautiful!
It's a pity father's dream
never came true.
And it's been so Long...
Maybe the little people
are gone now.
Mother, we've had these
pictures three years.
Can't we change them?
I truly love those pictures.
I've always dreamed one day
I'd see the real ocean.
Anyway, there's no point to
changing them now.
Father's a bit late.
I hope he didn't get caught
in that downpour.
It's Father!
Sounds like he's in the back door.
Father! Are you ok?
I've twisted my leg.
Lucky Spiller here helped me.
Pod?
Oh dear, you're hurt!
Hurry, bring him in.
Does it hurt?
It's not broken.
I'll be fine in no time.
Come in. I'll get you
some cold water.
Here's a towel. Dry yourself.
Who are you?
I knew it. It's not just the
three of us after all.
I go home.
Please don't. Stay with us.
Have some tea.
Why don't I attend to your Father.
And you get Spiller a cup of tea.
Ofcourse.
Thank you Spiller.
Father's so lucky you came along.
We're so indebted to you.
Spiller, have you seen
other Borrowers?
You see, we thought we might be the
only ones left in the whole world.
I think this many.
Ah! Then Cousin Lupy must be alright!
Is that a bow your have?
Can I look?
And you use this for borrowing?
Give that back,Arrietty.
It's not a toy.
Give!
Gotta go.
But..but we just about to eat
something. You like to join us?
You eat this?
Cricket's leg!
Want some? It's real good.
No thank you!
Get well.
I thank you again.
I'll see him out.
Did you go looking for a new home then?
After I tripped and fell in the woods.
I couldn't move until Spiller found me.
You were lucky.
Spiller knows the land on the other
side of the river really well...
he told me he knows a few places that
we can look to build our new home.
That's good I suppose.
I'm not looking forward
to sleeping rough.
I wonder if we'll find anything
as nice as this though.
I'm glad there is more like us.
It's make me feel better.
Spiller, do you live home with your family?
Family? No, just me.
Alright, please come visit us again.
My mother's makes really amazing stew.
Okay.
Haru?
Arrietty, your stitches
need to be neater.
You'll have to start over.
Huh?
What? What's this big bag for?
Why do we need it?
I think I'll go and see how father is.
Father, may I come in?
How's your leg?
Ah! I'll be walking very soon.
Father?
Are we going to move away?
Human being have seen us.
We've no choice but to move.
I don't think that every
human being is dangerous.
Arrietty...
Long before you were born, there were
two other families living in this house.
One of them just went missing,
they just disappeared.
The other one moved away.
They were seen by human beings.
No matter what happens,
this family must survive.
Father...
oh my.. what's happening? Earthquake?
Mother!
It won't open.
The frame's buckled.
Not the wall!
Homily!
I always dreamed
of having a kitchen like this.
Gather only the things we need.
We won't be able to carry all that.
And Homily, take nothing
from the doll house, please.
I'll go ahead and make sure it's safe.
Stay with your Mother.
Yes.
You finally came back.
So, what do you think of the new kitchen?
Our house is in a really big mess.
But it doesn't matter.
I came to say goodbye today.
Can I look at you?
Beautiful.
We are going to move away from you.
We've been seen by human beings.
Borrowers aren't meant to be seen.
Borrowers...?
We borrow from human beings.
We take things we need, they won't miss.
Soap, cookies, sugar, electricity and gas too.
Even my great-grandfather
was a Borrower.
And nobody seen them? Never?
Probably.
I think this is all my fault.
Niya, don't be like that.
Be nice to her.
Arrietty, are there other little people
like you living hidden away in the house?
No, it's just my father, mother and I.
What about elsewhere?
I'm sure there's more.
But I've only met one so far.
Oh.
So, one day you might be the only one left.
Every year you get less and less...
that would mean you're a doomed species.
That's not true!
There's lots more of us.
Spiller said so!
Spiller?
He's one of us.
And spiller says there's
many more of us out there.
Do you have any idea, how many people
there are living in the world?
6.7 billion
6.7 billion?
And how many of you?
I don't know.
There's probably just a few of you left.
Before my mother told me, I didn't
know that borrowers even existed.
There are so many rare species
that have already died out...
I've only read about them
in my school books, though.
So many beautiful creatures...
Ended dying out as the environment changes.
It's sad, but maybe that's whats
fate has for the borrowers.
Fate, you say?
You're the one who changed things. And
we are the one to have to move away!
Father said that we must to survive by all means.
So we're moving away even though it's dangerous.
We make do, we always have. You don't know
anything about us! But we'll survive this.
And we'll not simply died out!
I'm sorry. You're right ofcourse.
In fact, I'm the one who's going to die out.
What?!
It's my heart.
They're going to operate next
week but it's hopeless.
Your heart...?
I've been sick since I was a child.
I could never play with other kids.
When I saw you, I wanted to
protect you. But I failed.
I can't even do that.
I hope that you can forgive me.
Your illness is really that bad?
What on Earth is this doing in here?
The kitchen from the dolls house!
I found you!
What is it?
My Mother... I heard her voice.
This really is a great kitchen.
You're not the only one here, I bet.
I have to go.
Let me out! Help me!
The ceiling's been moved.
Hello? Hello? Squeaky Clean Services?
Yeah, that is us.
Can you make an urgent house call?
Yeah sure.
We've something small in
the house but not mice.
Not mice?
I don't want them killed.
You need trapping services?
Yes, I want you to trap them.
Sho! Sho!
Sho!
Arrietty!
My mother's gone!
Someone took the roof off.
I think a human being got her!
Mother...
I will help you find her.
Someones locked the door!
Let's try the room next door.
It won't budge.
Wait!
Here's a way in.
Amazing!
No, that's not it.
Further down the road, there's a
dirt track. Turn in there.
Before the bridge?
No, no, after it.
Haru's opened this.
Then Haru must've taken
Mother someplace.
Are you alright?
oh dear oh Dear, What's taking them so long?
Mother! Where are you?
But I locked the...
Lock?
Could I have some hot milk please?
Yes ofcourse, ofcourse.. just a moment.
Thanks so much.
So hungry. Do you have any cookies?
Just a sec!
Mother!
Mother?
Arrietty!
Here I am, Here I am Arrietty!
I'm up here Mother!
Arrietty!
Oh what now? They finally found
the right road. Nincompoops!
Ah!! Another human being!
Mother, it's okay.
We'd like to take a look around the
house first if that's alright by you.
Take your time.
Now who could be spraying that?
Haru? Haru!
Madam!
What are they doing here?
Dear maddam, the little people are here!
Little people?
Yes.
Little people who steal.
Is it true?
Really!
They steal things from
all over the house.
That's why so much
was going missing.
Haru, what's gotten into you?
All this time I thought
it was my imagination.
Well, it wasn't.
You certainly didn't need
to call pest control.
We'd better hurry.
The house is full of them!
You'll believe me
when you see this.
This is their nest.
Nest?
It looks like a pile
of old junk to me.
What? what happened? I swear I saw it..
I swear..
Haru! I'm sending the
pest controllers away!
Now, wait just a minute.
The doll house!
Master Sho, may we come in?
Ofcourse.
Hard to believe, they stole
the little kitchen.
You'll see, it's gone.
It's not gone.
This kitchen, it looks so nice.
Please.. please.. wait madam.
I caught one in a jar!
That's strange. I wonder
what's troubling Haru.
Hmm?
What wonderful fresh herbs!
Ah! Someone's been making tea!
It's just as my father said.
There are little people living here.
Yes, there are.
So Haru really did see them?
Though she accused them of stealing.
They weren't thieves at all!
They were Borrowers!
Sorry?
I mean, I wish
I could see them.
I sure they're here somewhere.
I think so too.
Madam? Excuse me, madam!
Is there any place you
like us to start?
Are you alright?
They got out.
I had it right in here!
It's not just my imagination.
There are little people!
I'll get them next time I swear!
How far is it where we
are meeting Spiller?
It's just end of this wood.
Then we head down the river.
I'm so..so..I'll never make it.
Shh!
Let's move.
I can't do it...
Better have something to eat now.
We'll be walking till sunrise.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
We had to leave our lovely house
because of my stupid selfishness.
That's in the past.
We'll make another lovely house,
with the three of us together.
I'm going outside for some air.
Don't stray too far.
It's Niya!
Niya...
Niya?
Just a little further.
Spiller!
That's everything.
Now let's get moving.
Okay.
Mother, you alright?
Arrietty!
Sho!
Arrietty...
We're just about to leave.
I'm glad I got here in time.
Niya showed me the way.
Thank you. Look after yourself.
I brought this.
I would be very happy if you
could accept it this time.
Oh! Thank you.
I must go now.
When's your operation?
In two days.
I'll be okay. It's you that's
given me the courage to live.
It will bring you luck.
Thanks.
Thank you for having protected me.
Arrietty...
You take care of yourself.
Goodbye.
Arrietty, you're in my heart
for now and for always.
I'll never forget you, ever.