How long has it been raining?
Forever!
Not forever... no
For 100 years
They say billions of people once
lived on the earth
and the temperatures rose
the great cities fell
and this rain came
this terrible, toxic rain
Our ancestors saw it coming
a catastrophe
They built ECOBAN
the first living city
genetically engineered to survive
in a poisonous environment
ECOBAN became our refuge
Our salvation
Survivors came by the thousands
Begging to be let in
but our ancestors turned them away
Left them to die in the wasteland
The ones who survived became our workers
Mining the corbonite fields to feed our ECOBAN
Diggers we call them
The diggers need us...
We need them
Everybody wins
But some win more than others
Commander Lock
The foreman says your putting the
mens' safety at risk
What?
he's concenred that they're...
Safety? What about thier quotas?
They're behind as usual
Damn it
Now we'll have to lose this generator
It's one headache after another
with this old equipment
Sir!
You're going to have to shut
everything down right now
To save my men
It's too late for that
Jettison the deck!
If...
If you do that I'll order a mass strike
I'm in no mood to negotiate
Jettison it now!
Over my dead body!
Really?
Alright then, If you so insist...
Jay shoot him
- That's not my job, sir
- No?
Do it now!
When you file your official report,
mention that he drew a knife
Go back to ECOBAN, I'll clean this up
You should have seen him Cade
He had a smile on his face
He enjoys killing them
they're like insects to him
Lock is getting more and more powerful
every day
There is no way to challenge his authority
Just do your duty and stay out of his way
Please be careful, you know I worry about you
I know
and I've always been able to
take care of myself
You should worry about the diggers,
not me
Our carbon reserves are dwindling...
fast
if ECOBAN dies someday
Do you think that diggers will
shed a single tear for us?
They hate us
Don't forget where your loyalties lie
For now, let's just try to relax and
enjoy the ECOBAN centennial
Come on
What's wrong with you?
I'm tired that's all
Go home and rest
I'll come up
as soon as I can slip away
Cade here, go ahead
We have an intruder alert sir
- What?
- Someone's hacking into the DELOS neuroplex
Dispatch alpha patrol...
now!
I'm on my way
System wide alert
alpha patrol to the DELOS neuroplex
We have a security breech in the
control center
What's he up to?
Sir, he's hacked into the cube data
- The DELOS file?
- Yes sir
Do not kill him
I want this rat alive
Run, try and run
Alpha team, the intruder has left the
DELOS neuroplex
There he is!
The target is heading east towards the basil canal
Alpha team, move in
We've lost him sir
No sign of him down here
Control room, stop the respiran
This device is decades old
Cabin alert in the cortex...
I'm on my way
Well well well, this rat's got wings
Jay, report your position
I'm in the Time-Capsule.
I think he's here
Send back-up
Jay it's Cade,
Are you alright?
Acknowledge
Jay, are you okay?
Yes
Did you get a good look at him?
No I didn't, it happened
too fast
How could he have made it this far?
Commander Cade promised us that our
security was impenetrable,
But tonite our air tight security
was breeched by an intruder
who materialized like a ghost
and hacked our neural core
It seems we do have a ghost on our hands
only 1 man could have penetrated
the DELOS system
A man we all believed was dead
Dr. Noah
Yes
We found his old entry codes on the
device the intruder used to jam the respiran
But after 10 years, why would
he risk returning to ECOBAN?
To shut down the DELOS
neurogrid
and achieve what he failed to
accomplish 10 years ago
A final energy release
The old man said the bi-products of
our refineries
were killing the diggers
sulpher in the air, mercury in the water
He wanted to save them
So he tried to release ECOBANS energy reserves
and destroy the system he created
When we shut down the flow mid release,
He must have faked his death
That explains why we never
found his body
all this time, he's been hiding with the diggers
planning, preparing to destroy us
But we must destroy him first
He and the rebel army he has no doubt enlisted
We must strike them down before they attack
ECOBAN again
Rebel army?
There's no rebel army
Dr. Noah sent in only one errand boy
Today he got lucky that's all
Rest assured we will find him
and stop him before he makes his next move
This I promise to each and every one of you
We don't need promises
What we need is Dr. Noah commander
And you'll have him within 48 hours
In the meantime, I implore you to make no move
against the diggers
They may hate ECOBAN, but
we need them
If they're not already planning
a rebellion,
Lets not give them a reason to do it
Remember, they outnumber us
100 to 1
You want us to just sit around and simply
wait for another attack
We need to strike first, and strike hard
or face the consequences
We must not hesitate!
Gentlemen, our carbon reserves are
becoming dangerously low
Step up security and find Dr. Noah
Act quickly before it is too late
That is all
Lock
Prepare your men
just in case
You can't follow simple instructions
This would have been alot easier if
you hadn't tripped the alarm
Easier yes... but not half as
much fun
Go ahead, make jokes
By now Lock has probably got half his troops
scouring the wasteland for you
well at least you got the data
Toss it over here Shua
Nice throw kid
Well well , let's see what's new in that
bohemoth of a city?
What's this? The systems dying
It's running at one tenth capacity
Is it enough for an energy release?
Perhaps
What's gonna happen if you release all
that power?
We'll blast open the sky
No, in ECOBAN. What will
happen to all the people?
Most will survive, but they won't have it easy
they'll have to use solar
energy and work shoulder to shoulder
with the rest of us
They'd kill us first
What do you care what happens to them?
Today, I saw someone I used to know
Oh?
Jay, she's all grown up and she's beautiful
She's ECOBAN
A girl? You're dead to them
in ECOBAN
So you better forget her
Now find that kid brother of yours
that orphan kid you take care of
It's too dangerous for him in the city.
Hanging around
with those rejects. Those petty hoodlums
He's ok, Let him pass
Come on, pass it Zed!
Hmmm.. hey you, cut that funeral crap!
Play something with a pulse
Don't smoke it all!
Hey Woody, wanna drag?
It's called tobacco
Nah
Woody
Huh, Shua!
Long time no see buddy
Woody, let's go
Hey Shua!
Big man with his big attitude
I tell ya, one of these days I'll kick his ass
Hey Moe, have you seen my uh...  propeller?
This?
No, it's about this size
Shua look what I got you
Great! So now those punks are teaching
you how to steal. Is that it?
Steal? No!
I found it
That's it, I found it. You said you needed
it for your glider
Don't hang around with them Woody
You'll end up stupid or dead
Now give me that harmonica
Ok
Oh wow!
What's that on your wrist?
A bracelet
Where did you get it from?
A girl gave it to me
Who is she? Your girlfriend?
Professor Noah says the sky used to be blue
'sky blue' he said. That's what they called the colour
My mom says there's a place where the sky
is always blue!
It's an island they call Gibraltar
You wanna see something?
What?
It's stuck!
This place is off limits
- We should go back
- Why?
I'm scared
Don't worry! I'll protect you
Come on Jay, I'm gonna show
you something
You will remember it forever
Now, open them
Whoa!
It's incredible
How'd you know about this?
Professor Noah said this would happen today
In Gibraltar, people see this every day
That's where I'm going
You could come too, I guess
That sky was so beautiful
it blinded our eyes
But it didn't last long
It disappeared
behind the clouds
That was the last I ever saw of it
And the last I saw of Shua
In ECOBAN they're living like kings
While we're dying in polluted slums
They call us diggers and they treat us like dirt
We want air we can breath, water we can drink
Or the next thing we dig will be ECOBANS grave
Sounds like another riots coming
Better get out of here quick
You scared? My brothers not scared
Shua's not scared of anything at all
Stop calling him your brother
Shua was born in ECOBAN, he's one of them
Such a big man, such a big talk
Big talk? What'ya mean Moe?
He's gonna find Gibraltar.
Gibraltar! What is he crazy?
It's a myth
Forget that loser kid, and stick with me
I'll teach you how to
kick some ass
Woody! Where you go...?
- Woody!
These damn riots are no good
Bad for business, bad all around
Isn't it worse to do nothing?
Maybe. Then again maybe not. All
depends on your philosophy
Mine is stay alive
Hey, how'd you get half a handcuff anyway?
ECOBAN's security is coming!
Woody, where did you go? You had
me worried to death
You don't just run into a riot. You could
get yourself killed
Look at that
Stay here Woody...
Glider glasses
Come back
Cool
Hey, If you see Woody, tell him
to go home right away
Jay, you're headed right for the riots.
Let's turn back
Jay! Jay! Are you alright?
Jay. Come in, come in Jay
Shua?
Shua
it's you isn't it?
You shouldn't have come here Jay
I thought that you were dead Shua
The Shua you knew is dead
We are enemies, we have to be
Why? I don't think the
diggers are my enemies
So that's why you poison them?
Because they are your friends
Now when we get up there, you let me
do the talking
Cause I know how to handle him
Fools!
Go hide in there
Don't worry about it, if he gives us
the slightest bit of trouble
I'll just kick his teeth in
Oh hey, Shua! Good to see ya buddy
What's goin on?
Got a business proposition for ya...
Gotta move fast cause time is short
Goliath is waiting for you at the
Fantasia club
It's cool Shua...
Shua! You have no idea how much I've missed you
Kate said you'd been killed
but I always dreamed you survived
and finally made it to Gibraltar
Go back to ECOBAN Jay.
That's where you belong
Damn I'm gonna explode
I got a rocket in my pocket baby
Rocket huh?
More like a firecracker
- You want me to kick your ass Zed!
- Knock it off
Can't you see we're talkin business?
ECOBAN is planning something big
Every day, trucks are moving weapons into
the wasteland
Yeah and we're gonna jack em all
If you're willing to help with our plan
We'll cut you in
Help how?
Now, woody tells us you built a glider
You fly past the security post
creating a distraction and...
And?
And we sell the stuff on the black market
to our friend the butcher
How noble of you
You know Shua, we can't all be heroes
Heroes? You're nothing but parasites
praying on the weak to make a filthy buck
You make me ill
Son of a....!
Ok, now here's my proposition
go ahead and get yourselves killed
but leave Woody out of it
Anything happens to him
and you'll will wish you were dead
Big man, waving his big gun around
Next time I see him
I'm gonna wipe that smurk off
his face
Come on let's party
Give me music!
Woody, let's talk... man to man
Why? What did I do wrong?
Nothing, you're a good kid. It's just...
It's just what Shua?
What is it?
I might have to go away soon
You're leaving? You're going to Gibraltar
without me aren't you?
I'll be good if you take me with you
Don't!
There is no Gibraltar
You wouldn't like it where I'm going
Here
All yours
A gift
But, your girlfriend gave it to you
She's not my girlfriend
Shua, promise me something?
- Promise what?
- Promise that you'll come back for me?
We'll see each other again
Oh Shua
Jay found him and didn't report it?
Yes, sir. Who is he?
- That'll be all for now
- Sir
Mya, be sure to keep
this to yourself
Yes, sir
Our target is Dr. Noah's accomplice.
He's hiding in an abandoned tanker in
the contaminated zone
He's dangerous...
shoot to kill
Spread out
Jay!
It's clean, no one here!
Sir no trace of him below!
Why didn't you tell me?
He's nothing more than a murderer
Have you forgotten why he fled ECOBAN?
That one! Look
Where?
Oh yeah, no problem
Sorry we're late, traffic was a bitch
Who the hell are you?
Show me your pass
The pass?
Sure, which pass do you want
Look, this is a restricted area, military only
Turn this truck around
Oh yeah, that pass...
I got one right...
I said turn this thing around
I got a red pass, a blue pass...
Get out of the truck
Who needs a pass now?
Hit it!
Now!
Enough! Let them go
We're gonna be so rich!
Who gave you the authority to move
weapons into the contaminated zone?
We set a little trap Cade
A successful trap that caught a few
of Dr. Noah's rebellious vermin
Let me remind you, I am still in command
of this operation
Or have you forgotten Lock
Who is in command?
Oh yes. You should really
ask the governor about that
The stolen transport is at the north bay docks
Wipe them all out
And that is not a suggestion. That's an
order. Got it?
What's all the ruckus down there?
Sounds like a party
It is. They ripped off an ECOBAN truck
So why are you up here with a tired
old man?
Maybe I prefer your company
You're thinking about that girl again
Maybe I am, so what?
Tomorrow after the energy release, none
of that will matter anymore
Will it?
Don't be such a fatalist
If you follow my instructions this time
And activate the safety pod.
You'll survive the blast
You want to keep living don't you?
Of course I want to live
Well I'm glad to hear it
That's the first sensible thing
you've said in weeks
But if it doesn't work
I mean, if I don't...
Look after Woody ok?
You're coming back! You look after him
Gentlemen, we are open for business
We'll take everything.
Name your price
Cool, what's this one?
What the hell is it?
Why's it blinking?
You idiots!
- Freeze!
- Drop your weapons!
Drop them now
No!
Move
Get away!
Don't make a peep
Just stay here till I come
get ya ok?
No more ammo! What do we do now?
Just stick with me
I'll get us outta here
Don't think, Run!
Ow shit!
Moe!
Stings like a son of a bitch!
Moe, Don't Move!
I'm coming!
Zed!
I'm so, so cold
I'll go find Shua
No please don't go.
I'm afraid
Show me how quiet you can be
- You're pretty good at it
- I am?
Oh
Sure, just stay here and be quiet and
I'll be back
Hush!
On your feet, against the wall!
Against the wall now!
He's not the one we're looking for,
scour the entire place
Yes, sir
Where's Cheyenne?
Woody?
You can't see me
You'll be alright
How did you lose your sight?
I was born this way, alot of us were
Why Shua?
Why'd you have to come back?
I thought I'd finished you off
You didn't finish anything, you just
let me take the blame for you
You were to blame. You took Jay outside
ECOBAN, It was forbidden!
Cade, you and I both know what
happened that day. You grabbed the knife
Enough!
You killed the trooper
You told them it was me
Jay never learned the truth did she?
She knows enough
She know you want to destroy ECOBAN,
that's all that matters
Woody!
Shua....
Jay move! Get out of the way!
I thought I was taking care of him
all this time, but I was wrong
He was the one that was taking
care of me
I'm Sorry, Zed
I'm going to ECOBAN
Who wants to come?
I appreciate it everyone
Thanks
Let's help Dr. Noah bring the place down
For Zed
Governor, with the diggers rioting, our refineries
are at a standstill and our carbon reserves
are rapidly being depleted
ECOBAN's dying, if Dr. Noah's men strike, it
won't survive an energy release
Commander Cade has failed
Now it's my turn
My troops will smoke them out of thier hiding places
And get rid if them once and for all
This I promise
You will never find them
In fact, you don't even have to look
Keep your troops exactly where they are
There is no need to mobilze them at all
Just wait
Dr. Noah's men will be coming right to us, and
this time we'll be ready for them
They will not escape, and we will crush them
I didn't expect you to come back
We are both full of surprises
aren't we?
This is goodbye Cade
By tomorrow this will all be over
and Shua will be dead
Shua? Shua's been dead for years in
case you haven't heard
Jay, where are you going?
Jay!
I love you
You love ECOBAN
Don't forget where your
loyalties lie
Wherever you are Shua,
that's where I belong
I want to give you something Jay
A sky full of light
Sky blue!
Maybe we'll see each other again
Maybe we'll find Gibraltar if it exists
But if we don't
Look for me in the skies
And know you're with me, always
Commander Lock has takin control
of ECOBAN security
We believe an attack is eminent
From this moment on, you are
all on full alert
Well
Are the preparations complete?
Commander Lock, all troops are in position, ready
and awaiting your orders sir
Where is Cade?
Commander Cade is heading for
the DELOS core, sir
Good
Get these men in position now,
we're wasting time
Yes, sir
Alpha patrol, move out
If the diggers have any hope for a future, we
must unleash ECOBAN's energy reserves
Your task is to shut down the power supply...
before Shua releases the core
Good luck
Ok, it's dead ahead
Ready...
Fire!
Governor, our trap is now set
And so we wait
No, it's already begun
There, straight ahead
Hey, aren't you going too fast?
Not fast enough
Hold on a sec... wait...
Wait! The bridge has a gap!
That stupid geezer
Goliath hit the brakes,
what's a matter with you?
Noah told me to floor it
That was wicked! Oh god, did you see that?
What a freakin rush,
let's do it again man
Hey Shua buddy, need a lift?
All set?
Ok Moe, now ya gotta really kick
some ass
So you finally made it
All that persistence for nothing
Cade,
If you kill me...
There'll be others
Maybe there could be others
Except one thing. They
won't have Jay will they?
They won't take her away from me
the way you did
No!
Jay
Jay, don't!
Don't make me...
don't make me do this
Jay!
Jay!!!
Grandpa, it's so warm
Yes it is, it is